Chapter 1

Sounds of fingers vigorously tapping on a mechanical keyboard along with clicking noises filled the dimly lit room. A certain 30 something so male was concentrating on his game of choice while enjoying the company of his fellow gaming comrades.

"F*king noobs, what are you aiming at!"
"God damn shitty team."

After giving them some more words of praise and affection the male exited the game and gave his desk a good thump with his palm, which made it shake in response. Well maybe he was a little bit angry, but if you had to play with teammates as he got, you would probably react in a similar way.

He leaned back in his overpriced gamin chair and looked at his small apartment in which he lived alone. His posture was crooked and his back almost formed a lump. He had bags under his eyes, making him look extremely irritable.

"Might as well check out my gmail..."

After scrolling through some advertisements which he promptly deleted, he spotted a strange message at the top which he clicked.

"Is this some kind of scam?"

'Congratulations on getting chosen as an alpha tester for our new Xianxia themed game, immerse yourself in our faction-based narrative, build your sect or clan up and become the number one under the heavens.'

"Sect building? is this some kind of strategy game? sounds a bit like an RPG too..."

After reading the colorful email, Matthew decided to give the whole thing a try though it looked like he could fill in a lot of stuff and create his own character right here and now for some reason.

"So I get one main character? guess it's more an RPG then strategy game, maybe you can upgrade stuff in your base or something."

After clicking a big button that said 'Get started' he was taken to a character creator that had a lot of options to choose from, Mat took his time in shaping his characters face, giving him manly facial features and long silver hair, his eyes were blue. For the build, he gave him a robust body type, quite muscular but not an overly beefcake look. 6'2'' as the height which was 190 cm.

"Well that took a bit longer than expected, there are way too many choices in this thing... let's see ..."

He was able to choose clothes for his character, it ranged from all sorts of robes through which he started clicking through and tried to match them to make his creation look nice and badass. He ended with a white one, the character ended up in white clothes. He as wearing mostly functional ones that wouldn't get in the way of a fight, none of those baggy type robes that those sword immortals liked to wear while zooming along with their oversized swords, though that was something he wouldn't be opposed if he got one to fly around. The model had a smaller robe over his body that covered the head part with his long silver locks peeking out for other people to see his abs were also visible as he decided to put a form-fitting shirt, would be a waste to have a muscular body and not show it off right?

"Okay, what's next... starting point?"

You start off as a young Qi Condensation inner disciple of a prominent sect.
You start off as the last Nascent Soul elder of a mostly destroyed sect.
You start off as a Core Formation young senior of a declining family clan.
( Character will be aged to fill the role)

"Wait... what does that even mean, you make me spend so much time on designing and then you want to turn my perfect boy to an old raisin or a little kid?"

The male grumbled and then looked at the choices that he was giving, he might as well finish it up not like it really mattered to him as he as just killing some time between gaming and before going to sleep.

"Ah whatever, guess choice 3 sounds close enough I'll go with that."

The screen changed to a short backstory that he didn't really want to go through as he started quickly scrolling down, the explanations to the game and world were also mostly skipped as it sounded like gibberish to Mat that was already confused with the Chinese sounding names and terms. Finally, after some skillful clicking, he found himself at the skills menu.

"Ah, guess I get to chose some starting stuff, let's see..."

There weren't that many skills to choose from, but he ended up going for the elemental type packet, with some premade skills that looked the coolest from the descriptions and pictures that were next to them, plus he thought that if he as going with the pure white look, he should add some nice lighting to the mix to fit his character.

"Guess that's it for now... just need to add the name and I'm done... Zhang... is that the first name or last name... hehe"

It didn't take him long to put in Dong as his name, in his mind this being the only obvious choice for a name in this kind of setting. His childish grin didn't last for long as he suddenly heard a strange robotic sounding voice.

[Core Formation beginner package selected]

[Beginning transfer in 3...2...1...]

"Wait what, that's not coming from the PC..."

His vision started going hazy as he heard the voice that sounded like it was speaking directly into his mind. He didn't know what happened afterward as he drifted off to sleep and the last thing he saw was the blinking screen of his computer.

Chapter 2

His ears were ringing and he felt drowsy as he finally came too, Matthew rubbed his glabella while slowly opening his eyes and he was greeted with green. He found himself leaning up against a big tree in an open field, a lot of grass around him with more trees after that as he was apparently in a clearing with no one around him.

"God damn, what happe..."

98%....99%....100%... Ding.

[Downloading of the package finished.]

[Initiating tutorial]

"What the..."

After waking up he was greeted by the sound of the similar robotic voice followed by a dinging sound similar to a microwave being done cooking. As the so called tutorial started he could see some screens pop up in front of him with a lot of words and prompts and something that looked it could fit into a mmorpg game. Matt flailed at the sudden semi-transparent screens in front of him with his hands but they just went through it, though this made him realize that his hands looked a lot rougher then what he was used to.

"Wait what is this..."

He looked at his hands, they looked rough and callused and looked like he could snap some bones with those. He then stood up and started feeling up his body only to realize that he changed into the character he was previously designing along with the same getup that he chose for it. He couldn't see his face but it was just like he made it, just in super high definition as this was a real-life person.

"D-did I just get wished away into another world? a video game? or both?"

He started frantically looking around the place, not really seeing anyone in the vicinity besides a few hopping bunnies, though they looked a bit strange with those horns sticking out from their foreheads. The square screens in front of his face kept following him around whenever he turned his head to the sides which made him stop and read what was written in them.

[Welcome to 'Immortals R Us' the best cultivation system in all the realms]

[Earn spirit points through various ways and increase your cultivation]

[Increase your faction's reputation to earn rewards, it's always more fun in a group!]

"Uh... what kind of name is that... is this some kind of scam... "

After reading through some introduction gibberish Mat, that was now called Zhang Dong could see his character's status screen though it didn't have much to it besides showing his name and cultivation realm and some more stuffs.

Name: Zhang Dong

Affiliation: Zhang Clan

Cultivation Base Qi: Core Formation(Pending)

Cultivation Base Body: Foundation Establishment(Pending)

Techniques : (Pending)

Dao: (Pending)

While looking through the screen he spotted a flashing button in the top right corner which drew his attention, it read 'Unload starter package' which didn't really mean anything to him at the moment as he found himself pointing with his finger at the button and pressing it in mid-air. He was greeted with the robotic sounding voice after he did that and a countdown. As it counted down he started getting stressed not really knowing if he did the right thing or not but he couldn't really do anything about it now.

[Uploading starter package, prepare to receive the information]

He suddenly felt a sharp pain, his head started throbbing while he collapsed to his knees tightly grasping his head as he squirmed around the grassy ground. His legs twitching around and kicking to the sides as he rolled side to side while holding his head with both his hands and screaming in pain. He could feel information being injected directly into his brain as he received the knowledge about techniques which he previously selected while in the character creator but not like he remembered what he clicked at that point.

Zhang Dong also felt a sharp pain inside of his body in his dantian area, his core was changing. It started crackling with lightning, spinning around as it transformed into an elemental lightning core making his whole body release static energy as it discharged some of it into the surrounding area.

[Transformation of the core finished, lightning core established]

[Beginning body refining...]

The animals in the vicinity could see the grown man squirming on the ground in a weird way, just trashing about while vomiting black blood which made most of them flee out into the forest. He could feel his body tensing up, muscles expanding and bones shifting around as he got stronger and his body got accustomed to the changes, but that wasn't the end of it as knowledge of martial art techniques started flooding his mind, the ways of dao and how to use his cultivation along with the techniques that came with it.

[....DING... starter package uploaded... have a nice day and don't forget to check out your inventory, you will find a couple of goodies!]

"S-shit god almighty...ughhh"

After some projectile vomiting of some black blood and rolling onto his back to pass out for a good 15 minutes Dong finally woke up while still twitching. After wiping the tears and snot from his face and checking out if he didn't pee himself during the whole debacle he rolled to his knees and while supporting himself on the tree, he stood up and took in a deep breath while trying to calm himself down.

"Woah... guess I know kung fu?... they made it look way easier in the movies..."

Chapter 3

Took a while for him to stop hearing a buzzing sound in his ears, his eyes were hurting and his whole body was aching. Matt felt like he had run a marathon, his muscles were sore and twitching while blue and white lightning energy crackled from them. The pain started to subside after a while after which he noticed that his fingers were digging into the tree that he was leaning on, bending the hard wooden bark on it like he was pushing into some soft cardboard. He pulled his hand away to examine it, everything felt surreal at the moment all of his senses felt like they were enhanced as he had a problem in focusing his vision on it.

"Okay let's calm down..."

Matt had a habit of talking to himself, probably because he never had many people to talk to back in his previous world, spending most of his time at the computer screen and just surviving through his workday without interacting with his coworkers all that much. He was a classic introvert, nothing special.

He felt the information insert itself into his brain, which was a lot of gibberish at first but after a while, he managed to piece it together as it was mostly information about the world he was in right now. He found out that he was in isekai of sorts, the planet was similar to earth but a lot bigger, closer to the size of the sun, quite huge. There were quite a few moons surrounding this planet, which he could even see now in daylight as they were quite close by, some looking green some gray and others red.

After shaking off the sweat and snot, surprisingly his clothes weren't covered in the black blood sludge that was covering the ground, guess they had some self-cleaning enchantment on it or something, which he would probably confirm after checking out is equipment screen and so he did.

*Um... status?*

He thought to himself as the screen popped up in front of him, he tried playing around with it managing to enlarge it with his fingers if he wanted it swiping at it as you would on a tablet screen, though he noticed that if he thought about it the screens and prompts would change to suit his needs without any hand movement.

*Oh neat, will take some time to get used to.*

Name : | Zhang Dong
Affiliation : | Zhang Clan
Spirit Points :  | 9999
Cultivation Base Qi : | Core Formation [Early Stage 0%] (Lightning Core)
Cultivation Base Body : | Foundation Establishment [Middle Stage 0%] (Silver Body)
Techniques : | Lightning Qi cultivation art, Silver Body Arts, Thunderlight Sword, Thunder Movement Art...
Dao :  | Dao of Heavenly Lightning , Dao of Smithing and Crafting
Other :  | Senior Aura

Matt read through the status screen, it had a lot more entries now than it previously had which piqued his interest a bit. He was mostly a gaming guy but in his off time he did read a couple of Xianxia and  Wuxia type novels, though he was more of a western than eastern fantasy type of guy as he always got confused with the naming sense in those novels and had to reread it to actually know who was interacting with who, plus the tragedy of coming back to an old novel and not knowing what the hell was even going on anymore was a real thing.

*Okay guess we are going with a cultivation system, the stage kind of one...*

The status screen showed him basic stats but nothing too specific, so he hovered his finger over the cultivation base which made it go into a bit more detail.

Cultivation Base Qi :

|

Core Formation

Cultivation Realm

|

Early Stage 0%

Foundation type

|

Heavenly Lightning Foundation(Immortal Grade)

Core type

|

Lightning Core (Immortal Grade)

*Immortal grade huh?*

He somehow knew what that meant as the information was dumped into his head just a few moments ago so he knew about the grading system, it went on from Common, Mortal, Earth, Heaven, Immortal, Celestial Immortal and then finally Eternal. Though from what he could tell on this planet Immortal grade was the cream of the crop, also those ranks had sub ranks ranging from low grade to perfect grade.

He also tapped the spirit point tab, finding out in the description that it was the name of this systems point system and he could spend them in various ways to increase his level, he could increase his cultivation base directly but he could also spend it on his support skills and techniques plus the system gave him a tip that he could increase all of his skills the old fashioned way as he gained said points if he did it himself.

He tabbed out of that screen and noticed a colorful blinding icon, that had a glowing sword and shield and a sack with hat looked like to be spirit stones.

*God damn, does this thing have a cash shop?*

He clicked the icon and it brought him to a cash shop screen, it looked like your regular free to play, mmorpg kind of cash shop with a search bar, on the left side he could see all the tabs like 'Magic Treasures' 'Spirit Herbs' 'Items' 'Weapons' 'Cultivation Techniques' and the sorts, while on the right side he could see the descriptions and the costs, they all had various costs ranging from 10 SP for some low grade common pills to millions and billions for some Immortal and beyond ones.

*God damn it, what kind of scam is this running, how am I supposed to get a million Spirit Points? Do they grow on trees? Can I suck them from some voluptuous babes bosom? wait... I hope you can do that..."

But soon he would find out one way of getting them as he suddenly felt a jolt run through his spine which made him turn around. He saw the unsuspecting bunny with the horn staring at him, his eyes red and out for blood. As he was staring at the creature he noticed that it wasn't just a regular-sized rabbit it was more wolf sized. Which to him was quite huge and as he blinked the creature decided to charge at him, horn first after giving out a high pitched scream.

"Wait... Mr. Rabbit lets talk about this like civilized people..."

Matt gulped as he wasn't much of a fighter, going through his life without having actually fought anyone, at most he got into shouting matches with some people but that didn't really count for much. So being the heavenly god of destruction that he was, the Senior that all his juniors look up to... he just froze in place like a brick. The monster rabbit didn't stop as it gained speed and momentum but our godly senior just stood there while sweating profusely.

*Is this it... am I going to get done in by Bugs Bunny here... I'm still a virgin for Christ sake...*

As the impending doom in the shape of a sharp horn was flying at his face he finally mustered up some courage to push his legs to try to dodge, but he wasn't dodging to the side, he was far to untrained for that to happen as he propelled himself backward. Though not being used to his new bodies enhanced stats he lost his balance the ground caved in and he did a backflip hitting the demon spawn of a rabbit right in the body promptly turning the creature into meat paste while he himself flew 50 meters back and hitting the tree on his way which broke in half as his face hit it, he tumbled a ways back before coming to a stop, he was on his back with his legs back while his butt was showing and his knees were resting on the ground next to his shoulders, if you didn't know what was going on you might think he was presenting his rear end to his lover or something.

[Frenzied Rabbit Slain ( Qi Condensation 6th stage ) Earned 50 Spirit Points

A note from Kuropon

Hello author here, don't expect this to be anything grand as this is the first time I'm writing anything. I'm sorry for any grammatical or spelling mistakes that I make as this is my second language. Not really sure where I'm going to take the story if I ever finish it as I'm more of a go with the flow kind of person and don't really plan ahead that much.

Also playing around with the text editor to make it look a bit nicer, having tables to keep everything more orderly is always a nice thing. Also open to critique just be easy on this noobie, I cry easy ((´д｀))

Chapter 4

There wasn't much pain as Matt found out that his new body was a lot more sturdy than his old one was, something probably to do with the silver body thing and how it was at the foundation establishment stage. He rolled to the side and pushed himself off the ground a bit surprised at what just happened. His foot was quite bloody and his hair had some tree bark in it as he looked at the area where he 'kicked'  the creature while trying to fell for his dire life.

"I-is it dead?"

He looked at the destroyed tree in the distance, he couldn't see if the horned rabbit was dead or not as the tree was in the way but he felt somehow that it was not among the living anymore after the robotic voice announced that he had slain the creature. But being the true hero that he was, Matt grasped a branch from the side and slowly crept up to the spot that the 'battle' took place.

"Hey, there Mr. Bunny... you're not going to pounce at me again are you?"

Gulping sounds could be heard as the over six-foot-tall man crept to the now tree stump,  he peeked behind it slowly and could see the red trail and entrails of the monster spread on the grassy field. It looked dead, not even twitching or anything as he slowly tippty toed closer and closer. His hand grasped the wide branch as he finally was at the head part, his kick having parted the weaker creature in two. After a few pokes to the head with his trusted 'weapon' he sighed in relief, then a vein could be seen appearing on his forehead as he gave the dead thing a wack with the branch putting it in an even more miserable state than it previously as.

"Damn rabbit! Who's your daddy now you little shit!"

The rabbit didn't reply but Matt started venting his emotions while poking and hitting it with the stick which broke in two after a while. He tossed to the side and calmed down, looking at the monster and then to his spirit points which now counted up to 10049.

*Guess that's one way to do it... why did it have to be this kind of setting...*

The novel protagonists made it look easy, get an op system? Learn some badass skills? Slay some monsters and court some ladies. Reality as a bit different as he didn't really know how to react as the monster run towards him, even though it was a trash mob that he could fart to death at this point.

*I have to get my shit together, these cultivation worlds are always so bloodthirsty, everything will stab you in the back if you look weird in their general direction*

Matt wasn't much of a fighter and if he could choose he would rather take the pacifist route and talk it out, the whole 'Kill them if they besmirch your honor' thing didn't really go with his life philosophy. But this was a nice wake-up call as he scanned through his list of skills and abilities. He had to test them out to see if he had any way of defending himself if anything bigger then the rabbit would attack him. What if some huge black duck was next? Or a yellow grizzly bear... wait wasn't that in that other franchise... well never mind.

*Okay I'm sure I had some skills in there...Lightning Qi cultivation art, Silver Body Arts, Thunderlight Sword, Thunder Movement Art*

He mumbled to himself while focusing on some skills, not really knowing what to do. He focused on the Thunderlight Sword one, did he need to get a sword to test it out? He had a feeling that he didn't need one for it. Matt focused on the name and then on his hand, he kind of knew what to do as he started gathering spirit energy into his right hand. He closed it into a fist, its electricity crackled around it and then with a loud boom of thunder a saber of light expanded from his fist being 1,5 m long.

"Woah... is this a lightsaber..."

It looked similar to it, but looked more unstable with the lightning energy buzzing and jolting out of the blade's shaft. He swung it around and it made familiar noises that you would expect a lightsaber to make. Matt looked to the side at the half-collapsed tree and then back to his light weapon. He took aim and swung to cut at the part that was still standing and with one swipe managed to slice it in half, the poor tree just falling apart even more and probably cursing him and his ancestors to a life of misery as it faded away.

"...okay... this could work...what else do we have"

He went through his skills a bit, somehow managing to throw some lightning-induced punches and kicks that made thundering sounds in the process and scaring the wildlife around but probably alerting some potential baddies in the process. Matt slowly got used to his new body finding it quite more robust than his old one, even after running around and flailing his hands and legs in all directions while 'training' he didn't feel all that tired, he was also strong, like really really strong. He could lift up large boulders with ease, and crush rock into dust with those big burly hands of his which gave him quite the confidence boost.

During the whole training montage that took about an hour he finally noticed that he had something stuck to his belt, it looked like a ring with some Chinese characters on it. Weirdly enough he could understand what was written on it 'Spatial Storage Ring' and he already knew what it was for. He focused his mind on it, injecting his spiritual qi into it, the ring had some items in it. He slowly started playing around with it and after fiddling for some time managed to remove all the objects and place them on the ground in front of him to examine.

"Hm... is that a flying sword or something? Some strange pills... a golden hammer... some scrolls and some books ..."

He glanced at the things but didn't really know what to do with them as he only had a rudimentary knowledge of the world around him, the gaming system didn't give him anything specific but he knew that those were probably some starting items that he received along with his package.

"Could really use something to identify stuff with... I have no idea what this is used for...wait a second..."

He remembered about the item store that he previously saw and pulled up the window with it.

"Hm, let's see..."

He poked the search field and was able to input words into it, he wrote 'Analize' but then changed it to 'Appraisal' as that gave more coherent choices.

Glasses of the Sage | Big glasses that give you that nerdy look, insert some spiritual qi into them to appraise items. | 5000 Spirit Points
Eye of Appraisal (Skill, Evolving type) | Look at an item to appraise it, appraisal stats vary by skill rank (You are able to appraise items 1 cultivation realm below your current cultivation at start) | 9000 Spirit Points
Pill of Appraisal | Swallow it to temporarily gain the Appraisal skill and identify items.  | 500 Spirit Points per pill.

There were more choices in the store but those were the options that piqued his interests.

*Hm... the Glasses sound okay... but it doesn't say if there is a limit at what they can identify... also not really keen on wearing those. The pills look like a scam to just dump points into so the middle chose looks the best... but uhh... that almost all my points...*

After contemplating for a bit more he went with the skill choice, it looked like the best deal at the time and it was an evolving skill so he could probably level it up. After pressing the buy button he looked at this spirit point number go down into the gutter.

[Uploading skill, prepare to receive the information]

"Oh shit, not this again..."

Chapter 5

His eyes got extremely itchy, it was like a bunch of mosquitoes decided to have a crazy party right inside his eye sockets. It was uncomfortable, to say the least, plus his forehead was also throbbing as the information on how to use the new skill was shoved in there as well. Matt wanted to strangle the person who made the information distribution in this strange system and also give him a couple of slaps, but this time around it didn't take that long till he felt a release from the itching and pain, probably something to do with it only being one skill this time around and not a full information dump.

Matt rubbed his teary eyes and straightened out his posture as he blinked a couple of times, his vision going from hazy to sharp as time passed. He looked down at the items on the ground, focusing on the sword and as he did he could see some words popping up.

Crystalline Flying Sword :  | Earth high grade, perfect condition

The sword was bluish-green and looked like it was made from crystals, it wasn't pointed at the end but was flatter. It was quite a lot bigger than regular swords making Matt think of a peculiar one-eyed, one-armed manga protag that had a rage problem. He figured that it was this big so that he could stand on it as he flew about and he kind of knew how he should do it, thanks to the previous information dump that he received.

*Okay moving on...*

He started scanning the rest of the items, managing to identify everything some the pills were used for restoring spirit qi, while others were used to restore health they were all in the earth grade which made him think that's probably what would be around his level, maybe a bit below. The books and scrolls were just cultivation manuals of the skills that he already knew, he wasn't sure what they were for as he already knew them, maybe he could sell them? Then he turned his attention to the map which he took and started to examine, it didn't come together with a gps though as he didn't have any idea where on the map he actually was.

*Well... this doesn't help at all... just some strange continents that I don't know, At least there is a name... Hm ...Heavenly Spirit Realm? Well, that sounds quite generic as you can get... can the system help with this somehow?*

Not much on the map could be discerned beside that so while grasping the map he opened up the system window wondering if he could find some help there. He was pleasantly surprised as the system did give him a new prompt which he clicked and selected.

World map item identified, absorb? Yes. No.

After a little jolt to the skull which he was now getting used to he noticed that he got a map option in his system screen, he could even bring up a mini-map that spread through a couple of kilometers around him. He could see a lot of dots some red, some green, some blue. Which he deducted that the red ones were probably monsters or beasts like the horned rabbit he just killed, green ones probably friendlies and blue ones maybe unknowns? He would have to confirm his theory later but now he went back to examining his stuff as he was mostly done.

He looked at his clothes, checked his pockets and scanned the ring once more to check if he didn't miss anything important and found some shiny gold coins tucked away in a sack by his belt with some shiny crystals to boot. After identifying them as plain gold coins and spirit stones he got a prompt once more as he was identifying the stones while his system window was out.

Spirit source detected, absorb lower grade spirit stone? Yes. No.

Matt raised an eyebrow and selected yes, and watched as the spirit stone dissolved into lights which then entered his body through his skin.

Spirit source absorbed, you gained 10 spirit points.

"I guess it works like that too? Neat."

He placed the pouch of coins and spirit stone into his storage ring along with the rest of the items he wouldn't really be using at the moment. He didn't absorb any more of the spirit stones as he didn't know if he would need those for something later and from what the info dump in his brain was telling him there were many uses for those, ranging from crafting to just plain old trading with others for other treasures and items.

The golden hammer was identified as a crafting tool with some nice bonuses, but he would need to get his hands on some crafting manuals to go with his crafting skills that he already had gained in the starter package. He tossed the shiny thing into his spatial ring and looked as it just vanished into thin air still a bit baffled by the whole sight.

*Well I guess I should get this thing to work now."

He looked at the huge person-sized sword on the ground and picked it up with his hand, surprisingly it wasn't all that heavy though as he gave it a few practice swings it had a nice ring to it and generated a nice gust, you wouldn't want to get hit by this thing.Matt looked at the flying sword and concentrated his Qi, he was starting to get the hang of this whole cultivation thing as he could feel the sword absorb his spirit. The sword started to shake and gently vibrate hovering upwards as he let go of the grip.

*This is getting even neater with each passing moment...*

He forgot about the dangers around him as the flying sword started swishing about , wobbling at start but then it swished back and forth like a drone, though he noticed that he couldn't control it too well if it got more than 10 meters away from his body, might have just been his inexperience or maybe that it wasn't a sword meant for fighting that much and more as a way of transport. Matt hopped on the wide blade and ordered the weapon to move upwards firstly just letting it move him up and down as he tried to balance himself on it without falling over. Luckily he came equipped with the sword flying technique which let him move around on it, while maybe a bit slow at first but with time he would probably get a bit more comfortable. After moving in circles while staying close to the ground a smile was plastered all over his face, as who wouldn't like to zoom around the area on a kick-ass looking sword like this? Though after a moment of bad judgment he jumped off while the sword punctured the tree stump in the middle of the field. He placed it in his ring afterward and placed the ring on his finger as he relaxed a gathered his thoughts.

*What am I supposed to do now, this is all nice and fine but I can't just run around in this field or forest without a place to go... wait wasn't there some setting to this...*

He opened up his system menu again and quickly moved over to his stat page and he clearly cloud see that he was affiliated with the Zhang clan, he clicked on that to bring up if there was any explanation for it.

Zhang Clan : |

Once a prominent family clan but now it's in decline, it's patriarch had failed in advancing his cultivation and suffered for it with early death. The clan is in dire need in higher cultivation elders so it has reached out to side families for help.

The clan is situated in the Spirit Spring City with a population of 10 million.

"Guess that would be a good place to start, now how do I get to Spirit Spring City..."

Chapter 6

Matt who was named Zhang Dong, which he still thought sounded hilarious in his mind clicked on his system screen and took a peek at his own name, wondering if it would bring out anything about his new persona and it did.

Zhang Dong : |

 Age : 30 , Mother Zhang Biyu (Deceased) , Father Zhang Peng (Deceased)

You were the child of two clan members of the Zhang Clan, your mother died while giving birth, your father a regular elder member of the clan brought you up till he also died after a beast attack, you were 12 years old at the time. Swearing vengeance on the beast you dedicated your life to slaying the evil monster. You didn't interact with the rest of the clan giving them the impression of a stoic type. You left the clan after reaching the age of 20 and ventured the world. Your cultivation level exceeds your peers, your cultivation choice of heavenly dao makes you give off a noble aura. After reaching the core formation realm you managed to slay the evil beast that took your parents in a ferocious battle. Afterward, you heard the rumors that your old clan was in decline and decided to see if you could help them out with anything.

*Well that's a nice little story, well at least I don't have any family members that know me, that would make it weird if they started acting all familiar with me. Guess going with lightning wasn't such a bad idea if it will give me a popularity boost like that.*

Matt smirked while reading through his short bio, that didn't tell him much about his situation, he was more or less a blank slate to the people of the Zhang clan as it said that he didn't interact with them all that much from a young age, so it wouldn't be weird if he couldn't identify anyone if he showed up, he didn't really look forward to any awkward situations that could come from that.

*Okay spirit spring city, where is that and how do I get there...*

He fumbled around his map system and found a handy GPS like option that let him search for things and after writing in the name of the city it showed him the direction that he should be heading in. Matt opened up his eyes wide as he looked at just how far away the city was, it was in the hundreds of thousands of kilometers, which was more than the whole circumference of planet earth that he lived on. Guess he would have to figure out this flying sword thing otherwise he would probably spend his whole life just walking there.

*Why do they have to make everything so big in here, is someone overcompensating with something here?*

His brows were furrowed as he looked at his destination, though he could see that there were other smaller landmarks on his way, plus he had some gold coins and spirit stones so he would probably have a place that he could stay in while traveling. Matt's train of thought got interrupted as he spotted a lot of red dots moving in his direction, the thunder sounds were quite loud that he was producing with most of his skills so more trouble was heading his way, this made him sweat a bit.

*Okay... calm down, they are just weak little creatures, my power level should be way above them, they shouldn't even be able to scratch me if they are below the early stage of the foundation level.*

Z.D. tried to pump himself up while looking in the direction of the red dots and as they appeared he noticed that it was the same wolf sized bunny creature type as before. He had his appraisal skill this time around so as he focused on the fuzzy balls he could see their cultivation realm, safe to say they were all in the Qi Condensation realm, which made him a bit less tense but he was still uncomfortable. The horny bunnies looked at him with their red eyes that were filled with rage and madness and gave out high pitched sounds before charging at him.

*Why are these things even attacking me, shouldn't they run when they meet someone of a higher cultivation level, thought magical beast should be somewhat intelligent... Maybe it has something to do with the Frenzied prefix in their name? *

He focused on the charging creatures while feeling tense, but as he did so he noticed that they were moving really slow, like as if they were in bullet time. He could clearly see them charging at him all 5 of the little buggers, crooked teeth in their mouths and pointy horns ready to penetrate him in various ways. He was quite a distance away from then so he decided to test out the waters, he quickly grasped a larger rock from the ground and then promptly chucked it at the closes one of the buggers. The round object just flew through the air with momentum and hit the creature right on the mouth. The monster hare gave out a strange sound before his head exploded along with the rock that hit him.

Frenzied Rabbit Slain ( Qi Condensation 5th stage ) Earned 40 Spirit Points

*One down...*

After the first kill Matt decided to keep it safe and started running around and chucking rocks at the fuzzy buggers, sometimes he hit on the first try, sometimes he had to run away while the monster bunnies chased him around the field but he was much faster than them so after a while, all the creatures were slain and covered the grassy field in their blood.

*Geez... what's up with these shitty rabbits...*

They all laid dead before his mighty rock chucking skills, he felt a sense of accomplishment even though he bested the beasts in a cowardly way, it was better to be safe then sorry though if people from this world saw a core formation senior running away from Qi Condensation creatures while chucking rocks at them they would probably think that they had a bit too much to drink. He would probably have to grow some balls before he started interacting with the people of this world or else they would see him as quite the oddball.

*Damn, after a hard-fought battle I sure could use something to drink, I didn't see anything back there in the spatial ring though.*

His belly rumbled a bit as well as he was getting hungry, he rubbed his belly as he felt the hunger, he stopped a minute as he noticed that he had abs now, long gone was his flabby belly that he was used to now he too had a nice beach body. After some self-encouragement in the form of patting his muscles he decided to check the item shop if it had any food and it did, it even had hamburgers and soft drinks but there were various other foods around ones that made his eye bulge out, but mostly because they have astronomical costs to them so he went with the cheap junk food, for now, guess old habits die hard.

After his burping from his soft drink, he decided to take a look at that flying blade of his but before he could do that he noticed that even more red dots were approaching him and one from them was looking a lot bigger than the rest which gave him a bad premonition.

Chapter 7

He started wondering if he should move from this open spot as he was in the same damn area for the past couple of hours, no wonder some bloodthirsty creatures were just emerging one after another if he just hung around the same spot all the time for no reason whatsoever.

But using the help of his 'radar' he picked up some rocks and decided to use the same tactic, hey why fix it if it's not broken? He took aim and fired off his rock bullets hitting some of the rabbit mobs right on the head, his aim getting better and better with each of his throws. Though after he managed to take care of a couple of the raging monsters he could hear some trees fall down in the direction that the monsters were coming from. He could hear the trunks snapping and the birds flying away as something got closer and closer and then he saw it. It was a giant rabbit monster, about as big as a polar bear, it had black fur that was kind of shiny, it's build was a bit lankier and lean then the what the smaller rabbits had and instead of a horn sticking out of its forehead, it looked like it had a bladed weapon stuck there instead.

Matt threw the rocks at it, but they shattered against the monster's fur that seemed to be metallic in nature so his tactic of kiting around the mobs went out of the window. He focused his eyes on the large monster that was roaring at him in a much lower-pitched voice then the rest of its kin.

Enraged Obsidian Hare Foundation Establishment Middle Stage

*Guess throwing rocks at that thing won't work... should I try with a boulder?*

The creature didn't give our hero much time to think as it charged at him while its eyes glowed a deep crimson, it didn't really care about its kin either as it just plowed through them as it was much faster than the low-level rabbit monsters. It tried skewering the man dressed in white, though it missed the mark by a hair as Matt managed to dodge to the side now without losing it's cool, the creature was a lot faster then the other ones but not as fast as he was, though he barely managed the maneuver still not being used to this combat thing but he was slowly getting used to it, adrenaline was pumping through his veins as he also managed to dodge a swipe from the thing's large paw that had huge claws on it, though he lost some of his long locks to it as he backed away, even more, trying to formulate a plan in his mind while the Hare kept swiping and trying to headbutt him.

*D-damn... this thing isn't stopping... what the hell can I do, the rocks aren't doing anything... should I try hitting it with one of those strange skills that I have...*

He didn't think about just running away as probably running into the forest where more of these things could get him wouldn't be such a good idea, either way, so he used the skill that he previously played around the most and summoned the sparkling light sword that he had. Matt was still a bit scared to get too close to that thing, what if this lightsaber of his doesn't do anything and he ends up getting mauled by the thing, so he waited for the thing to do another large swipe at him with its paw which he dodged to the side and after finally maning up he delivered a sideswipe, the aim was the large arm of the creature. As the flashing sword came in contact with the black metal like fur of the monster it discharged electricity directly into its body, who would have thought that the metal in the creature's fur would be good at conducting, right?

The sword of light dug into the flesh of the monster but it didn't sever it in one clean swipe as out Zhang Dong didn't have that much practice in swinging a sword of light just yet, but it did some damage as he stepped back even using his movement technique that made thunderous sounds.

"...Huff... Gasp... I-i can do this..."

He could see that the creature wasn't looking so great as the loss of its front paw made it limp quite a bit, making it lose a lot of speed and quickness in the process. While holding his sword he managed to cleave one of the grunts of the larger monsters in half as it tried to attack him from the side. He didn't charge at the injured thing as it was still going at him for some reason, it was clearly mad with rage not really caring for it's well being as a normal animal would have probably fled by now. He danced around it some more, poking and cutting it here and there mostly aiming at the limbs and after a while, the Hare couldn't really move as all of its limbs had huge gashes in them. Before going for the last hit he made sure to back away from it so that the smaller mobs would follow and so that he could clear them out as well and after that he delivered the finishing blow, separating the creatures head from its body in one clean swipe. Of course, after he did that, he collapsed on the ground onto his knees and continued panting.

Enraged Obsidian Hare Slain, gained 6100 Spirit Points

*I did it...*

It wasn't the cleanest fight and he was fighting something much below his level,  but being a normal person on the inside it was tough to get used to slaying huge monsters on his first day. He stood up and examined the body of the thing in front of him, Matt started to think that he should probably get out of this place as soon as possible because these berserked mobs would probably be appearing more often and what will he do if the big boss decides to great him and he ends up in its belly.

As he looked at the cleaved head he noticed something shiny and round sticking out from the neck, he moved in close and picked up the orb that was dark in color and about the size of a golf ball.

Obsidian Hare Core discovered, absorb spiritual energy?

"Oh? guess I can use this... think this thing can also be used for crafting things... I think I'll save it for later."

He pocketed the monster core and looked at it, using his light sword to cut of the blade looking horn of the creature, thinking that he might be able to sell it somewhere later, this giving him the vibe of looting a monster mob after you killed it in a video game. He also wondered if he could find any cores on the lesser rabbits, but he gave up on that after looking at the gory bunny bits all over the place, he didn't really want to go through all those animal entrails, though he did take the horns, maybe he could use those as throwing knives or something. And just as he did that he noticed more red dots coming this way.

"Okay, screw this..."

He tossed out his flying sword and jumped on it, making it slowly move upwards and into the air and would you know it as he was in the air he could see more of the same creatures down below walking out of the bushes, he could probably grind quite a bit of points on those things but he wanted to get to some town and just lie down and take a warm shower.

*Wait, do they even have showers in this world?*

Guess a hot bath would do too, so he moved the sword forward, it wasn't moving fast for now as it wobbled around in the air in the direction of the first settlement which looked like a small village, it was still quite far but as he picked up the speed and got used to flying he would probably reach it before the sun went down, he didn't even want to think about the weird creatures that came out at night in this world.

"Next stop, a warm bath!"

Chapter 8

-Schwing-

Sounds of a sword cutting through the air could be heard as Matt flew through the air, at first he had to go down to his knees and hold on for his dear life as he was wooshing through the air a bit too fast, but after a while he started getting used to it now looking like a bro surfing around in the sky with his hands on the sides as he balanced it out. He didn't have to do that though but he just liked how it looked, the flying sword technique kind of made his feet stick to the sword blade so he wouldn't fall down it also generated a little spiritual forcefield around his body, covering it in a thin membrane so that the winds wouldn't get to him, though his long silver locks flopped around all over the place which was a bit annoying if he tried doing anything besides flying in one direction while facing it.

He was getting close and close to his destination, his speed was picking up as he hovered above the large forest of the beasties and there were many of them there, he could see the monsters duking it out as he was above them, he was lucky that most of the flying beasts left him alone as he discovered that he could release his aura that was of the core formation level and if he did that the non frenzied beasts would quickly turn around and flee from him. He also learned that he could more or less judge the power of the beasts around him even without his appraisal skill, but he could probably use it for other things later on and he felt that 9000 points weren't all that much as he got  over 6000 points for slaying a monster that wasn't all that strong.

He started whistling to himself as he flew around, trying out various cool poses. He crossed his arms in front of himself and struck a haughty pose, then he moved his arms behind his back and straightened out his back to look like a seasoned master, the fluttering of his hair and robe made him give off a refined aura. He thought that the last one was probably the proper one to use if he meets other people, as the other ones made him look either a bit goofy or eccentric, this was a good middle ground of a mysterious expert.

As he flew longer and longer he noticed that the magical beasts were kind of getting weaker and weaker, that was probably the indication that he was getting closer to some human settlements as the weaker the mobs the safer it would be in the vicinity of any village. The thought of some rest and relaxation made him release more of his spiritual power which he had loads to spare the flying technique wasn't that hard on his cultivation, maybe because he had it cultivated to a high level. Though as the village on the map starting getting closer and closer he started to worry a bit.

*Will they be friendly? don't think they'll attack me like these monsters right?*

He wasn't sure about the people around this world, he hoped they weren't that bloodthirsty but this was a world ruled by the laws of the jungle it was a lot less organized as his old one plus he wasn't part of it that much. His introverted character trait made him a bit reclusive around other people, but if he found someone he hit it off he was able to keep up a conversation. Though he probably wouldn't need to interact that much with others, he would probably just find himself some food and a place to stay for the night his spatial ring didn't have any magical hotels in it, though the cash shop did but the pricing on those was horrendous.

Matt gave off a sight and continued with his trajectory, now even being able to detect some humans on the way, they weren't that far from him and he stopped and looked at the map of his and as he calculated with his big brain that he was just a couple of kilometers away from them, he might have just read it from the map, but no one would ever know that. The small habitat which he presumed would be a village wasn't far from those people, he hoped there wouldn't be any problem when he arrived but he slowed down a bit to see if his clothes were in order as he didn't want to look scuffed when he arrived or make a fool out of himself, he also hoped that his choice of clothes wouldn't be considered strange he did look like a martial artist and all.

As he got closer and closer to the blue dots and noticed that there were 5 of them and they were moving in the direction of a red dot. They were probably a hunting party going for some beast meat. He slowed down and increased his altitude a bit as he didn't really want to alert anyone to his position, he hoped that they wouldn't see him from so high up while he himself with his enhanced vision could see what was going on.

After getting to a good spot he stopped and focused his eyes below him, his vision zooming up to the desired spot as he could see 5 men encircling what seemed to look like a deer, or maybe it was a moose? He couldn't really tell though it was quite big for a deer more of the size of a large horse with huge antlers that looked like they could do a lot of damage, the tail that it had looked also a bit strange it had a strange pattern to it and looked like crocodile skin which didn't match the rest of the big deer which had brown fur on it. It wasn't very strong he could feel it even without his appraisal skill as it was even weaker than the monster rabbits that he previously met.

*Interesting... I'll just wait and see how these people hunt I guess...*

Matt wasn't all that in a hurry as he was close to his destination and with the help of his flying sword he wouldn't take long, plus he could follow these people back there if there were problems with the map. He could see some arrows poking out of the beasts hide as it ran and tried to evade the attackers, the men were getting closer and closer though slowly tiring the deer out while plunging more sharp arrows into it and it didn't take long before it fell to the side and the people had some meat to transport, it was quite uneventful as he watched the people tend to the dead creature, slicing of its tail and horns and putting those away, probably to sell it or use it for something else.

*Hm, well I guess it would look strange if I popped out now and asked them for directions... I'll just keep it low key and follow them for now, maybe I'll learn something while at it.*

He rubbed his chin while the men dug into the deer's flesh, taking out a round object that was probably a beast core, but it was really small compared to the one that he got. Then he heard a howl and could see the men become alert as they got in a defensive stance. He glanced at his minimap and could see a lot of red dots moving closer and closer to where the men where and soon enough he could see a big pack of what seemed to look like wolves but they were red in color and quite scary looking.

*Gulp... they can take those out, right?*

He wasn't very keen on interfering and if the people survived in this environment the probably were capable fighters, right? He apprised the wolves and they had the obvious 'Crimson Wolf' Name to them, but there was another thing, the just like the ones that attacked him had the 'Frenzied' and some had the 'Enraged' prefix as well. Judging by that fact they would probably throw themselves on the people, plus the natives didn't look that confident as Matt could see them shouting to each other while backing away. They even abandoned their hunted deer while backing away, probably hoping that the wolfs would go for it instead of them but the beasts ignored the fresh dead meat and threw themselves at the hunters that weren't too keen on a fight.

*Hey watch out!*

Chapter 9

Hunter point of view :

Cheng Yun was a member of the Tatar Tribe, he just reached the age of 15. This was a special occasion in his tribe, at this age you were considered an adult and you had to start real work for your tribe. The males were obligated to hunt or if they weren't cut out for that gather food or take care of the livestock. Most of them preferred hunting though, it was the most honorable type of work in the tribe, hunting down beasts and protecting your family was an honor for these people.

The men from the tribe formed smaller hunting parties of five people, this was his first time out in the deep forest, children were forbidden in going in too deep as dangers lurked at every corner. Lately, the creatures in the forest became more and more unruly as his fellow tribesmen came back injured more and more, even a few deaths happened. They reported about how the beasts were acting strange, eyes going red while they lost their mind, they charged at the humans and other beasts without any sense of self, just throwing at anything that moved and ripping it apart, they even went after their own kin from time to time.

Though the village he was part of couldn't support themselves on only farmed food and gathered fruits and vegetables from the forest, they needed meat dense in calories and also Qi. After a mortal began their cultivation and went their first step into the Qi Condensation stage, even if it was the lowest one they started to need food high in spiritual Qi, the stronger the person became the more they needed, there were all kind of spirit foods around but they were hard to produce out in a small village as they had , the seeds were hard to come by and you needed special qi rich soil to grow them, so the best way to circumvent that was hunting what most people called spirit beasts.

A spirit beast of the same cultivation as a human mostly came out on top still, it was possible to win for humans. That was why they formed small or large hunting parties, mostly targeting the herbivore types of creatures as they weren't as ferocious as the carnivores and were less crafty than the omnivores. But lately, the beasts started acting up, getting violent and attacking people that were clearly of a higher caliber then them. The people didn't know what was driving them crazy but they would have to get to the bottom of this if they didn't want to have a hard time during wintertime.

They managed to find a nice adult Serpent Tailed Deer, it would bring quite a lot of meat for the people in the tribe, he was more or less in a support role on this hunt, using his bow skills that he was quite proud of as he was the best at his age group. He managed to hit the beast in a couple of spots but the damage wasn't that great, but after a while, it added up and with the help of the more experienced hunters they managed to bring the spirit beast down without any loses on their part.

He was in charge of the field dressing,  meaning it was the removal of the animal’s internal organs, also known as the entrails, which was necessary to preserve its meat. While he was doing the dirty work the others used their time to pluck out any arrows from the deer and any that they could salvage from the vicinity. They fished out the core and were ready to move, they didn't want to wait for that much and the smell of blood would probably attract the other beasts. They were quite unlucky though as a pack of crimson wolves suddenly appeared around them.

The cultivation levels of the tribe members weren't all that high, the highest was at the Qi Condensation 6th level, they were poor and it was hard to cultivate without any resources. The condensation stage ranged from 1 to 12 but every three levels you would reach a bottleneck, so between the 3/4, 6/7, 9/10 stages and then at the 12th stage the biggest one as you had to form your foundation. Every bottleneck was harder than the last one, so without resources being them guidance from a seasoned master, spirit herbs, cultivation manuals it was impossible to advance.

The wolves were between the 4th and 6th levels, but there were over a dozen of them and they were only five. This was quite the predicament as the only option was to flee, they didn't stand a chance against those beasts that also didn't care much for their own safety and didn't feel any pain when attacked. They abandoned the deer in the hopes that the wolves would go for it and started backing away, but they just howled and looked at them with a ferocious glint in their eyes, more interested in the moving humans than the ready to devour dead beast in front of them.

The hunters fired off a couple of arrows that did some surface damage and then bolted out of there with haste as the chase started, they knew the forest quite well so even though the wolves would be faster than them in an open field as they run through the forest while having to go through bushes and trees they could somehow flee. Though that was the case for the four experienced older hunters, the boy was panicking and tripped over a root that sealed his fate. He soon felt sharp teeth going into his thigh as one of the red beasts caught up to him as he was trying to get up. The pain was unbearable and he screamed, his fellow tribesmen looked at him in fear but they knew that the couldn't do much for the youth.

But at this moment something strange happened, as another wolf was about to go for a neck bite while the other one was chewing the kid's thigh a sudden explosion happened kicking up dust and debris into the area. The hunters covered their eyes as the smoke flew into their eyes trying to make out what was going on, was it another horrendous beast that came to wreck more chaos? But to their surprise, after the dust had cleared they could see a huge sword in the spot that the charging wolf was in, sliced in half. They saw a man standing on the hilt of the large sword, hands behind his back and standing straight up with an otherworldly aura to him

He looked like an immortal in that pure white robe, the top of his face was covered with his robe and his back was facing the four hunters while the scared bitten boy was a couple of meters from the huge sword. They could see lightning crackling from him as he looked at the crimson wolf that was next to the boy, it wasn't biting his leg any more as it growled and flung itself at the new enemy only to be bisected by a strange glowing sword that the stranger formed in his hand.

If they could they would have cheered on but they were too shocked to say anything and just gulped while watching as all the wolves charged at the robust-looking cultivator. They stood no chance as with every swipe of his light sword a beast fell. Soon they were all dead in a gory puddle around the white-robed man. He stood there for a moment as he looked at the slain monsters and then looked down at the youth that was still in need of medical attention.

Cheng Yun looked up while grasping his leg, he was bleeding out as the wolf had mangled up his artery. He would probably die soon if nothing was done. Then he heard the man speak, he had a domineering voice. "Here, eat this." He placed a pill in his mouth which the boy swallowed with haste. After the pill went down his throat he could feel it's healing properties getting released and his leg started patching itself up at a visible rate and within a minute it was all healed up, he could even stand up while looking at his torn pants and blood that they were soaked in.

The man was also surprised about the healing speed, though the boy and hunters didn't see that as he was hiding his face behind his hood...

Chapter 10

*Holy fucking shit... they are going to die...*

Matt looked on as the shit hit the fan and the wolves started chasing after the human hunters, he was still hovering above the crowd as it all happened , it looked at first that they would be able to escape as they were quite agile and moving through the forest quickly while the beasts were a bit less used to running there. But one of them tripped and fell right on his face, Matt did a mental facepalm at the sprawled out kid that was right below him, he looked quite comedic. Though this was no laughing matter as he knew that a wolf could catch up to the fallen teenager.

*Damn... I have to help them... but... *

If you had to assign an alignment to Matt he was probably in the neutral good category, if he played any rpg games he always went for the good guy options, not really liking to replay them with the evil path options. But having a good personality and acting out on it were two different things as he froze while the kid was close to getting attacked by one of the monsters. He wanted to act, he wanted to be the hero of the story and whatnot, but that was harder than expected. While he was looking down at the scene, the wolf finally chomped down on the hunter's leg, ferociously shaking its head to damage it more and more as it tore into the flesh. He could see the fear in the kid's eyes, he screamed out in pain the other people around him didn't go to help him as they only stopped for a moment before turning around wanting to flee once more.

*Fuck... move you damn coward!*

He gave himself a slap to the face and gritted his teeth, finally getting a hold of some courage and finally forcing himself to charge directly down while on his sword. He used quite a bit of his spiritual power to fling himself downward hopped up on adrenaline as he charged. The sword slammed into the ground and luckily killed the second wolf that was going for the boy's neck, he finally arrived. He managed to keep his balance on the sword, his eyes looked around while the dust was settling he didn't even notice that he was still holding his flying sword pose from all the stress but after the other wolf that was at the boy let him go to charge in his direction he used his sword skill to quickly take care of him.

These crimson wolves were about the same levels as the trash mob rabbits that he fought, maybe a bit more agile. He took care of them quite fast just hopping down from the sword and swiping at each one once as the stupid mutts just blindly charged at him without any strategy whatsoever. He cleaned up quite fast, thinking to himself that he shouldn't be scared of creatures of this level down the road. He glanced at the boy that was bleeding out, he noticed the spot that he was bitten and there was a lot of blood and he knew they the artery was probably severed, the kid would bleed out in a short while.

Matt remembered that he did have some healing pills on him, so he fumbled around with his storage ring and brought out one of them not really sure if it would work but that was the only thing that he could do at this point, he didn't have any healing skills whatsoever. He didn't wait long as he moved closer and just popped the pill into the young male's mouth while hoping for the best. Luckily it worked, he could see the leg glowing a bit as it healed itself up which made him stare at the phenomenon. He sighed in relief and then he looked back at the dead wolfs.

Now he was in a bit of a predicament, he managed to save the kid but now he had five people stare at his back. He wasn't good at speaking with others as he was very reclusive in his old life. The hunters themselves were shocked down to the core, they never saw a cultivator of this caliber in their entire life and didn't know how to react. They thought it would be rude to speak up first in front of someone of this immense strength so they kept quiet, the boy below him also turned around and started bowing his head down after examining his now healed leg.

"I-it's fine you don't need to do that... I was just passing by and saw you having some trouble... no biggy..."

*No biggy? do people even talk like that here... wait can they even understand me in this world... please don't speak in mandarin...*

"Honorable Senior!"

They all fell down to their knees and started hitting their foreheads on the floor, while not looking up which gave Matt a funny feeling. Though he did understand them, he wondered if English was normal around these parts or of there was some kind of translation thingy helping out.

"Uh... you don't need to do that, stand up"

All of them shoot up to their feet as if it would be rude not to follow his instructions and doing it slowly would be rude. He rubbed his neck a bit finding the whole thing uncomfortable but people in this kind of setting tended to be this way always revering the strong cultivators. One of the men that were previously running away moved forward over to the boy, he had a large build being even taller than Matt, he looked like the leader of the bunch.

"We of the Tatar Tribe greet honorable senior and thank him for giving aid."

He bowed some more while the other three moved behind him and helped the previously injured boy up Matt didn't know if the pills accounted for blood loss but the other three were tending to the kid so he would probably be okay.

"Do these uh... beasts often do that, they seemed to be... enraged?"

He was now interested a bit why the creatures were so violent and he also wanted to move the conversation along, he found the whole bowing thing to be quite awkward, to say the least.

"Yes, Senior! the magic beasts have been acting up for the past months, it started off small. Mostly it was a one or two of them that we came across but after a while more and more started getting violent, we believe that they are getting affected by something, maybe by another stronger beast or some treasure, but we can't go check as it's far too dangerous now, we have lost a lot of brothers to the beasts, we don't want to lose more."

He rubbed his chin while hearing the explanation while trying to think about his next move. The burly man in front of him seemed to be stressed out a bit as he stood at attention like he was talking to his superior. He looked even more stressed as after the explanation Matt kept staring at him without saying anything. Matt noticed that the man didn't look like any particular race of humans that he knew of, their skin had a darker tint to it but looked more to be a deep tan.

*I wonder if there are any other races besides humans in this world, there are magical beasts here... maybe there are some elves around?*

He wouldn't be against meeting some curvy elf girls to be honest, or maybe some cute catgirls? Though he preferred the more humanoid looking ones plus he liked them quite curvy... in his old world those girls were referred to as thicc, but thick in the right areas not overweight this and that were two different things. He remained with his poker face while his mind drifted to pervy thoughts. The men that were looking at this overpowered senior in front of them gulped down as they didn't know if this was a good thing that he came here to save them or if he would be worse than the wolves.

Chapter 11

"Uh... aren't you going to take those? Think you were out here to hunt."

Matt coughed into his hand as he finally noticed the uncomfortable atmosphere around him as the men were frozen while staring at him. He pointed with his finger at the dead creatures that laid down on the ground, he didn't really want them as he already gained the spirit points for killing them, he was tempted to see how many he had now but he wasn't sure if the others could see his system screen and either way if he started waving his finger around in a weird way they would probably think that he had a few screws loose.

"Oh but if you find any cores, could you hand those over?"

He stood to the side a bit moving away from the bloody scene as he inserted his spiritual energy into his flying sword that was still stuck to the ground. As it hovered upwards the blood and gore pieces fell down from the corpse of the crimson wolf that it parted in two. It was dripping and had pieces of flesh on it, the tip was kind of flat and looked more like it was better for bashing than skewering things on it. Matt grimaced at the gory sight. The flying sword didn't seem to have a cleaning function like his clothes and the light sword as just a skill and it just evaporated all the blood anyway so he would need to clean that otherwise it would probably start to stink in a bit.

"Um... do you  guys maybe have some water and a rag?"

He looked at the men that were moving over to the animal corpses who froze and looked at him as he was speaking. He had a strange way of talking in their opinion, but they thought that experts of that level were probably a bit quirky. He looked at them while asking and then to the sword that was hovering a bit of the ground and then placed down on it, then back to them. They spotted the blood on the tip and blade and then quickly spunk into action. The hunter in charge gave one of the other men a bottle of water and told him something and then that man started tearing off his sleeves he quickly run-up to the blade and started cleaning it with a ferocious dedication like his life depended on it which made Matt rub his neck as things got even more awkward.

"W-wait you don't need to do that..."

"Dignified Senior! it's an honor for us to clean your blade!"

The leader replied while cupping his fists and doing his bowing show of respect while Matt just looked at the thing a bit perplexed, but this was kind of how the world worked so he probably had to get used to it, or maybe he could change that world view of those natives if he wanted later on. His sword was nice and shiny within moments, the blood and guts were still warm so it was a lot easier to get them out than if they were dried. The male that cleaned it bowed to him and then moved to the other tribe members while they gathered up the spoils.

"Ah yes, thank's."

He moved the big sword closer to himself and just let it hover next to him, the hunters kept looking at the huge thing and the animal that it parted in one go and gulped. They were on their guard a bit, but kind of knew that they couldn't do anything about the situation and hoped that this immortal cultivator was of a gentler kind, but that went a bit against their popular belief as most of what the rumors said, was that when someone reached a high enough level of strength they became quite haughty. But this person wasn't giving off those vibes, so maybe the rumors were false.

"Ah, Also is there a hotel or something like that around here? It would be nice to take a bath.

The men looked at each other a bit surprised that this person was even here, most of high level cultivators wouldn't really interact with low-level ones if they didn't have too. He was even asking about bathing and staying for the night at their crummy little backwater tribe village. This wasn't really a problem for them as having someone of this caliber come to their land would just make the other tribes shake in envy, maybe he would even fancy one of the tribe girls or pick up a disciple? That would elevate the entire tribe to new levels. This was a big opportunity and they were quite lucky because they even had a nice hot spring in their village, that being mostly the only good thing about it.

"Yes Senior, we have hot springs in our village also you can use any hose you deem worthy to stay in it, it would be an honor!"

The hunting party leader replied while his eyes were sparkling for some reason, Matt wasn't sure why the person was looking at him like that but he shrugged and nodded back.

"Okay then, how about you pack those beasts up, I'll just follow behind you, also would be a waste to not take that deer beast too."

The men went back to work, quickly cleaning up and removing the beast cores that they handed over to Matt as he told them too. Though there was a little problem there were 14 dead wolves and 1 dead deer beast, they were a bit bigger then their Earthy counterparts and the men weren't really  prepared to drag so much game back home, they were mostly just prepared for maybe getting smaller animals and maybe one or two larger ones at most.

Matt wasn't really too keen on dragging the dead animals on his own and he wasn't interested in their meat whatsoever if he could just get food from his game like system instead. Though at that moment he almost facepalmed as he remembered that he had something he could transport the dead beasts with.

"Hey, just gather all of those together in one spot, I'll just take them."

Two of the men came back with the larger deer in tow and placed it together with the dead wolfs, and then looked as the man waved his hand around the corpses vanishing from the spot afterward. The beast corpses vanished into Matt's storage ring of course, the hunters opened up her eyes wide as they never saw spatial manipulation before. They just bowed some more while the man dressed in white moved back onto his large sword.

"Venerable Senior, we thank you for the aid! Would you honor us with your name."

Their eyes were sparkling even more than before, and Matt rubbed his neck as he felt a cold sweat taking over.

"Um... you can call me Zhang D-dong I guess..."

He regretted getting a silly last name like that, the man having a juvenile sense of humor but in this word that wasn't such a strange-sounding name. But he would probably have to get used to hearing dong this dong that around this place now.

"Well, I'll just follow you from up above then..."

He hovered back up while the hunters nodded to each other and started running towards their village, hoping that they could get this Senior to show some interest in their Tribe, they were a bit of an opportunistic lot but the times were tough so that was normal around these parts.

Chapter 12

Matt flew above them as he didn't really want to move along with the strange men, and sighted to himself as he looked down on them just running in one direction. He was stuck in this world, everything seemed so surreal, he didn't know if he was in some other world, or if he was comatose and stuck in a game world. The people looked real enough and he couldn't see any lag or the sort of thing, though the game-like interface plus the appraisal skill made him see numbers, names and cultivation bases of the people that he was looking at.

Cheng Yun, Human, Qi Condensation 2nd level

*Hm, that's quite low or is that high for that age?*

The youth looked between 15 and 16 years of age, he was a bit on the thinner side but it was lean muscle. He probably had a hard life, the clothes all of these men were wearing weren't too extravagant. It was all plain clothes, brown colors it was more functional but looked a bit shabby compared to his own white robe.

*Well, looks like with those guys speed it's going to take a bit longer till we get to that village of theirs, they said I could have any house they had, heh wonder if the town chief or is it mayor will give me his if I wanted to, he probably will judging by the strength of these hunters and how they look at me. Well I guess I'll look at my points, should have gained a few now...*

Name : | Zhang Dong
Affiliation : | Zhang Clan
Spirit Points :  | 8084
Cultivation Base Qi : | Core Formation [Early Stage 0%] (Lightning Core)
Cultivation Base Body : | Foundation Establishment [Middle Stage 0%] (Silver Body)
Techniques : | Lightning Qi cultivation art, Silver Body Arts, Thunderlight Sword, Thunder Movement Art...
Dao :  | Dao of Heavenly Lightning , Dao of Smithing and Crafting
Other :  | Senior Aura

*Hey, almost got all my spent points back, not bad should I stock up on them or go buy some stuff? Well, no need to rush guess I should check out my skills a bit more, I really could use some range attacks though, Maybe some spear throwing lightning attack? But first, what's this Dao thing...*

He tapped the Dao of Heavenly Lightning and looked at the explanation.

Dao of Heavenly Lightning | The Dao is the way that every cultivator strives for, you have chosen the way of the heavens, the Heavens are the beginning and lightning is the end. By cultivating this dao the user gains bonuses to all lightning-related skills as well as a 30% discount in the store.

*Oh that's good to know, makes it easier to specialize if I stick to lightning stuff. I recon the other Dao will give me a discount to crafting skills? Hm... I guess it would be best to get these Dao abilities and then get the responding skills, but I bet those cost a lot...

Being curious he decided to look up the Dao skills and he could even order them from the cheapest to the most costly one.

Dao of Gourmet | 30000000 Spirit Points | You dedicate your life to food, there is nothing your taste buds won't be able to taste if you go on the path of a foodie!
Dao of Tea | 32500000 Spirit Points | Making tea is an extremely meticulous and labor-intensive procedure, you dedicate your life to it gain bonuses from brewing tea!
Dao of Painting | 33000000 Spirit Points | Painting is an art in itself, create new worlds inside your paintings if you peruse this dao!

* 30 million? ... Tea?... Gourmet ... why would you even want that... are there battle skills related to tea making and eating food?*

His eyes bulged out as he looked at the prices of some of those Daos that looks a bit useless for him... unless he wanted to make a restaurant. Or some tea shop with nice paintings hanging on the walls that would give of a nice atmosphere. Guess there are or sorts of those, he was mostly interested in the battle ones but after looking at the prices he gave up on getting any at the moment, he would probably need to kill like a million of those trash mobs to even have enough spirit stones to get one, guess the prices were so high due to the skill discounts, he was glad that he had two already...

*Think I'll stick to the lightning-related skills... hope I won't find anything with lightning resistance here. Guess I'll just use the Jojo secret technique if that happens.*

He fiddled around his status screen some more and found out that he could spend his spirit points to further his cultivation, but he also knew of normal ways other people did it in this world that would work, he did have the core formation manual for it so he could cultivate it without the help, guess he could save that option if he was in need of a power-up. Should I get a lightning bolt spell then? Chucking lightning bolts at people was a cool thing, he could just hang out in the back and pelt them into nice fried corpses.

Lightning Javelin (Earth mid grade) | 11500(8050) | Throw a javelin made of elemental lightning at your enemy, power of the skill is dependent on cultivation base and other stats.
Lightning Bow (Earth high grade) | 15000(10500) | Form a bow of lightning and fire of arrows formed from your Qi, power of the skill is dependent on cultivation base and other stats.
Thunder Strike (Earth low grade) | 8000(5600) | Summon a lightning bolt from the sky to strike down your enemies, power of the skill is dependent on cultivation base and other stats.

*The Thunderstrike sounds kind of meh, how would I even aim that, the bow one sounds nice but I never used one before, plus I don't really have the points, the Javelin looks nice too... and with the discount I will just have enough points, should I get it or not, maybe I should have farmed more of those beasts back there...*

He furrowed his brows but finally selected the new skill, he really needed some range attacks and not like anyone around here would have any skill manuals he could learn, could he even read those if he wanted to? He felt a buzzing sensation in his head and felt a little migraine as the skill information rushed in. After it subsided he started closing his hand and Qi gathered around his fist, it looked similar to his other sword technique but the light was equal in length on both sides, the lightning javelin was about 2 meters in length. He looked at it, waving it around before chucking into a faraway tree looking at it collide with it and obligating it to pieces while scaring the poor hunter tribe members as they heard a loud boom in the distance.

"Oops sorry about that, nice penetrating power though."

He got back into his sword flying pose and looked as they sky started becoming red, the sun or the star that this world had was going down in the horizon, the sight was quite captivating as the many moons in the sky added to the whole spectacle.

"I'm really far away from home, aren't I? Hope mom and dad are doing okay..."

He got a bit sad as even though he was a loner he still had a family back home, he didn't talk to them much and lived alone but they were still his parents. He wondered if they would miss him much after they found out that he was gone or not, but he soon tossed his worries to the back of his head as he saw a village in the distance, they had finally arrived at the Tribe settlement.

Went back and changed the points he gained vs the bigger mob bunny as it felt a bit too low. Worked out some numbers and this seems a bit better now. Sorry for the inconsistencies.

Chapter 13

Matt looked down at the village that was bathed in the color red of the setting sun. The small town was covered with trees from one side, while from the other side you could see farmlands stretching out. It was built at the edge of the forest, probably for easier access to the beasts in there. There was a big wall around the settlement, it was at least 4 meters high and build from thick logs. It looked sturdy and hard to break down by old earth standards, but he wasn't sure about the standards of this world, he felt like it wouldn't last that well if he gave it a good punch or kick.

He was hovering quite a bit above the hunters that he was following at a slow pace, the others probably couldn't see him that well from the ground while he himself could use his heightened senses too zoom in and focus on the desired area and he could hear and see everything like he was there, all thanks to the previous data dump directly into his brain, it sure hurt a lot but was quite handy.

Matt saw as the people shouted someone to the people inside the village that was fenced of with the tree wall. They were standing in front of a  large gate now and after they made their presence known people on the other side reacted. They opened the gate and while the hunters looked back behind them, then looked upwards while scratching their heads a bit probably looking for Matt who was hovering above them and hiding within the clouds and just stalking them instead. They went inside and were greeted by some other people, one person moved over to the party of five and started shouting at them while a group that was behind him just looked on.

"Why are you coming back so late? Did you bring anything back with you? Even the other teams managed to nab some small critters."

What was surprising that the one that was shouting was a boy not much older-looking then the one that was in the hunting party, but all the burly men were hanging their heads down as if the youth-owned the place. He started berating the men, while they sweated bullets and sometimes look behind themselves and up into the air, the youth noticed this of course and a big vein could be seen bulging on his forehead.

"What are you idiots doing, you dare look away when I Yang Rong am speaking to you, you seem to have forgotten that I am the tribe leaders son and the next in line!"

The men were probably searching for Matt, not being sure where he was now, did he just get bored with them and leave? He was the one that was carrying all the animal meat, the hunters didn't know how to explain this. The youngest from the bunch decided to speak up though, showing a bit more guts than the elders or maybe it was a bit of bravado that young warriors tended to have.

"W-we were attacked by a big pack of crimson wolves, there were 14 of them as we were trying to hunt a serpent tailed deer, one of them even bit me in the leg"

Cheng Yun said quickly while Yang Rong showed some disdain towards him, mostly at the fact that he was interrupted in his speech. He pointed to his bloody pants that were ripped, though the lack of a wound and how he was walking just fine was suspicious.

"What nonsense are you spewing, if you meet so many wolves you would be in more sorry states, you all look fine, you think those torn pants are fooling anyone, you probably did that yourself, did you smear some squirrels blood on there"

"Well... we were suddenly rescued by a powerful cultivator, he went by the distinguished name Zhang Dong, he took care of the beasts in a flash, they were dead before we could even blink! He also gave me a pill that healed my leg in a flash!"

The brow of the village chief's son rose up high as he was listening to the younger male babble on, this sounded like total hogwash. Why would some powerful elder come in and save some insignificant cultivators, what would he gain from that? Also, why would he give precious pills and resources to a useless bum like Cheng Yun, he was having none of this, he would have to show what happens to people that can't pull their own weight and that lie so blatantly. He started it off by walking over to the younger male that was talking nonsense and gave him a rough slap to the face, his cultivation base was higher so Cheng Yun fell down to his knees while spitting out blood from the full force smack to the face.

While this was going on, Matt was hovering above the group not really sure what to do, having a bit of a stage fright of his own while meeting new people. He just looked on as everything was happening and the youth he previously saved was giving them the rundown. He also was interested in the walking talking trope that was Yang Rong, he was playing the stereotypical silky pants, son of the leader type of character quite well, he even had his own entourage behind him, they all had mocking expressions on their face as he was berating the hunters. His cultivation wasn't all that high, just on the Qi condensation 3rd level, so not much more from the kid he saved and he was even 1 year older.

"Man, didn't think I would find a silky-pants character right off the bat... I bet he gets all the best resources that this poor tribe has and comes running to his daddy whenever something wrong happens, well... guess I did help those people out so they are kind of my responsibility now... plus it looks like it's going to get violent."

As he presumed the slap to the face came soon afterward, the cronies of the tribal silky-pants closed in, they outnumbered the hunting party two to one, but they probably wouldn't really fight back worried that if the village chief found out he would punish them even more.

"Uhh... going to have a migraine..."

Matt moved his hands behind his back and stood up straight, he put on a poker face as he slowly descended down into the village after sighting a bit. He learned how to hide his aura and how to use it so that other people would feel its weight on them. His eyes began to gleam in blue color and lightning crackled from his body as he slowly flew down to where the fight was about to start. He made sure to give off a frighting aura that could be felt all around the settlement as people began looking in his direction with fear in their eyes.

*Guess it's time to face slap some little shits.*

Yang Rong and his group were feeling good about themselves, they all knew that they could do anything they wanted around here if they threw the Chief's name around, all the tribe members cowered in fear and all the girls came running. It was a nice life that most of the tribe people envied. This was just an everyday occurrence to them, just another time to take care of some trash. But then something strange happened, their body hair began standing up for some reason and they suddenly felt an oppressive force slamming into their bodies which made them go down to their knees. They all looked up, their eyes went wide and their jaws dropped as they saw an otherworldly looking cultivator descending from the heavens. His eyes were glowing and his body was covered in lightning that gave off thundering sounds. He was descending on a huge sword made from some strange crystals, they just realized that the hunting party was telling the truth and that they made a blunder, they might have offended this cultivator as he was looking quite stern. A unanimous gulping sound was heard as their bodies tensed up and they began sweating profusely.

Chapter 14

Cheng Yun rubbed his cheek as he spit blood on the ground, he felt a stinging pain where he got smacked but he couldn't resist the son of the chief, he didn't want to trouble his family as Rong was a known trouble maker. He would have to take this beating, the senior that supposed to be following them behind probably had better things to do than, it was odd that he saved them to begin with. He was ready to cover his head to ease the blows but then he suddenly felt it, he felt the weight of a powerful cultivation aura, the senior didn't leave and he was coming down.

Everyone looked up and the people from the tribe were shitting bricks right now as Zhang Dong was descending down from the sky while being lit up like a Christmas tree. He had an impeccable posture, he was straight as a pillar, his hands were behind his back and his hood was covering his head. The people could see his bright glowing eyes as he let his aura run free. Matt took his time, thinking to himself that he might be overdoing it a little bit as everyone around here looked like they were shitting bricks.

He came to a halt in front of the cowering Yang Rong and his band of bodyguards, he looked down at them the kid was too scared to raise his head upwards and look him in the eyes, as he knew well that this man in front of him was a lot stronger than his father that was the strongest fighter in the whole tribe. After a moment of silence the cultivator finally decided to speak.

"Sorry to break up your welcoming party, but I think these belong to those guys."

He said while moving his arm in the direction that youth was in, this motion made Yang Rong almost scream out in shock but before he could do that he could see multiple dead beast bodies drop from thin air, with a larger beast deer body landing at the end and covering him in gory guts. Matt had dropped the monster beasts that he was storing in his storage ring and placed them directly on the silkypants that was now squirming under a pile of dead animal carcasses, he would be smelling mighty fine indeed.

"You don't mind me dropping them right here, right?"

He pulled back his overbearing aura and stopped glowing like a neon light and looked back at the hunters that were behind him. They eyed him back with a dumbfounded look on their faces and didn't know if they should laugh and cry. The person under that bloody pile was the oldest son of the Chief who would probably be enraged if he saw that. On the other hand he probably wouldn't be able to do anything anyway as this monster of a cultivator had an unfathomable cultivation base, he had to at least be in foundation establishment but could he be in the rare core formation realm? They shook their heads side to side along with their hands while awkwardly smiling.

"N-no it's fine, it's fine Senior Dong!"

"Oh? Well glad to hear that."

He replied and then looked at the still shocked bully bunch.

"Think you should help your little friend out of there, he'll probably need a throughout bath afterwards though."

The tribe members that he was talking to, looked at themselves and moved up from their kneeling positions and just nodded sheepishly at the male in white words and began pulling the dead wolf bodies off of him, Rong climbed out of the pile covered in some gory bits, the wolfs weren't processed and Matt did cut them up into pieces with his sword skill, so there were various 'juices' flowing in that pile, better not to know where they came from.

Cheng Yun had to cover his mouth to stop laughing, turning away after seeing in what of a sorry state the silkypants was in. He was glad that the bully got some instant karma, even though it wasn't that much but it was quite a hit to his face. His eyes sparkled as he looked at the man in white that was hovering on his sword in front of them, hands behind his back and looking like a mountain, those were the sort of people young men alike looked up to.

Matt nodded his head a bit, thinking that was enough for now. He didn't feel like beating up the brat, even though he looked like he needed a good trashing. He thought that some public humiliation would bring the overconfident youth down a peg or at least he hoped so.

The hunters sighted in relief as all of the animal bodies were removed, they could go back to their original work now and deliver those to other tribesmen for processing. They cupped their fists at Matt and started helping the others with the bloody mess, everything got cleaned up in a jiffy. Afterwards you could hear more footsteps coming closer as more and more people arrived, they all looked in the prime of their life, everyone was built like a brick house while one bearded man stood out as he was the largest one of them, being half a head taller then the next largest man from the loot, this was the tribe Chief.

The burly bearded man looked around, he saw his son that was drenched in what looked like blood and some unidentified bodily fluids. He looked to the floating man that was looking in his direction. He couldn't measure the degree of this man's strength, plus he was hovering on a treasure with no problem he was clearly above the Qi condensation realm that everyone in this village was in, this man could not be messed with or everyone in here could lose his life.

"A pleasure to meet such a master, my name is Yang Shan I'm the Chief of this village, what brings you to our humble home."

He ignored his son's predicament as he probably was up to no good as always, he already had a headache as he always had to cover up his son's stupid escapees and he sure hoped that his stupid son didn't offend this type of cultivator or they all were done for.

"Ah yes, greetings. Sorry about that little friend over there, just wanted to drop of those beast bodies and I didn't see him there."

He shrugged while every person that was here before sweatdropped as they clearly saw him fly up to the Chief's kid and wave his hand in his direction before the pile of gore appeared. Not like they would tell that in this situation though.

"I met some of your people back in the forest, they said that you had a hot spring in here, was wondering if I could stay here for the night and use that hot spring of yours."

The tribe chief glanced over at the hunters that Matt helped out, they just rubbed their necks and gave the chief a little nod. He wasn't sure why the cultivator wanted to use that, as it was just a plain old hot water pool, there was no spiritual qi in it or anything. But cultivators were always an odd bunch.

"Ah yes! We will prepare the springs and bring you some refreshments as well, you can stay in our humble village as long as you want!"

He barked some orders at the near by people that quickly started running from where they came from, while the Chief moved over to Matt that was still hovering on his sword and tried to beckon him in the direction of the hot springs.

"Just follow me Senior, I'll guide you here, you can also ask me any questions that you may have."

Matt nodded while jumping off his sword, the sword then vanished into thin air after a wave of his hand which made the surrounding people go wide eyed once more and whisper among themselves. Spatial storage techniques were a rarity and most people didn't have storage rings like what he had, if they did the storage capacity wasn't much bigger than a cubic meter. Matt had an almost infinite amount of space in there.

"Okay chief, lead the way."

He replied and followed after the burly man, a lot of people followed after him while a lot of them were also in front as they shooed other tribe members away so that the cultivator behind them wouldn't need to wait, rule one of this kind of world was not to anger people stronger then them.

Chapter 15

Matt kept his hands behind his back while walking straight, he kind of didn't want to keep this position anymore buy he wanted to at least look like a Master even though he was a total noob on the inside. He looked around checking out the wooden buildings. The buildings were mostly made from wood, with straw like roofs though for all he knew they might have been made out of some fantasy spirit straw and spirit wood, for some reason a lot of things had that prefix in them.

He glanced left and right, people were curiously looking out of their homes wondering what all the fuss was about, but they quickly ducked back in after they noticed the tribe elders in the front with solemn faces that were kicking everyone to the side that they came across.Matt didn’t really notice the rude behavior as it was a bit in front and he had a wall of muscular men from each side to block his view.

*What’s with this beef cake parade… couldn’t you bring out some curvy amazon ladies to do that instead…*

He lamented to himself as they walked through the village, the pace wasn’t too fast or too slow. They moved closer to the middle of the small town and Matt could see the marketplace that even this place had, though there wasn’t much what the people were selling besides animal pelts, meat, fruits and vegetables.

The whole thing got more awkward with each passing moment, he was surrounded by people and looked like some big shot with way too many body guards around him. The moved along the normal villagers kept their distance but also sneaked in glances while holding on to their kids, it would have been really unfortunate if one of them bumped into the tribe members that were on edge and sweating bullets not knowing if this strange cultivator would go berserk on them for any little thing they would do.

Of course a little ball rolled in the direction of the meat shield around Matt and one little kid was chasing after it, while the parents had their hands full with other kids, quite normal from the size of families that were around here. The ball fell right in front of the marching of the burly uncles and the child run up to them to grab it, this making them stop in their tracks and glare at the kid in front of them.

"How dare you block the way of this honorable senior!"

One of the men barked while the child looked up in fear, starting to cry in response. It was a little girl about the age of 5, her mother quickly arrived at the scene and grasped the little thing trying to protect her from the rage of the burly overbearing men. Matt did a mental facepalm as he saw the whole thing.

*What's wrong with these people, it's just a little kid, she's just being a little oblivious to her surroundings like any kid that age. T-they aren't going to do anything to her and the mother... right?*

He looked on with concern while keeping his indifferent looking poker face, he was at lest good at showing no emotions. He looked at the pleading mother and the crying child while the angry uncles were looking awfully angry, he gave out a sight as he would probably have to diffuse this awkward situation. Just as one of the big men was about to go towards the mother and child duo, he stepped forward. He was a lot faster then the other man, he grasped his shoulder stopping as he was stretching his burly hand out towards the other two.

"That's enough, you're scaring the poor thing"

Everyone stopped in their tracks as the cultivator moved forward to stop the tribe member from moving the child out of the way, the man in question did a bow while moving to the side while Matt moved over to the child and mother. He still had his poker face on, he picked the ball up from the ground and presented it towards the little girl.

"It's okay you little rascal, the angry looking uncle won't do anything to you if I'm around."

He tried smiling a bit, but it looked more like a smirk, but thanks to being quite handsome and maybe thanks to the aura that he exuded the small child stopped crying as she took her ball back. The mother looked at the handsome man in front and blushed a bit, nodding her head at him as she backed away with her daughter in toe.

*Well, think that went well... I think.*

"Hey dude, no need to be so rough with kids, you lot have to chill out a bit."

The tribe members looked at Matt, not really knowing what he meant with 'dude' or 'chill out' , did he want them to go under a waterfall? Or into the icy mountains?

"S-so... where was that hot spring again?"

He coughed into his hand as he could tell that the men were giving him odd looks, soon they resumed the walking towards Matt's next destination. After they were away from the spot that they bumped into the child a lot of the villagers showed up, leaving their houses now when the coast was clear.

"Did you see that? He defended the child."

"Yeah, he was also really handsome!"

"Think he is looking for a wife?"

"Who would want your ugly ass as a wife."

The man that said that to the lady got socked in the face right afterwards and the people began laughing at him. The tribe members got lively after seeing the wandering cultivator in white, they got a good first impression as he seamed like a righteous person. They wondered what he wanted around here, they sure hoped that this was a sign that something good was about to happen to their village.

Matt was oblivious to the good impression that he made on the villagers as he just wanted to get to the damn bath and be left alone for the rest of the day, this was a bit too much human interaction for one day for him and he just wanted to wind down.He was lead to a wooden building after a while, after coming inside he noticed that this looked like a bath house that you would see in Asian countries, he could see the side for men and the side for females as also what looked like to be the innkeeper lady that bowing to him accordingly and greeting him while the tribe chief was giving her the stare down.

He was finally left alone in the changing room while the other men all left to wait outside, the surrounded the whole building making sure that no one else would come in. They also forced any people that were doing anything in the hot spring to leave. This made Matt sight a bit more as he still wasn't used to the special treatment that everyone was giving him. He started removing his clothes, but he didn't really need to place them in the changing room as he just placed them in his storage ring that he kept on his finger, he was sure that storage rings were water proof.

There was a big mirror in the changing room, which made him look at his new body and face. He didn't get a good look at it yet, he placed his fingers on his chin and moved his head left and right while examining his new found handsome man face. He had a mature charm to himself, he wasn't a bishonen or anything, his age made him look something between 25 and 30 , but he knew that people lived longer here and your aging started to slow down if your cultivation increased.

"Hm, not bad... but the most important thing..."

He looked to the left and then he looked to the right, shifting his gaze all over the closed of changing room before slowly moving his hands towards his undies. He had regular boxer briefs all in white like the rest of his clothes, he didn't know if these type of clothing was the norm as he thought people in this kind of setting wore a loincloth or something. But he had more important things to think about now as he had to know the size of his little brother down there and with one quick push he revealed him.

*Woah, well this is an improvement over the old model*

The villagers provided some warm water and soap to wash of before going into the hot spring, you didn't want dirty people going in there right of the bat without soaping up and rinsing themselves, so he did just that. After cleaning up he headed to the hot spring with a towel wrapped around his mid section, finally having some time to wind down as he lowered his body into the water and close his eyes while sighting. He gazed up at the sky, it was turning dark and he could see the stars and the unfamiliar moon above his head.

Chapter 16

The villagers left the cultivator at the hot spring inn of their village, the Chief ordered his people to block it off so that no one would bother the peculiar acting expert while he himself left to tend to his idiot of a son. He hoped that he didn't say anything foolish to the cultivator he wanted to be on friendly terms with anyone of this caliber, he couldn't really offer him anything as they were just a poor tribe in the middle of nowhere. Most people just dreamed of getting picked up by a prominent sect or clan and being a disciple of a renowned master. He wished he could help his son do that, but he seemed to have offended this Senior so that went out of the window, but the man didn't look angry probably not caring about a junior doing silly things, which was good.

After getting Yang Rong over here along with the team of hunters that knew the most about this enigmatic man, he started asking questions finding out about him saving the team, fending off a pack of wolves on his own and doing it without batting an eye. He then looked at his son that was holding his head down as he told that he started berating the hunters that the man helped, this ending with him having a pile of dead beasts dumped on his head, he still had a peculiar smell coming from his body even though he had already changed his clothes by this point.

It seemed to the Chief that the man wasn't hostile towards them as he saved his villagers and also didn't do much to his son besides embarrassing him slightly. Yang Shan was glad at the later part, as this experience might get his useless son to think before acting first. There were far more powerful people out there, he couldn't have his son just parading around and throwing his weight around if he didn't really have anything to back that up besides his old man. He nodded and gave a good fatherly smack to the head with a closed fist, reprimanding him for being an idiot. Yang Rong went down to his knees and rubbed his poor noggin, now he had a bump in the middle of it.

"B-but father..."

He sent the boy home, he couldn't have his antics offending Zhang Dong so he wanted his son to keep it low, he'd invite the man to his home later for dinner, or maybe breakfast if he didn't want to eat anything at the moment. He told the men around the hot springs to inform him when the cultivator was about to leave and then walked away to prepare the feast.

About half an hour passed as Matt was soaking in the springs just relaxing with his eyes closed, his body wasn't tired though he did feel stressed. It hasn't been long since he was wished away into this world, did some bored god do this to him, as he passed out in a coma in a hospital and this was just a dream? He had no way of knowing, he could clearly feel pain, everything looked like it was real and the people were acting normally, well normally for cultivator type of people with the bowing and respecting things.

He opened up his eyes and realized something, something really ,really bad. This was a hard truth of this world... there was no internet around... he was getting bored ... He couldn't play any games, he couldn't watch any new tv shows, read any comics or manga or read any fantasy novels like he liked to do back at home. He didn't know how the entertainment industry looked around in this world, but what he could tell cultivators spent most of their time hold up in some abodes meditating and contemplating their dao. Dread filled his mind as the thought of meditating in one spot for years at a time just gathering spirit energy? How did that even work... he brought up his screen and clicked at his cultivation method.

Lightning Qi cultivation art : | Immortal grade cultivation art, can be cultivated up to the great circle of the core formation realm. The cultivator gathers the surrounding Qi into his body transforming it into lightning Qi, works best if cultivated at high altitudes, closer to the heavens or in a storm where the lightning elements are abundant.

*Well that doesn't explain much, let me see, also it has a cap on it...*

He got out of the spring and wrapped the towel around his waist to cover his little brother. There was a large boulder in the middle of the spring onto which he got up and sat down in a meditation pose. He gathered his thoughts on the cultivation technique as he had the information about it in his brain. Matt sat in a lotus position with his legs crossed in an uncomfortable-looking way. He brought his hands together with his right palm going under his left one while his right thumb went above his left thumb as they connected. He closed his eyes and tried to feel the spiritual Qi around his surroundings.

Matt remained in the cultivation position for a bit and started absorbing the Qi around him. The spiritual force felt like little droplets around him, hovering in the air that he needed to pull in and towards his lower dantian that was in his abdomen. The droplets of Qi were guided to his hands and then towards his belly as he started absorbing the water-like substance, slowly gathering more and more. The spiritual power was thin around these parts so it was taking him a while to do this, but he was getting the hang of it. After the droplets turned into liquid and entered his body, it started getting rowdy in there. He needed to transform the spiritual energy into lightning Qi now, this was one of the hardest types that a cultivator could cultivate as it was quite unstable. But with the knowledge that he already had and the formed lightning core he managed it do that without fumbling all too much. He didn't even notice that a good couple of hours had passed by now and that it was midnight.

The tribe people noticed it though as they could feel a disturbance in the Qi force. They could feel the spiritual force from the surroundings getting sucked in one general direction which was, of course, the hot spring that Matt was sitting in almost naked. He was absorbing most of the spirit essence from the air which didn't leave much for the others, so everyone that was trying to cultivate peeked out in protest wondering who had the audacity to suck up their resources. They quickly found out that it was the wondering man dressed in white that was doing it. About this time they also noticed that the sky was void of stars as it was got really cloudy. Thunder could be heard up in the sky as it rumbled and in a shocking turn of events, lightning bolts started crashing down into the hot spring that the cultivator was in, this making everyone go wide-eyed at the spectacle.

Matt was really in the zone right now, just taking in the Spiritual force and turning it into his own special kind of Qi. The sudden jolt of electricity that hit him just propelled his cultivation further and further. The little storm wasn't much as it didn't generate that much force, this as the reason why it was advised to cultivate in stormy areas at a high altitude, the practitioner could then gather many more lightning bolts into his body and further his cultivation at a higher pace. You could also use special herbs, magical treasures or pills that had a similar effect as well.

He opened up his eyes that were now glowing and looked upwards as the last thunderous strike was delivered onto his body before the stormy clouds subsided. Matt looked around the hot spring that was now sparkling with lightning energy that sipped into the water and supercharged it. Due to his forceful cultivation method, he managed to turn this spring into one that gathered lightning qi energy now, it was a gathering spot of the lowest of low grades, but for the people in this Tribe, it would be quite the treasured spot now. After finishing up he brought up his screen to check if his cultivation had advanced in any way and he was pleasantly surprised.

Cultivation Base Qi : | Core Formation [Early Stage 5%] (Lightning Core)

*Heyyyy, that's pretty goood.*

*Now I only need to figure out the body cultivation thing*

Silver Body : | Silver Body is the next advanced form of the Copper Body refining technique, instead of hard psychical training that is mostly attributed to body refining techniques, the cultivator absorbs weapons/treasures that are metallic in nature to refine his body into a treasure in it's own. The higher grade the treasure is the stronger the body gets. Common grade weapons and treasures have no effect on this technique. The technique can be trained up to the Nascent Soul great circle realm.

*Ah, so it's one of those... glad that I have a discount to crafting skills... guess I'll have to get some crafting materials and some crafting skills next.*

Chapter 17

*Wait, how long was I sitting on this rock...*

Matt noticed that it was really dark outside, some lanterns lit up the place around but he knew that it was quite late now.

*Those guys are probably still waiting for me outside...*

He moved off the boulder and found himself a towel to dry his body off. He put his clothes back on finding the self cleaning function of them quite handy, as he wouldn't be stinking up the place like some of the other dudes that he saw in this village. The hygiene around here was just so so, but at least they did have this hot spring to wash of. He put on his boot and fixed his wrist protectors as he got ready, he stood up and looked behind him at the spring what felt a bit different than before he sure hoped that the people still could use it with the mild lightning Qi now floating around in there.

He noticed that the moment that he walked out to get dressed someone outside the changing room walked away, guess they were keeping tabs on him or something.Matt went out feeling refreshed and even a bit stronger thanks to his slight cultivation progress, he also didn't feel all that hungry even though he didn't eat much the whole day, besides the junk food he got from his store. This was also attributed to his high cultivation levels as people of that level could sustain their bodies on spiritual energy for a very long time without having to eat or drink. The same thing applied to holding their breath and living longer, a core formation expert had a 400-500 year life expectancy and considering that his body was about 30 years of age, he had a long way ahead of him.

*Maybe they'll invent the internet till my life runs out if it's that long -sight-*

Matt was greeted by the burly men outside that were still standing there, they gave him a bow of respect like they always did. He moved out while nodding his head at them and going back to his stoic poker face look. The Chief of the village soon came up running with some other people in tow once more.

"Hope you enjoyed your stay at the hot-springs, but those lightning strikes..."

"Ah, sorry I just had an epiphany and cultivated for a while, but don't worry the springs are still intact.Though they are a bit different now than before, shouldn't be much of a problem though." *Well, don't really know though*

He interrupted the Chief's questioning as it was getting late and while not needing that much sleep he wanted to turn in for the night.

"Do you think I could stay here for the night, I can also pay you if you want."

The town leader perked up at the mention of a reward, but he couldn't just ask a monstrous cultivator for any cultivation resources all willy nilly. So he decided to decline the offer, at least for now...

"No need Senior Dong, we have prepared accommodations for you at our guest house, I'm sure it will be to your satisfaction. It's right next to my own home, so if you have anything you need you just need to ask. I'm hoping that you'll join me for a morning meal tomorrow after you rest."

Yang Shan asked while declining the payment, though Matt just wanted to give him some gold coins, thought that those were probably enough.

"Ah sure, I'll see you in the morning then, hope it's not a bother."

They both nodded at each other and Matt was lead away by some other warriors and women that were prepared to serve him for the night, yes the girls were supposed to serve the cultivator in any way possible, plus they agreed out of their own free will as this looked like a free meal ticket out of this dump. But they also were there to clean and cook if he decided to stay for longer or needed any servants.

He was led to a nice log cabin looking building that you would see at lake resorts, there was a fireplace inside and it was quite spacious. He was soon left in there with three females, there were all cute looking ladies and also quite young. Two of them looked like they were between the ages of 16 and 18 while the third one looked to be in her twenties. The girls gave him a bow and just stood there with sparkles in their eyes as they looked at Matt who was removing the hooded rope part of his clothes, he didn't need it now and he placed it in his storage ring.

Our hero found himself in the company of three pretty ladies, now you might think that being the manly man that he was he would just woo all of them at once, while using his sensual skills. But Matt just found himself frozen in place, not really being able to muster the courage to speak to the female trio that kept looking at his face. He had almost no experience what to speak of, he had one or two encounters here and there but they didn't count for much. He found himself staring at the girls with his passive resting bitch face so after a while the women started getting uncomfortable as they thought that he wasn't pleased with them being around here.

"Uh... I'll be in my room, g-goodnight..."

He didn't want to be in this awkward situation anymore so he decided to head over to the bedroom alone, the females felt a bit dejected but they bowed at his words and left the building, reporting to the people outside that the cultivator didn't seem interested in them that much and gave them an unimpressed look. The three girls were one of the best looking ones from the entire village. Guess after a while you lose interest in those sorts of things? The girls lamented their fate as the cultivator was sure their type of man, strong and good looking and probably loaded with cash, the clothes that he was wearing were a sign of how well off he was as they didn't compare to anything they had in this village.

The girls pouted at each other and just went away for now while Matt himself gave out a sigh and flopped onto the bed, the mattress was a bit hard but he could deal with it. He lamented to himself at the blunder with the girls but not really that much, thinking that after he got acclimated in this world and got the hang of it, then he could start pursuing the whamen.

He glanced at the map of his and could see dots surrounding his abode, probably being the tribe villages that were guarding or just spying on him for the night. He mentally shrugged at the whole thing and thought that he had a couple of options now. He could either stay here, for the time being, there were a lot of beasts around here that weren't a problem for him. He could earn spirit points by slaying those quite easy. Though the odd prefix before their names was strange, something must be making them go berserk and if he stayed he would probably have to face that as well. The second option would be to leave and head over to Spirit Spring City where his so called Clan was in, he could get acclimated in there as well, but would he have a place to grind like here? Were there more powerful cultivators in the city that he wouldn't be able to defend himself against? Or go with option three and just ignore that City and just explore some more.

*Think I'll stay here a bit longer, the people seem friendly enough. This thing isn't giving me any quests, so I guess this is more of an open setting, the rage monsters seem like a quest to clear though...Well, guess it's time to sleep.*

He put his thoughts to the back of his mind and turned to his side as he closed his eyes, the first day had finally finished, but on the next time new adventures and opportunities awaited.

Chapter 18

Morning came and the sun was up once more, the small town was buzzing with noise as everyone was gossiping about the person that was resting in the cottage next to the Chief's home. The man in question didn't sleep all that well as he tossed and turned in the unfamiliar bed most of the time, getting in like 3 to 4 hours of sleep. He wasn't that tired thanks to his new constitution though, but he swore to himself to get a better bed in the future, he even pulled up his cash shop and could see some furniture that had plus stats to resting and relaxation. But he had less than 100 points at the moment so first came the grinding.

He washed his face and brushed his teeth, he got a nice deal in the form of 1 SP for a toothbrush and toothpaste set at least the non magical things were cheap in the store. But there was nothing in the form of electronics in the item store, guess they limited it to non technological items from his old world, guess they didn't want him selling smartphones around here. People in this world used some strange jade slips that had limited range and the world was huge so you couldn't just contact everyone you wanted.

*I guess food and furniture will have to do. Well I can turn spirit stones to SP, so I should see if I can sell stuff at one of those action houses, if I grind here enough I'll probably have a lot of beast cores to spare, think those should sell well.*

Matt whistled to himself as he exited his bedroom and as he opened the door he twitched a bit as one of the serving ladies from the previous night was standing right there. She gave him a little bow and informed Matt about breakfast that he was invited to by the Chief.

"Ah yes, the big guy did say something about eating in the morning yesterday, I guess you'll guide me there, little miss?"

The girl smiled at him and nodded moving in front of him as they left the house, there were the guards around as yesterday but this time around they didn't follow after him but remained in place. They were right at the Chief's place, so there was no use in doing that as there were more burly uncles at his house anyway.

The Chief's house was also made from logs and wood, it was a lot more spacious then the cabin he was sleeping in. He could see that there were a lot of people living in there as they were buzzing around and everyone was doing something. The Chief had one wife, but he had many children the oldest one being the kid that was berating his fellow tribesmen yesterday. It wasn't odd to have many wives if the male was of higher status and could support them. His whole family was ready and waiting at a long table filled with many various dishes that Matt wasn't all too familiar with, but there was a whole lot of meat there.

"Good morning Senior Dong, come sit with."

He was lead to a spot next to the village leader, he nodded at the people around the table which varied from old elderly people to kids in about their teens, guess they spared him of having children there. He was feeling a bit guilty as the people were making a really big deal of him being here and he didn't really do much to deserve it besides being the person with the biggest cultivation in the room. The man of the house started prattling on while Matt examined the food on the table, there was something to drink, the cups were dark so he didn't know if it was water or something else. Most of the dishes were meat based, there was some brown bread in there too though but no butter.

"And this is second uncle Li and his wife Lei"

He nodded at the people not really being able to remember the names as they all sounded a bit similar to him. But he decided to suck it up and just nodded while not showing much emotion on his face, but it twitched here and there as he could swear he heard the same names getting repeated several times.

"Does the honorable Senior Dong want to say something before we eat?"

*Could you stop calling me honorable, you don't even know me.*

He grimaced a bit while everyone in the room looked at him, their facial expressions ranged from fearful, curious all up to stern as they waited for him to speak. Matt just coughed into his hand and tried replying in a way that wouldn't make him look stupid.

"Ah, the Tartat Tribe was it, you have my thanks for the lodging and the food, um don't worry I'll be sure to repay you, later on, Oh also, could I have a word with you, Chief Shan, after we have eaten?"

The Chief showed a glint in his eye and nodded while laughing, he also ignored that the man got the tribe name wrong. A big smile on his face as he heard that the cultivator would repay them later on and that he wanted to speak with him in private.

"Sure sure, Senior just eat as much as you want and we will speak afterward."

He mostly wanted to discuss the grinding session that he wanted to do, there were a lot of beasts in that huge forest that was the size of a country on its own. There were a lot of frenzied monsters in there but they weren't strong or anything. He wanted to strike a deal with the Tribe members, he would provide them with the animal corpses and they would process them for him. The tribe would get all the meat from the beasts as they wanted and the pelts but he would anything that could be used for crafting, like horns, claws, scales and also the beast cores that were also used for that, but could also be used for other things like pills and potions and even for some cultivation techniques.

He took some bread and gave it a bite, it was the brown kind of bread with seeds in them so it had a lot of nutrients, it wasn't all that fluffy but it had a good taste to it. He was worried about the meat on the table as after killing the wolves yesterday he was afraid that they would cook and serve those to him, he didn't really want to eat dog or wolf meat. He just asked and was told that it was made from the deer monster instead as herbivore meat was a lot better to consume than carnivore meat. So he took the plunge and started eating the meat, it tasted a bit bland without seasoning but was fine to eat so he chomped and nommed to his heart content and after some time they were done with eating.

Well at least he was done, but everyone else was kind of forced to stop after he was done with his share. They later stood up and he went away with Yang Shan to a separate room to talk. Matt told him about the deal and he was ready to even let them have some of the crafting materials if they wanted them, he was mostly aiming for the cores and the spirit points to further his power level. But the Chief was more than happy to agree to his terms as they were having a bit of a food crisis now, with all the beasts killing each other at an increased pace and the hunters having a hard time procuring meat without casualties. He also had another agenda as he thought that maybe if the cultivator was going to go to the forest to hunt beasts, he might get to the bottom of why the beasts are going mad. He didn't think that the man was there just for the beast cores though, but he didn't want to pry further.

"Great, well then I'll be heading out not sure when I'll be back, but you don't need to have people follow me all around this place next time when I return... okay?"

He asked while scratching the back of his neck, the Yang Shan just nodded and opened the door for him while letting Matt out of the room, seeing him off as the large crystal sword was revealed and Zhang Dong jump onto it to fly away towards the forest area while other people just watched him with wonder and envy in their eyes.

Chapter 19

He flew into the air, his sword glistering in the sun as he zoomed around the area already feeling better after he left that village and was now alone. He always disliked crowded places and he didn't have his trusty headphones to block out the noise around him anymore. So he was finally out in the open and decided to go in a different direction than he came from, wondering if the same problem was happening in other parts of the forest. He could see where he was on the map, he marked a waypoint on his spirit maps and flew off at a high speed. He didn't worry about losing his way as the map was pretty accurate, he did find this settlement and all.

Didn't take him long to spot a couple of angry looking beasties, they were attacking some other creature that was running away. It had an elongated frame split into segments, with one pair of legs per that body segment. It looked like it was made from a hard shell and the head had large antennae sticking out, a pair of elongated mandibles along with more claw like appendages that made it look quite ferocious. Size wise it was about 4 to 5 meters long. It was more or less a giant version of a centipede, Matt grimaced as he saw those monsters moving about and just wanted to ignore them as they were quite gruesome looking.

But he had to toughen up, plus he had a way to take them out without moving in too close. He gathered up his spirit energy into his hand to form a long spear and took aim at the creepy crawlies that were chasing something that looked like a big boar? He focused on his target and chucked the javelin at it, hitting one of the monsters closer to its hind area than in the head. This didn't kill the big centipede, but it did slow it down. It stopped in its tracks to see what attacked gnashing its mandibles at the surroundings in a menacing way. But this only gave Matt the chance to charge up one more bolt of lightning and as he got closer he chucked it right at its head that promptly exploded into gory bits.

Giant Centipede Slain ( Qi Condensation 4th stage ) Earned 35 Spirit Points.

The second monster didn't stop in its chase after the large boar and continued on without helping its kin. He decided to forget about the body of this horror as he chased after the other one, missing with his aim here and there before finally landing a killing hit, the trees were getting in the way and he wasn't really used to throwing lightning bolts at things that moved, but this whole thing sure made him feel like Zeus.

The other beast got away but he didn't chase after it, he flew down to check if the monster was dead. The guts and bodily fluids were all over the place, Matt covered his nose as the big bug had quite the smell to it.

*Uh... will those villagers even want to eat this thing...*

He shrugged for now and placed the dead body in his storage ring and then backtracked to the spot that he killed the other one, only to find more giant bugs of the same kind eating the corpse that he had slain. This was a good thing and a bad thing in a way, good that he had more monsters that he could practice his skills on, bad that the other beasts body was wasted now. Well, he rained down lightning laced javelins on the monsters, getting better and better at aiming them as practice did indeed make perfect and soon a pile of remains was filling the ground. He was glad that he had his ring on him, it would really be annoying if he had to fly with those stinky corpses around, he waved his hand and they vanished into thin air.

*Well this is going well... should I see where these monsters come from and clear out the nest, or just check out the area some more.*

These monsters weren't enraged or anything so they were just regular insect beasties, but they gave similar amount of points that he could farm. He left one corps outside to examine it, he could tell that the armor was kind of sturdy as knocking made robust sounds, maybe the people in the village could make things from this?

He got the smart idea of leaving one of the creature bodies out in the open, in the hopes of attracting it's kind. He thought that there should be a pace where they were coming from as the other ones appeared quite fast after he slew the first one. He hovered above them while checking his points, he had some now but still far from having enough to buy better skills or gear. He heard the sounds of insectoid feet on rummaging on the ground as another group of giant centipede monsters emerged. He smirked and cleared them out as well, soon being able to precisely aim his lightning spear at the heads which brought the beasts down with one hit.

"I'm sure am a bit overpowered, aren't I? Or at least haven't found anything that could hurt me yet... better not get cocky. Think those monsters came from that way."

He flew in the direction the large insects came from and after spotting more of them, clearing them out, gathering all the remains he wooshed further and further and finally came up to a hill. The hill had many holes in the side of it and he could see the insect monsters crawling out of them. Sometimes they moved some food inside, sometimes they bit each other but mostly they were just being creepy.

"Hm... wished I had some grand skills so I could take this hill out ... It looks like there are hundreds of them there..."

Matt checked his map and the amount of red dots on it was huge, he couldn't tell how many of those creatures were stuck in that hill but it was a lot. He could more or less distinguish the power level of these monsters by now, there weren't any strong ones around them as all of them were at the Qi Condensation stage, there was one a bit stronger than the other ones but it wouldn't be a problem.

"Question is... do I have enough spirit qi to fling so many javelins at them... guess this will be a good training exercise."

He wasn't tired from using his throwing skill that much at the moment, but he didn't use it that much and he had downtimes to gather up more spirit qi from the surroundings, which his lightning core was kind of doing on its own passively.

"I'm cheating a bit as they have no way of getting up here to where I am... oh well... "

Matt started throwing javelin after javelin at the creepy crawling giant centipede monsters, doing it faster and faster as they emerged from the hillside to see what was going on. They knew that they were in danger but they couldn't see with their limited senses, not really having good eyes and mostly using their huge antennas and changes in the surroundings to get a read on their opponents. They weren't really ready for a shameless cultivator that just bombarded them from a safe distance with bolts of lightning. Matt started getting really good at this, managing to fire off multiple javelins at once, he learned that he could produce multiple spears of lightning in his hand and throw them with an added devastating effect, or he could charge up longer and fling a huge one that could take out multiple centipedes if they piled up in one spot.

After using this skill to take out most of the insect beasts, he started feeling tired, he felt weird as his body as getting deprived of spiritual energy after prolonged usage.

"I guess that I do have a cap to this power, but luckily there aren't many left and I think the leader is coming out."

The hill burst open and a centipede that was about twice the size of the other ones emerged, but it also wasn't much for him to handle as it also just took one supercharged javelin to the face before crumbling down, dead on the ground.

Giant Centipede Slain ( Qi Condensation 12th stage ) Earned 100 Spirit Points.

"Oh, guess it was close to advancing, maybe I'd have gotten more points if I had waited a bit?"

He cleared out the entire nest within a couple of hours, his throwing abilities were at a higher level now plus he finally had some SP to spend.

"Let's see...think I killed close to 200 of those bugs."

Name : | Zhang Dong
Affiliation : | Zhang Clan
Spirit Points : | 5584
Cultivation Base Qi : | Core Formation [Early Stage 5%] (Lightning Core)
Cultivation Base Body : | Foundation Establishment [Middle Stage 0%] (Silver Body)
Techniques : | Lightning Qi cultivation art, Silver Body Arts, Thunderlight Sword, Thunder Movement Art...
Dao : | Dao of Heavenly Lightning, Dao of Smithing and Crafting
Other : | Senior Aura

Chapter 20

He was quite satisfied with himself, he was gaining points and learning to better use his skills in actual battle situations. If he could he would buy himself some sort of high tech training chamber to train instead of in a safe environment.

He stretched a bit and looked around his surroundings, it looked gruesome. There were dead bugs everywhere and they gave off a pungent smell. The centipedes were monsters with a poison attribute to them. The whole place was covered with various liquids besides blood and they ranged from yellow to purple.

Matt grimaced as he started to place the corpses in his storage ring. He sure hoped that those tribespeople would find a use for these giant bug remains. He was a bit disturbed while walking around the remains at least he didn't need to directly touch the remains just get close enough so he used his sword to hover slightly above ground level. This took him some time as he also started checking out the surroundings wondering if these types of bugs hoarded any items. He thought that maybe he could get some added treasure, but he didn't find anything and the openings in the hill were kind of narrow. Matt didn't want to crawl into the dark an unknown even though the minimap didn't show anything living inside, what if there was something blocking the signal and some creepy thing pounces on his face?

*Okay, I have some points now. But that skill sure does use a lot of energy if I have to spam it for an hour.*

His core was working in overdrive as it naturally sucked in spiritual energy from the surroundings to replenish his used up tank. He felt like he lost about half his Qi while going berserk with the javelin skill. He focused to bring out his lightning sword now with one hand, while summoning the spear with the other hand. He held both of them in the same way and concentrated.

*Hm... even though these two skills look similar and have a similar length to it, the javelin drains a bit more... maybe because it has to have enough punch to it, so when I throw it, it doesn't dissipate. The sword is always close to my body so I can sustain it better.*

He started to learn about managing his Qi reserves while engaging in battle. But he also wanted to test out some close-range combat and incorporate his other skills. He had the basic fighting knowledge to use punches and kicks, plus he had that flashy movement art that made him very hard to hit, but it was a bit hard to hit anything while moving as well. He sure could use a sparring partner or something for this, was kind of hard to learn much on your own, guess he would need to find himself, someone, to train with...

However, he did not see any old Asian grandpas that would teach him the way of the Dao while he cleaned their fence anywhere within the area he was in. For the time being the monsters around this area would be used to test out his plethora of skills which he didn't have an awful lot of. For the remainder of the day, he flew around the area taking it easy. He helped the members of the saucy tribe here and there if he spotted anyone in danger but he didn't find any more infested breeding grounds of monsters like the poison insects.

Matt managed to find a nice elevated spot as well, it was a larger hill, maybe it could be considered a small mountain but he didn't really know. He sat down in the lotus position as he did the previous day and started cultivating. The clouds soon gathered around him as he sucked in the spiritual Qi from around the area, the beasts and animals fleeing the spot that he was in as they noticed someone of a higher cultivation level. The beasts were somewhat intelligent and unless they had that strange berserk status they would not bring themselves in harm's way.

He spent the remainder of the day there, managing to go from 5% to 12% in his cultivation. Matt was a bit surprised that he was advancing so fast but that was probably because this was just the early stage, plus his body cultivation didn't budge at all as he needed to get some weapons to absorb.

He saw the sun starting to go down on the horizon, so it was time to return. He probably could handle himself during the night, but due to his old habits, he decided to head to his temporary home in the village. People could see him wooshing about in the sky, clasping their hands in respect as they saw him. Matt headed to the Chief's house, for now, he wanted to get rid of the giant centipede monster corpses as soon as he could, it didn't feel right to carry those things around with him.

"Greetings Senior Dong."

Said Yang Shan as he saw the cultivator in white who was standing outside his abode, he tried to beckon him over to his home for a chat and maybe some tea but Matt just waved him over instead. The Chief walked over and looked at the man who was scratching the back of his neck and thinking about something.

"So, uh... remember the deal from yesterday? I did hunt some monsters, so uh could you guys take care of the bodies?"

Yang Shan smiled in response as the deal didn't sound bad at all, they didn't really need to do much on their own, just process the goods and earn a bit of spare change while getting food and resources.

"Oh yes! Sure, sure just let us handle it."

The Chief looked ecstatic as this would aid his tribe a lot.

"So... where can I unload the bu... the beasts... Probably going to need a large area..."

He asked while scratching the back of his neck even more.

"Oh, you don't need to trouble yourself, Senior, just drop the beasts off anywhere you want, our Tribesmen will begin processing them immediately!"

"Are you sure? ... right here in front of your house? "

Matt looked at the burly man that just nodding with a smile on his face and shrugged, looking at his ring as he took a few steps back. He took out his flying sword first which made the tribe chief a bit puzzled. He then flew up so that he could begin the dumping procedure. Yang Shan then looked in bewilderment as a mountain of dead giant centipede monsters quickly piled up in front of his home, blocking the main gate fully from one side. There were a couple of other monsters in there but the dead bug parts were the things you mostly saw.

"Well then... I'm going to turn in for the night... you guys have fun."

Matt quickly zoomed out of there on his sword while the Tribe Chief's face started twitching. From all the monsters this Senior could hunt he had to go for the dreaded Giant centipedes, this kind of monster wasn't edible for humans at they were poisonous and their bodies were hard to process. They could kind of fashion crude armors and weapons from the insect shell and their sharp mandibles, the cores were the most lucrative part as they could be sold. He barked some orders at his retainers that moved out to gather more people, this mountain of dead bugs would be a chore to clean out as the poison from the bodies was dripping down into the soil already.

"I'll have to designate a special building for this... that senior is an odd one... "

While the other people were slaving... happily working through the night to clean up the graciously gifted animal remains, Matt brought up his status screen of his gains. He managed to rack up more points after the bug wars.

Name : | Zhang Dong
Affiliation : | Zhang Clan
Spirit Points : | 6084
Cultivation Base Qi : | Core Formation [Early Stage 12%] (Lightning Core)
Cultivation Base Body : | Foundation Establishment [Middle Stage 0%] (Silver Body)
Techniques : | Lightning Qi cultivation art, Silver Body Arts, Thunderlight Sword, Thunder Movement Art...
Dao : | Dao of Heavenly Lightning, Dao of Smithing and Crafting
Other : | Senior Aura

"Not bad for the first day ... feel a bit sorry for those guys, but there were a couple of edible looking beasts in that pile... sure hope dropping them in that bug pile wasn't a bad idea..."

It, of course, was a bad idea as the poison from the centipedes soaked into the other creatures remains but it could be eaten as the tribe people did have some cleansing and cleaning measures. They, of course, coursed him out at night as they found out that there would be even more work for them due to this. Matt just flopped onto his bed and rested while thinking about the things that he should do tomorrow.

Chapter 21

The next day, Matt brought up his cash shop and checked out some of the crafting manuals, there was a lot of stuff in there it ranged from single weapon crafting recipes to full collections of everything in a bundle, that would be cheaper than buying everything one by one. There were many weapons and armor categories, he did have that golden hammer that he got so he probably should get some weapon crafting skills first, but wouldn't he need something to sharpen the blade, was that hammer enough?

Novice Crafting Bundle : | 8000 (5600) | Lets the user craft basic gear, the bundle includes recipes for common grade items, the grade of the items depends on the crafters skill, Novice starter crafting abode included in the bundle.

*What's a crafting abode?*

He searched for the term in the store and raised his eyebrow at what he got.

Novice crafting abode | 4000(2800) | Creates a manufacturing abode for the user, can not be opened if enemies are around. It can only be used only for crafting common grade equipment.
Apprentice crafting abode (Can only be purchased if Novice abode is present. ) | 40000(28000) | Creates a manufacturing abode for the user, can not be opened if enemies are around. It can only be used only for crafting Mortal grade equipment.
Adept crafting abode(Can only be purchased if Apprentice abode is present. ) | 400000(280000) | Creates a manufacturing abode for the user, can not be opened if enemies are around. It can only be used only for crafting earth grade equipment.

*Well this doesn't explain much, the abode can be opened? Does it put me in some kind of pocket dimension so I can craft in there? ... well, that would be neat! Or does it spit out some kind of house out in the open instead?*

Matt wasn't sure about the opening part of the explanation, he sure wanted to get that noobie bundle though even though he could only make the lowest of low items. Being curious he decided to buy it not like he had to use it right away. He looked as his points dwindled once more, spending points on skills was one of the more exciting things that a gamer could do, but it also was a chore to choose if you had limited points for it.

He waited for the crafting knowledge to invade his brain and give him a migraine once more, he closed his eyes and tried to focus on good things but the pain didn't come and he didn't feel any knowledge of smithing.

*Did I get scammed?*

He poked on his status screen and he soon spotted a new icon there, it looked like tongs and a hammer, crossed with each other. He hovered his finger over the new prompt being uncertain if he should click it or not. He looked outside the window, the night was dark and he couldn't see much outside. The place didn't have any electricity so there were no street lights around, people in this world used either fire or special magical treasures that produced light. But this village had none of that, besides simple candles and fireplaces.

Matt gulped and went for it clicking the icon and was greeted by a clung of a hammer on an anvil before a bright light filled the whole place. People could see a bright flash in his window that vanished as soon as it appeared. He felt a buzzing sound in his ears as he got momentary blinded, after rubbing his eyes he opened to find himself in another room. The walls looked like medieval castle walls, there was a giant furnace that was bubbling with liquid metal. There was a big anvil in the middle of the room with the furnace next to it, he spotted all the classical blacksmith utensils around, but they all looked kind of shabby.

*Okay, so I have my own pocked dimension to smith stuff, neat.*

There were no windows around and the room was lit by torches that were attached to the walls, plus a lot of candles here and there, the whole place had that middle-age vibe to it. He pulled his golden hammer that was supposed to have some crafting related bonuses, he swung it around hitting the anvil in the middle just to hear a nice ding sound.

*Well... shit, what am I supposed to do in here, I didn't learn any crafting skills*

He could see some iron ingots lying around the place, but not much besides that. Matt scratched his head and brought up his window, which was a bit different as it looked like the crafting space had its own window. He could see the list of recipes that he probably previously got in the bundle listed there, it was mostly for regular weapons like daggers, swords, maces. But there were other things like fans, robes and some tools. Guess it included all the basic craftable items that were in the bundle, though they were in there and not in his head for some reason.

Matt selected a regular looking iron dagger, wondering if it would do anything and as he clicked he saw that there was an iron ingot next to the dagger picture now. As he was looking at that a little clip played of a caricature of a blacksmith picking up an ingot and placing it in the large smelting furnace and then hammering on the anvil.

*Is it showing me to place one of those ingots in the furnace? Well, not like I have anything to lose at this point.*

He shrugged and picked up an iron ingot from the pile by the wall, and slowly placed it in the furnace. After this something weird started to happen, the smelting furnace began glowing and music began playing. He then looked at the anvil in the middle of the room as an enthusiastic voice could be heard coming from it.

"Get Ready! 3.........2.......1......GO!"

He was bewildered as a slab of red glowing metal appeared on the large anvil, a catchy tune began playing and some glowing green prompts started appearing on the slab.

*God damn... this is a rhythm game!?*

He had the golden hammer in his hand and started hitting the glowing green spots that turned red if they were out of sync, the whole thing took about 2 - 3 minutes and as he kept hitting the hot block of iron it started turning into the shape of a dagger.

"Congratulations, you created a common Iron Dagger middle grade"

He looked at the dagger on the anvil while some confetti got tossed in the air and then vanish soon after, he picked it up and swung it around and sure enough it was a real dagger and it was quite sharp too. Matt was a bit surprised by the whole thing but that explained why he didn't get any direct knowledge about crafting, it just put it in the game like system and depending on how well he did in the rhythm game, the quality of the item would be decided.

*Uh... I'm not good at rhythm games..."

He sighted while tossing the dagger into his inventory, he decided to chug another ingot into the furnace and now being prepared he run up to the anvil before the countdown started. A different tune than before started playing which made him frown but he was more ready than the last time as he started hitting the spots with his golden hammer, the slab of iron glowed quite a bit as he managed to land a perfectly timed hit but this was just his second time and all things considered he did quite well though he missed here and there.

"Congratulations, you created a common Iron Dagger high grade"

He took out the first dagger and compared it to the other one, the high grade one was shinier and it looked sharper than the first one he made. He poked at the tip with his finder wondering how sharp the thing was, but the dagger wasn't able to inflict any damage on his superior body, that had a high body refining technique and common grade items couldn't damage him.

"Well, I guess this is an interesting way to do it... at least It's fast I just need to gather materials and the rest thing is automatic. I wonder if I can add some special effects to these items..."

He started playing with the crafting interface and he figured out that he could add other items to the ones that were required, the prompt only showed him the minimum required items needed.

"Wonder what will happen if I add one of those beast cores...

He had the big rabbit core on him and also the smaller crimson wolf cores that the villagers gave him previously. So he decided to test it once more, going for a regular sword now, it used up one more iron ingot then the dagger. After adding one of the cores he started hammering the now bigger slab of metal in the middle of the anvil. He started getting better and better at the game but he wasn't perfect at it quite yet, but after getting the finished product he got surprised.

"Congratulations, you created a common Crimson Long Sword perfect grade"

"Hm, don't need to get a perfect score to get the highest grade item? Maybe if you add high grade materials it lowers the requirements for the items."

Afterward he went on a weapon creation frenzy and used up all the iron ingots and cores to create perfect grade common weapons, he made a Spear, a two-handed Hammer, a Greatsword, an Axe and a Jian Sword there were all in the crimson series and looked nice and menacing as the added cores gave them a style upgrade as well.

"I need cotton fiber or leather for clothes, so I guess I'll try those later... don't think the hammer game will play for those though."

He didn't see any tailoring equipment, it looked like a forge mostly for weapons and maybe metal armor, though people in this world didn't really wear those as they used a plethora of colorful robes and clothes. Guess you don't need iron armor if you can make your body as hard as a diamond.

Chapter 22

He found himself back in his cabin, nothing looked out of place as he was standing in the same spot as if he never left. He felt a bit spent, but more mentally than physically. He had a high cultivation base so after he focused his senses he could more or less hit all the glowing spots, he reckoned that due to this he would be able to have an easy time crafting things below his level that were the common and mortal grade items but when getting into the earth and heaven graded ones there would be a spike in difficulty.

Matt was curious about making the cultivator robes, there was a couple of cool ones in there though the one he was wearing felt like it was quite the high spec as well. He soon would find out the horror that was tailoring...

He turned in for the night. After a good night's rest, he left his cabin only to get greeted with many busy villagers that looked like they were still clearing out the gory pile of centipedes that he left for them. He kind of turned his head in the opposite direction as he spotted the mess hoping that people wouldn't see him, but he was kind of sticking out like a sore thumb.

Well not like anyone would complain to him even though they were mad, Mad just b-lined towards the market as he wanted to get some clothing materials. His appearance was met with bows as always and with smiles from some of the villagers and with frowns from others. He headed over to what looked like a stand, it had various beast hides in it and other things.

"W-welcome sir, how can I help you?"

The shop owner that was a middle-aged lady greeted him as he moved closer, he nodded at her and replied with a casual hello. He looked at the wares and then back to the shop owner. He rubbed his chin while looking at the wares while the lady got more and more nervous.

"How much can you give me for this..."

Matt didn't really know the value of those clothes as well he didn't know the value of his gold coins or spirit stones. The shiny coin was placed at the wooden table and the woman looked at it with open eyes. She grasped it with a shaking hand and examined it. Matt looked on as the lady shook, bit and then licked the coin for some reason before trying to return it to him.

"S-sir, I cannot accept this... it's too much"

The woman was troubled as she did indeed want the golden coin, but this coin, if you translated it to the modern world rate, would go for about 10k dollars or Euro. The things the villagers sold weren't worth that much, they were mostly simple cotton cloth and beast leather, a common thing around these parts.

"Well... just give me all of your leather and cloth, uh don't need finished clothes just the fabric though. You can just give me more if you have some later."

After some pushing, he managed to give the bewildered woman the gold coin and left with a bunch of leather pelts and rough cotton fabrics. He sneaked back into his wooden cabin and closed the blinds in his room before heading out into the crafting abode once more. He now had the raw materials needed for the procedure and he was curious about what the game system had cooked up for him next.

He looked at the items that he could craft and selected a leather tunic that looked kind of sturdy. After he selected the crafting item a prompt appeared if he really wanted to change to crafting clothes, which he found strange as the prompt didn't appear when he was selecting the weapon recipes. After he selected yes the room started shaking and the anvil started getting lowered to the floor, till it was gone. In its place, a handlebar started moving up along with a white platform. After it appeared it started glowing in a pattern that he was familiar with.

*I-is this a dance dance revolution pad...*

It had two arrows pointing left and right and two pointing up and down, but also had some going into each corner as well. The handlebar was there to hold onto it while tap-dancing around as it was in these kinds of games. He put in the required leather pieces for the tunic and looked at the dreaded dance game. He could see which arrows he needed to step on as an out of place screen moved down from the ceiling and it showed him the steps he needed to take while showing a seizure-inducing animation on it as well.

Matt awkwardly moved his legs hitting the arrows more or less, he never had the pleasure of trying this in real life and the experience was new so he didn't get a good score as he fumbled around. In the end, the got a middle grade one which wasn't really an achievement as he would have to really mess up to get a common low grade.

*I think I'll stick to this robe in the future...*

He looked at the dancing game which was flashing in the colors of the rainbow and looked super out of place in the gloomy blacksmith looking room. But he did get a whole lot of crafting resources, it would be a drag to let them go to waste.

*Well, no one can see me in here... so no one will know... still better than sewing the stuff myself.*

He slapped his cheeks to pump himself up, he moved his feet to the beat fumbling here and there but after a while he figured out the gist of it, but he didn't get anything above the Common high grade, now he had a lot of tunics and cotton robes that he didn't know what to do with. The clothing didn't really have any special attributes to them, besides being a bit more sturdy due to the high grade. He would have to add the beast cores and other resources to make them more special.

*Think I had enough for today ... *

He rubbed his chin and looked at his system screen, after going through the crafting window he also figured out that he could access a creative mode where he could design his own weapons and armor, but it was severely limited at the moment and he couldn't add much besides symbols or letters. Maybe later he could design a gunblade ... or maybe a chain blade?

He got a little bit sweaty after the jumping and wiggling his posterior about, if someone saw him dance around with that awkward expression on his face he would probably crawl under a big mountain in shame. For now, he exited the pocket crafting dimension and gave out a sight.

*Well, not if you don't take the fact that I have to do silly games to craft items, this isn't a bad thing at all, though I'll have to experiment with the recipes and see what I can use to make things like the crimson weapons, maybe I can use something besides the beast cores as well.*

He had somewhat an idea what to do now, gather more points, make more weapons and maybe more robes. Though he didn't want to spend a super long amount of time in this region, he did remember the city that he was supposed to go to, but he wanted to stock up on things he could sell there as well.

*Well, don't think it will be a problem if I stick around here a bit longer, there must be more insect nopes to slay!*

So the decision was made and Matt continued with his routine, he mostly hunted monsters in the day gathering them for the townspeople which were a lot gladder as he started bringing in some huge lizards and snakes as well. He tended to go for the nonmammal looking beasts as those reminded him of cats and dogs a bit too much. This was hypocritical, but he mostly defeated those in self-defense or while protecting other people thus, the poor tribe received quite a bit of insect monsters to work on instead. A week had passed like this.

Chapter 23

Name : | Zhang Dong
Affiliation : | Zhang Clan
Spirit Points : | 21034
Cultivation Base Qi : | Core Formation [Early Stage 42%] (Lightning Core)
Cultivation Base Body : | Foundation Establishment [Middle Stage 0%] (Silver Body)
Techniques : | Lightning Qi cultivation art, Silver Body Arts, Thunderlight Sword, Thunder Movement Art, Lightning Javelin, Lightning Punching and kicking arts, Basic and Advanced Fighting Techniques.

I implied in the previous chapters that he also got punching and kicking skills along with some combat techniques, but I never put it in the table and just left dots in there. Sorry if you get confused that I put it in now. Might have forgotten to do it earlier... >_>;

A handsome man was standing out in the wilderness, he was looking at a house-sized boulder. He had his fist tightly clenches as he was focusing on the huge rock in front of him. The space around the man started crackling and tiny bolts of electricity started appearing. They were guided to his closed fist filling it with spiritual energy and making it glow in the process. The man pulled his fist back while looking at the big boulder in front of him and then delivered a punch. The hit produced a thunderous sound and as his fist collided with the side of the large rock it exploded into pieces. It now had a huge hole in the middle of it, collapsing right afterward as the man looked and nodded.

Matt was getting used to this cultivator lifestyle a bit, the gaming system made things easy as he spent his day's training in his previously gotten techniques. He had quite a bit of points now, though not enough to buy the better crafting abode just yet. Even less if he wanted to get the entire bundle that cost over twice that plus not like he really needed all of the crafting recipes in the system. His cultivation was increasing at a rapid pace as well, he wondered if his body was just gifted or if the cultivation method was special as he didn't think cultivating would be this fast, he should hit the next stage within two to three weeks like this.

*Okay, I'm getting the hang of it now. Guess it wasn't such a bad idea to stick around here for a while. Guess the next step would be to test things out.*

He mostly used kiting abilities, which in gamer terms were using his range skills to fight the enemies off while being at a safe distance. He didn't want to rely on only those though. He wanted to spend some time getting used to the hand to hand combat skills that he had. He wanted to find himself someone or something to test his skills on. Matt glided up into the air and flew around the forest. But as he flew around he couldn't really see any beasts that were worth his time. So he decided to go deeper into the forest than he usually did in the direction that he previously arrived in it was about half a day's time away. He got really good at zooming around now so it might take even less. Luckily after a while, he found a fitting one, this one had red eyes as the other crazy beasts and looked like a silverback gorilla, but it had sharper teeth, long claws on its hands and a horn coming out of the forehead, plus it had four arms.

*Well, that's one ugly looking unicorn.*

Frenzied Horned Tetra Ape (Foundation Establishment early stage )

*It has that prefix, well... now to approach that without pooping my pants...*

The monster was scary looking, it was drooling and just standing there. It had a big bone in one of its hands, it placed the bone in its mouth, the sharp teeth just crushing the hard bone in one big chomp as it munched on it. Matt gulped as he was watching, but he had decided that he needed to get stronger and this gorilla unicorn looking thing would be a good start. He was slightly paranoid and he knew how these cultivator worlds worked, so he needed to get in some practice for the future to come.

*Okay, I got my healing and spirit energy recovering pills right here, shouldn't be a problem...*

He jumped down from his flying sword and placed it in his storage ring, for now, he wanted to face this creature in close range combat. He started slowly going up to it, the large ape noticed him coming and gave out a huge roar. This making Matt stop in his track as he focused on the monster that began charging at him in an enraged bull charge.

Matt went into a defensive position and took in a good breath of air to relax. He focused on the charging behemoth that was making the ground thump each time in brought it's meaty fists onto it as it pushed itself forward at him. The creature was quite scary looking and twice his size as well as bulky. His mind was telling him to run away at this moment as the gorilla choo choo train was barreling towards him. But he wanted to get used to this, he couldn't avoid all of his problems plus the creature was more visually scary but when it came to its abilities it paled in comparison to his.

He used his movement technique right before the monster was about to deliver an overhead strike, leaving an afterimage that was sparkling with static energy. When the creature smacked his after image it felt electricity run through its body, shocking it and making it stop in its tracks for a brief moment while also delivering moderate damage. Matt had learned that he could use his movement technique in this way, so as he dodged he left afterimages of himself that had residual lightning qi that if they got touched discharged a shock to the assailant.

He appeared behind the Tetra Ape in a blur, giving it a good kick to it's back which sent it flying. The creature flew face-first into a tree that collapsed under the strain and shattered into many splinters. The monster roared in madness as it shook, it got kicked quite hard and it was feeling a sharp pain in its rear. Though as if not caring or just mad it turned back after gathering itself back up, it roared once more and charged yet again.

Matt didn't punt it with all his might, he didn't even infuse his foot with lightning Qi this time around just using his body as he tested out the waters. He danced around with the monkey monster, the creature was easy to dodge and predict as it only came at him with berserk charges and large swings which he could dodge at ease. He finally managed to get used to the intimidating look of the thing and had no problem delivering a nice hard punch to the creature's ugly mug, which just made it tumble backward hitting even more trees.

*Hm, guess I'm getting desensitized to battling a bit...*

He looked at his fist that had blood stuck to it, he grimaced and shook the red liquid off. Then he looked at the creature in front of him that he was kind of bullying at this point.

*Or maybe now, now I'm feeling bad about this whole thing...*

He didn't feel so good about himself as he used the creature as a punching bag, just testing out his skills while the thing looked more haggard with each passing moment, though if things were reversed he was sure that the monster would have torn all his limbs and eaten him like a snack. But as he was contemplating his skewed moral compass something strange started happening, the Ape started convulsing after his last hit, it started exuding strange red energy. After a while, he could see tentacles coming out of its ears and even bursting out of it's back the name above its head also had changed including its cultivation level.

Corrupted Horned Tetra Ape (Foundation Establishment middle stage )

It started looking like a tentacle monster and as if revitalized it let out a different kind of scream than before and charged at Matt again.

Chapter 24

*Corrupted? It went up a level?*

Matt looked at the strange-looking gorilla that had tentacles protruding out of it now. The tentacle monster charged at him once more trying to overwhelm him with it's added speed and power. This, of course, wasn't enough to give Matt a run for his money, the only thing holding him back from beating this thing up once more was the disgusting way that it looked so instead of attacking it he backed away.

*Eww, that thing looks gross...*

"Hey, I'm not an anime girl, you tentacle monster!"

He shouted as he used his movement technique to zap the tentacle mass while he evaded, the creature looked like it took less damage than before. The creature kept up with its charge, destroying the trees and boulders along the way, smashing into anything in its path while Matt tried to keep his cool. Finally, he got fed up with the constant running away and charged up a lightning javelin after dodging and letting the monster attack his after image as it dumbly did all the time. The thrown bolt of lightning smacked the creature in the upper arm shoulder, which was now gone.

The man could see a big gaping hole in the corrupted creature's right shoulder, but along with blood more tentacles started squiggling around from it. The tentacles thrashed as if they were mad and he could see that most of the creature's insides were composed of those tentacles and weird tendrils. This, of course, made him grimace in disgust even more.

"If one won't do the job... then how about ten?"

He didn't give the monster time to recover as he started choking his energy spears at it, putting more holes into its large frame. But each hole was just getting filled up by more and more tentacles and the ugly thing wasn't going down and still tried to charge at the cultivator in white. He was too fast for it but didn't really want to get too close to the thing but his range attacks didn't seem to be working. He kept on hitting it, taking out the legs from range and finally landing a blow on the head that just burst open with more squiggly things.

"Why... won't ... you ... DIE!"

The creature didn't have regular legs now and was just a pile of tentacles attached to the creature's torso, it was a lot slower than before but by some strange rage-filled will it still wiggled its way towards Matt. He at this point started charging up the javelin attack once again, but this time he really focused all of his spiritual energy to pump it up to an enormous spear of light. The huge lightning spear crackled around as he held it above his head, he looked at the disgusting pile of tentacles that was inching slowly in his direction and flung it at the creature.

What followed was a resounding boom, the monster exploded along with the ground that it was slithering on. A huge dust cloud was kicked up and the wind pressure from the explosion was immense, making the large trees in the vicinity shake violently. The creature was finally dead but it also delivered its last blow against its opponent as the massive amount of tentacles flew in all directions and one of them hit Matt straight in the face.

Corrupted Horned Tetra Ape Slain (Foundation Establishment middle stage ) Earned 6000 Spirit points

The slimy appendage slid down his face and to the ground while his eye twitched. After the dust had settled he could see the squirming tentacles all over the place. Something strange started happening afterward though, the squirming appendages started giving out smoke or steam and after a while, they just crumbled into dust. The only thing that was left was the creature's core that was in the spot that the monster was slain. Matt wiped his face with his sleeve and moved over to the spot that the creature's core was and examined it, the core was described as a Tetra Ape core, guess the corruption didn't affect the cores that the monsters dropped, it was even of the lower early-stage level.

Matt looked around the forest that seamed eerier than it usually did, this creature gave him the creeps. It was one of the strange monsters that were always berserk and enraged, he guessed that it was those tentacles that were the cause of the disease but when the host died they just turned to dust leaving the core intact.

*Is it some kind of parasite? Or did something infect it for some reason... You can't detect if the creature is corrupt after you kill it as the tentacle things inside just vanish and the core remains intact. Hm, should I ask the village chief about it? Maybe he'll know something about it*

The man was feeling a bit creeped out, hoping that it wasn't anything that he could get infected with as the tentacle did hit him in the face and all, so the first thing that he did was to find the river and vigorously wash his face in it. He checked his status screen if it would show something clicking his name but nothing out of place came up. He decided to head to his temporary base of operations in the village hoping to get some answers from the village chief.

It was the middle of the day and he was a bit far out but he managed to return before the sun went down. He didn't get in any trouble while returning so he gave out a relieved sigh, he didn't want to fight any more tentacle monsters on the way. Matt didn't have anything to give to the villagers today as he spent most of the day 'sparing' with the ape monster and the trips back and forth took up the rest. He went to his cabin first as he thought about what he should ask the village Chief and after that, he gave him a visit while the sun was going down.

People greeted him as always on the way there, he already knew his way here and the villagers kind of accepted the quirky Senior. He was giving him a lot of resources to sell and bargain with other tribes, even though the bug monsters were a bit of a hassle.

"Greetings, could I have a word with you, Yang Shan?"

The other man nodded and led him to his room, Matt noticed that he looked a bit different today as if he had some things on his mind also there were fewer guards around for some reason. After the got to the room he started explaining about his encounter with the strange monster, of course, he didn't say about how he just spent most of the fight just running away and throwing his attacks at the monster.

"I came across a strange beast today after it took some damage it started changing, its cultivation realm expanded while various tentacle-like appendages started protruding from its hulking form. Of course, it's dead, but the tentacles vanished without a trace afterward, it seems that that's what is causing the beasts to go mad in this forest."

The Chief had a stern look on his face while Matt tried to explain what had happened in a more formal way for a change. The burly man rubbed his chin while looking distressed.

"It can't be ... it has to be the Corrupt one ... it corrupts other creatures to elevate its cultivation, consuming their bodies. But if one of the beasts has already turned, it must be close for it to feed... it's probably going to come out of its hiding place to consume the other monsters."

Matt didn't like where this was going, there was some kind of strange monster out there, probably one with even more strange appendages. Maybe now would be a good time to leave this place? He wasn't that keen on fighting the thing, but as he was thinking about his next move the burly man dropped to his knees and started kowtowing furiously.

"Distinguished, honorable, illustrious and respectable Senior!"

*Aren't you overdoing it with the honorifics dude...*

"Please hear me out, my stupid son has gone missing for a few days, he probably went to the forest to prove himself after offending you, but he hasn't returned with his men, now I fear that the Corrupted One could have something to do with it, please find it in your upright and just heart to aid this old man in finding his stupid son!"

Matt looked at the burly man that was hitting the floor with his forehead, making thumping sounds that just made more people show up and see the Chief prostrating himself in front of him. But instead of stopping the man they did the exact thing as they also knew that his son was missing putting Matt in an awkward position.

"Ugh..."

Chapter 25

The thumping in the house continued as Matt was looking at the people down, there were burly men and women even children prostrating themselves in front of him, probably most of them were the relatives of the silky-pants that was giving him a migraine right now. He scratched the back of his neck and then held out his hand out.

"Ok... Stop, that's enough."

All of the people stopped in their tracks but their heads remained planted to the ground, not daring to move an inch unless the honorable Senior told them too. They were praying that he would help them out, if he didn't the Chief's son was as good as dead and they would probably have to relocate their tribe as well due to the corrupted monsters and the even more dangerous beast that was behind them.

Matt felt a headache coming along as looked at the silent people in the room. He contemplated what he should do for a moment, the moral thing to do would be to help the people out. The smart thing to do would be to just get out of there or wait to see how strong that so-called corrupted one was otherwise he might find himself munched on by some creepy thing. Though Matt was one of the sorts of people that broke under increased social pressure so even though he didn't think it was such a good idea, he decided to help the people out plus this also aligned more with his morals, plus deep down inside he was a big softy. He also was feeling bad for the prostrating people in front of him and he reckoned that he should be able to handle the creatures in the forest as he didn't come across anything too dangerous for the time he has been here.

He gave out a big sigh as he spoke.

"Okay, stand up. In what direction did that silk... uh in what direction did your son go?"

Yang Shan was the first one to raise his head as a glint appeared in his eye, or it might have been a tear. He stood up and bowed once more, the rest of the tribe members did the same while backing away a bit.

"I can't promise you anything though, this forest is gigantic it's like looking for a needle in a haystack."

As Matt was talking, the Chief took out some kind of circular medallion with a stag engraved on it and handed it over to the cultivator in white.

"This is?"

"Senior, this is a treasure that was handed down to me by the previous Tribe's head. It has a second part in the form of the ring if you focus your energy into it you can feel in what direction the other part is. It has a limited range though so we can't use it from here."

The chief replied while Matt was looking at the stag medallion.

"I didn't use it as I thought the boy would just be away for a couple of days while hunting, he does these things from time to time... but with the appearance of the corrupted one, I'm afraid that he has a slim chance of coming back."

Matt tried putting his spiritual energy into the magical treasure and as it absorbed it, it started to give out a dinging sound as it glowed slightly. After a few moments, the dinging stopped as the treasure couldn't find its counterpart. He nodded and was lead out of the Chief's house and pointed in the direction that the silky paints and his crew had left. The other problem was that it was getting dark outside, but the other people looked quite concerned and were giving him those puppy dog eyes as they pleaded.

"W-well, I'll be off then."

He said awkwardly as he didn't take the expectations of these people all that well, his shiny Crystalline Sword was tossed out onto the ground, he jumped onto it and as he took his flying stance it took off while the concerned tribe people looked at each other with worry in their eyes. They didn't doubt that this Senior was strong, but they didn't know if he could handle the evil beast in the forest they had to keep the well being of the village in mind so they decided to inform every important person in the village. They had to prepare for the situation of the Senior not coming back, or abandoning the Chief's son and coming back empty-handed. If it came to that they would have to relocate deeper into the mainland while seeking help from the stronger clans that were in the cities.

The Crystalline Sword produced a faint light as it drifted through the air with the muscular cultivator on top, that was scratching his head while flying forward.

*Why does it always have to be started by the young bratty masters, every damn time. Do they have some kind of troublemaker gene in them to cause trouble for others if you interact with them?*

He had been flying for a good hour by now, the sun was down but he still couldn't get anything from this treasure. Matt had no tracking skills besides his map, but it had a limited range of showing living organisms in the vicinity as well. The boy and his entourage had a couple of days head start on him, but they couldn't have gotten that far into the forest and he was a lot faster on his flying sword than people on the ground that could only run. He only had a vague idea where they could have gone, the people of the tribe told him a couple of places that Yang Rong could have gone to.

He was hovering above one of those places right about now, but he couldn't see anything but he found out that he could see a lot more in the dark than he thought he would be able to. Guess the cultivator's body came with various enhancements, plus the moons in the sky were also illuminating the silent night.

Why was it so silent though, Matt stopped in his tracks and tried to listen. He thought he would hear wolves howling in the night or various creepy beasts just crawling around the place. But it was really silent as if they had gone into hiding or escaped in a different direction. This gave of many red flags in his mind when he thought about it.

*Did they run away due to the corrupted one?*

He gulped and resumed with his flying. Going further and further as he flew for a good couple of hours now being close to the spot that he had arrived in where it all started. He grasped the medallion and inserted his Qi into it, it started dinging and dinging just as it always did, but this time around it gave out a louder sound than before. Matt could feel that the magical treasure was somehow guiding it to a certain spot in the forest, this must have been the area that the kid was in and would you know it, it was right dab in the same spot that Matt was spirited away to this place.

He scratched his neck and wondered if it was just a coincidence as he sped up towards that area, he still remembered hitting that tree and kicking that poor rabbit into meat paste by mistake. He just wanted to get there and get the kid and his idiotic posse and would you know it, there were all there but looked haggard and in a bad state, he was still a bit from their position but with his enhanced vision he could see some beasts surrounding the group. The beasts in question had squiggly tentacles protruding from their bodies as the ape that Matt battled previously.

Matt brought out his trusted lightning javelin and was ready to give them air support before they got the hentai girl treatment there, he really didn't want to see burly men getting tentacled if he could do something about it. But before he could come to their rescue the broken tree in the middle of the field that he crushed previously started shaking and with a resounding boom, a creature emerged from within, kicking up a crowd of dust in the process. It was big and ugly and when Matt squinted his eyes to take a closer look his jaw dropped.

"I-is that... Is that god damned Cthulhu!?"

The creature wasn't as big as the great old one from the stories, it was given or take 6 meters tall, but it was the spitting image of peoples favorite monster, it had the octopus-like head whose with a mass of feelers on them, plus the scaly humanoid body, claws on both hands and legs as well as a fitting name...the name made Matt feel like he was getting trolled by someone.

Mini'thulhu The Corrupted One ( Foundation Establishment Great Circle )

Chapter 26

The creature gave out a roar and the other tentacle beasts around it started squiggling as if they were having a dance party. The Tribe members were hugging each other tightly with the silky pants in the middle. The kid's face was filled with tears and snot at this point and he probably had some more liquids filling out his pants as he looked terrible.

Matt got a hold of himself as the creature was looking around, it had wings on it's back just like Cthulhu. It spread its wings and generated a lot of wind that sent the poor tribe people flying, slamming into each other, the ground and trees while the other tentacle monsters got closer. Just as the group of tribe people made peace with the world as they knew that they would be devoured any second now they saw some light in the distance and it was getting here really fast.

The closes tentacle thing next to them exploded into gorry bits as Matt's lightning strike hit it, then more and more of the creatures started exploding from the hits while the people looked on in astonishment in their eyes. The big baddie turned in the direction that the attacks were flying from and gave out a roar, but it was met a light spear to the side as well. It staggered from the hit and a big wound appeared but it started healing at a rapid pace.

Matt appeared in a flash and kept zooming around on his sword while looking down at the creatures below, the Tribe members cheered as they saw who it was. They were glad that the Senior that they were familiar with somehow appeared out of the blue and was attacking the monsters. The group was a band of misfits but they weren't dumb, they saw their chance as they noticed that the creatures stopped paying attention to them and slithered closer to the man standing on the flying sword. So they used this chance and run into the forest from the open field, Matt did clear out a path for them to escape and all.

So they grabbed their sobbing and shocked silkypants master and bolted for their dear life while not looking back at what was happening behind them, they could see some tentacle creatures moving to the clearing where the biggest monster was. For some reason, they didn't seem that interested in them anymore. It was an eerie sight of the tencale wiggling things just converging into one location it was better viewed from up in the sky which Matt could see happening.

The cultivator dressed in white looked as the other people escaped on their own and then looked down at the squiggly spectacle below him. The big baddy was roaring up at him, this for some reason made his flying sword buzz. He had to focus on it so that it wouldn't drop down to the ground, guess the monster was trying to bring him down below but its cultivation wasn't strong enough for that.

*Hm, still in foundation establishment realm, guess I can still handle this one. Was this thing placed as the tutorial boss or something, or was I summoned here knowing that it was hiding below that tree and gathering its forces?"

The monster got angry as it couldn't get the person down to the ground and found itself covering its head with those massive muscular arms. The lightning bolts started raining down on it as Matt was testing out the waters, the creature was taking a lot of damage and all but it was healing quite fast as well. But it didn't look like the thing would be a problem for him at his current level. He didn't feel like jumping down and engaging in fisticuffs with the huge thing, what if it spit some strange goop on him or if he got covered in tentacles?

While he was doing this he kind of ignored the smaller corrupted monsters that were slithering towards the big guy, but if he had some combat experience he might have been able to figure out what was about to happen. Why was the monster infecting the other beasts? What was the purpose of turning them into tangled up tentacle monsters? Also, the Chief mentioned that it used the monsters to elevate its cultivation in some way. But by the time the cogs in Matt's head started turning you could see a massive ball of squiggling tentacles in the open field that was giving of an eerie red light.

What happened next would act as a wake-up call for Matt, as the huge humanoid-shaped, squid faced monster bolted away with huge strides and jumped at that mass of tentacles. The cultivator stopped pelting it with his lightning bolt spam and looked bewildered not sure what the creature was doing, was it trying to hide from him in that? Did it want to shield itself with the tentacles? But no, seconds after the whole area began glowing in a crimson hue, Matt could feel the mass of tentacles giving off bursts of spiritual energy and he could have sworn that he heard a heartbeat-like tune that went along with those bursts of Qi.

What happened next was a low witch shriek that made the man hold his palms to his ears. He could feel a sharp pain in his ears as he lost control of his flying sword and crashed to the ground. He landed a bit away from the mass of tentacles, but the screen kept him back from it. The creepy ball started shrinking and shrinking, it looked like the energy was getting absorbed from it and the tendrils crumpled into dust. Afterward, you could see the monster emerging, its eyes glowing red and it looking a bit taller than before all the injuries that it had sustained also couldn't be seen.

Mini'thulhu The Corrupted One ( Core Formation Early Stage )

It as at this moment that he knew, he fucked up. He probably should have taken out the smaller creatures first before they could gather up to give the ugly looking boss a power-up, he also felt that something was now blocking his flying skill as he couldn't make the sword hover upwards well enough to escape.

This was the first time he came across anything at the same cultivation realm as he was, he wasn't sure what that meant but it wasn't anything good. His first thought was to flee but would he be able, if he fled what would happen to the people that were in the forest not so far away, would this behemoth turn on them instead? He mustered up all his bravery and took a fighting stance, he sure hoped that he could handle this beast as but it looked really intimidating.

The monster-filled the area with its core formation aura which gave Matt goosebumps then charged at him. It was a lot faster than the gorrila monster that he sparred previously and a lot bigger as well. Matt misjudged how fast the creature would get to him and was a bit slow with his dodging. He could see a huge fist getting thrown right at his face, he imagined he would be turned to paste if that thing cleanly hit him. Dodging to the side he could feel the creature's limb just barely passing, the wind pressure throwing him off balance as he fumbled to the side a slight pain hitting his shoulder as the giant fist's knuckle grazed it. This was the first time that he actually felt pain, the previous beasts were below his body strengthening technique so they weren't able to even hurt him even if they gave him a full-powered hit.

He instinctively grasped his shoulder as he felt pain, but this only gave the monster the opportunity to extend one of its wings which landed a direct hit to his chest. He was sent flying into some trees, kicking up a storm of broken bark and splinters. The creature roared again while stretching out its muscular arms in a show of might, taunting its enemy that it just landed a hit on. Matt got off the ground and spit out some leaves from his mouth while his hair looked scuffled. The creature looked like it was feeling good about itself as it managed to bash this cultivator good and thought he wouldn't be a problem. What happened next was a barrage of attacks that the monster unleashed on the human, which the human mostly managed to doge but not precisely. Each time he tried to evade he got scratched, poked and prodded and the damage on his clothes was a testament to that as after a while you could see a big scratch on his chest. Matt panted while he was trying to not die from the enraged monsters continues attacks.

Matt wasn't really looking where he was dodging the monster as the fight had switched locations into the deep forest, the two were kicking up a storm as the huge behemoth just stomped its way through the trees while charging at the cultivator. Being the lucky bastards as they were, the tribe cultivators found themselves escaping in the same direction that the fight was happening. They looked behind them and they saw the hulking monster moving towards them while the Senior that they knew was dodging its attacks, he was dodging right towards them. Matt stopped in his tracks and looked behind, seeing the people right there they had stupid expressions on their faces as they collapsed from the monsters pressure. The beast didn't care about them all that much it was focused on Matt, so it delivered another huge swing in his direction while the people were behind him, if he dodged they would surely turn into pancakes...

Chapter 27

Time looked like it had slowed down for Matt, the giant was slowly coming towards him while the people were right behind where he was standing. They were all weak cultivators a snort from this creature could turn them into gory bits. He had a decision to make, does he prioritize his own well being and move away or does he take the hit and hope that those people will getaway. There was another option though that he was running away for all this time, it was the option to fight back.

Matt was only a regular person, his life was mundane, to say the least before he was thrown into this world. He mostly cruised by his life unnoticed never really interacting with others and just doing enough to pass his days. Never doing more than was required of him and never having any ambitions, he was okay with his video games and slow boring lifestyle. But somewhere deep down inside he knew that he wanted to change, but he never could bring himself always putting it off for another day. Sometimes he wondered how he ended up with this sort of pessimistic outlook on the world but that was soon forgotten as soon as he got a new game or tv show to enjoy. Always looking at others as they led fun lives while he himself gave up on it.

He clenched his fist, anger appearing on his face as his brows furrowed, he wanted to change himself, he needed to change himself not for the people behind him, but for himself. An oppressive aura exploded from within his body as his fist started shimmering and crackling with electricity. He met the giant fist of the monster with his own attack, he just mustered up all his courage and anger into this one hit. His hand looked tiny compared to the corrupted ones, but as the two fists met and collided the one feeling most of the pain was the huge monster instead.

Lots of spiritual energy exploded, the monster could feel its fist hit something hard it expected to squash the little human in front of it but instead it felt immense pain in its upper limb. You could see the huge muscular hand's veins bursting and the muscles convulsing as the lightning fist strike run through it. The beast got pushed back as it roared in pain, its knuckles broken to mush after it got hit by the cultivator's own fist that was infused with lightning Qi.

The man didn't stop at that though, no. He stepped forward acting and as the monster was momentarily stunned by its arm getting mangled in the exchange he delivered a high kick right to the monster's chest. The monster had a humanoid body and it also had various humanoid-like organs so as the lightning infused kick landed on the chest area it could feel the air getting sucked out of it. The ribs or rib-like bones in there broke apart as the beast got sent flying in the opposite direction crushing into many trees as it just flew in an arc.

Matt stood there, panting a bit. He looked at the creature that just flew over a hundred meters away from him and crashed into the bushes and trees. The people behind him opened their eyes in bewilderment, their pants were a lot warmer than before as they might have gotten a bit scared. They saw the white-dressed cultivator from the back, he was holding up his fist, lightning sparks coming from it. The creature was gone but it didn't take long for them to count two and two together.

*You fucking piece of shit!*

He ignored the people behind them and looked at the monster that was in pain, his eyes started glowing as he focused and took his first step forward, it was payback time. The monster stood up after a moment, it had self-healing properties so the damage was slowly regenerating. It couldn't keep it up the whole time as it did train its energy. The red eyes glowed with madness as it looked in the direction of the cultivator that it was fighting with, but he wasn't in that spot it only saw some pesky humans there instead. The creature soon saw a foot instead of in its field of vision as it landed right between the eyes, sending the hulking behemoth backward yet again.

The sound of thunder and thumping soon filled the forest along with a lot of trees getting destroyed as the creature got knocked around the whole place. The previously weak cultivator that was only dodging the attacks started wailing on the large thing, they were of the same cultivation level and all but the cultivation ranks that they had were a lot different. The monster reached its level by doping and absorbing other creatures, while the cultivator had a cultivation technique miles ahead of it.

"You like that you overgrown Squidward!"

Matt landed a palm strike to the creatures back after using his movement technique to dodge its attack, he was hopped up on adrenaline while fighting the thing but he was finally doing something. The creature might have been weaker than him, but it was still in the core formation realm and was regenerating from every hit he inflicted on it. After a while the creature started backing away while protecting itself from the hits, wings spreading apart as it tried to flee.

He could have let it flee at this point, he had won the fight. He still felt rage and was in battle mode at this point, not thinking all that straight and not being able to calm down. He used his range skills to charge up and aimed for the thing's wings which brought the monster down after a couple of hits. The corrupted one screamed out in agony as it glared at the small human in front if it had known that the ant-like existence was that strong it would have run from the start.

The monster gathered up all its energy and started glowing in a crimson hue, its muscles bulged and the tentacles on its face started thrashing about. The cultivator saw that and started charging up his own energy as well, his eyes started glowing with bright blue energy, his whole body looked like it was covered by a sheet of lightning glowing the brightest in the spot where his hands were. The two stared at each other before they ground under their feet trembled and showed cracks. The two collided with each other as they unleashed their strikes, the two started pummeling each other but this time around the cultivator didn't back away.

You could see that the creature wasn't looking too great, its regenerative powers not kicking in anymore as it had drained itself during the fight. Matt didn't look that well either, he had many scratches and bruises on his body but was still in better shape than the giant octopus. A huge arm was severed and flew up into the air as the cultivator held his light sword in one hand, the monster didn't have much time to react as it tried backing away but got one of its lower limbs severed instead then collapsed onto the ground.

It roared in protest as the small human cultivator got closer and closer. Matt saw everything in bullet time, the eerie atmosphere filled the place, you could see the damaged trees everywhere and leaves were slowly falling down. The cultivator brought both his hands together, fist placed over the other as the energy sword expanded in length and girth. He then charged at the beast that was kneeling down on the ground. The monster let out one last roar as it tried to defend itself from the attack, but its large tentacle filled head got severed right at the neck. It flopped next to the large body that went down with it, but this creature wasn't dead yet. The severed head started squiggling around and moving towards the severed neck, wanting to reattach itself.

At this moment the tribe people stood up wondering if the Senior killed the beast or not as they could hear less and less of the sounds of fighting. But then they saw the man in question fly up into the sky, he hovered there while raising both his hands above his head. He started forming what looked to be a spear of lightning, but it was growing in size every second, soon it was wider and longer than the human below it and thundering about.

Matt gave forced as much energy into the javelin attack as he could muster. He looked at the creature that was below him, the head was slowly using its tentacles to attach itself back to the body. He didn't give it enough time though as he chucked the jumbo lightning spear down on it, a resounding boom could be heard right after as the corrupted one exploded along with everything in a 500-meter radius around it, leaving a gaping hole in the ground.

Mini'thulhu The Corrupted One Slain ( Core Formation Early Stage ) Earned 90000 SP

Chapter 28

The cultivator was panting as he looked on at the big hole in the ground, the damage was immense. He could see water slowly filling up the hole as a river was close by to it. He slowly descended to the ground going to the impact zone, he grasped the only thing that remained of the beast which was its core. He looked at the thing that caused him so much trouble and smiled to himself a bit, he did it, he won. He was a bit happy that he managed to fight the beast, but a bit mad at himself for being such a coward for so long. He gave out a chuckle and then placed the tennis ball-sized core into his storage ring, he should be able to get some nice rewards for it or use it to craft some good stuff.

He looked a bit dirty due to having been battling the monster in the forest, his clothes weren't super sturdy or anything, but they had some strange self-regeneration ability to them. So with a bit of time they looked brand new, he himself didn't feel all that great, he didn't think that he fought well. He used up too much energy and relied on his superior cultivation prowess to win while running away for the first half of the battle. But it was his first fight with someone close to his level, he was happy that he actually managed to win but he had a lot of things to work on.

He popped one of the healing pills into his mouth and felt a refreshing sensation wash over him, he kind of forgot that he even had those in the middle of the fight. Matt could feel that the creature's evil Qi was subsiding and the forest would go back to how it was previously, the berserk monsters would also vanish without having its host around. He smirked at the number of points that he received for the fight which was a whooping 90k points, he would be able to get the next level of the crafting abode, or maybe some new kick-ass skill.

At this moment he remembered why he even came to this place in the first place. He looked in the direction the scared Tribe members were and hopped onto his flying sword, slowly drifting towards them while the tension from the fight subsides. His legs felt a bit wobbly at the moment , but he didn't show it the healing pills having refreshed him somehow.

Yang Rong stood up with the help of his buddies and looked in the direction of where the fighting noises were previously coming from, but now it was silent, too silent.

"D-did that man win?"

His cronies looked at him a bit awkwardly when he referred to the Senior that just saved them with 'that man' and not with a more honorable title, but they kind of gave up on their master as they knew his character well. Suddenly they heard a strange sound and in the distance, they could see a faint glow that was moving slowly towards them, at first they thought it was some monster again but after a while, they noticed that it was Zhang Dong slowly hovering towards them on his sword. There was a path of broken down tries that he made by kicking the creature away, so he had a clear path towards them.

"Everyone alive?"

The man asked the group that stood up, clasped their hands and took a bow, well everyone besides the kid they were protecting who just did a half-baked bow. This made the others sweat bullets as they didn't want to anger the person that just slaughtered a huge monster on his own. The cultivator hopped down from his sword and slowly walked over to the silkypants in question, the others already afraid of what was about to happen.

"Hey kid, you should fix that attitude problem, you'll get yourself killed one day if you continue like that."

He flicked the youth's forehead with pointing finger, which with his increased strength left a bruise behind making Yang Rong yelp out.

"Let's go back to the village, your father and family are worried sick about you."

The youth moved his head down as the cultivator mentioned his family that was worried about him, they soon moved back towards the village but it would take them a bit to get there plus it was late at night. They abandoned their temporary camp along the way, they had all of their gear in there. They mentioned this to Matt that decided that they should go see if it's still there, he didn't really want to fly at a slow pace for the entire night plus he felt tired, more psychologically than physically.

Luckily after a couple of hours, they found the old camping site that was mostly intact, didn't take the tribesmen to bring it back in order. It wasn't much but just light tents though. Matt, of course, took up the tent that the kid previously had to himself, so he had to sleep with the rest of his men in the other one. The tension lessened in the morning as they moved on, Matt decided to place all the equipment into his storage ring so that the men could move faster and ordered them to run back to the village with all their might, he wanted to reach it before the day ended.

All of the people were cultivators so they had a lot of stamina, but not that much as they were all in the Qi Condensation stage, ranging from 3 to 6. Surprisingly the beasts didn't attack them anymore, probably the disappearance of the corrupted one and the Qi that was corrupting the animals and making them violent was the cause of that. Also, the beasts weren't that stupid, they could feel the overbearing aura of the cultivator in white so they made sure to stay far away from him.

The tribe people collapsed as they were in the close vicinity of the village, other members came to help them as they spotted the whole group. They were surprised and happy that all of them were still alive and breathing, they sometimes didn't see eye to eye with these silkypants bodyguards. They were of the same tribe though and they still felt a sense of unity.

A huge commotion was then heard as everyone rushed to the town gates, the Chief showed his love to his son by giving him a good punch in the face that broke the kid's nose and sent him flying into a nearby wall. Matt scratched his neck and smiled a little bit as he saw the father 'disciplining' his no good offspring. After Yang Rong went down, he was picked up by some family members and carried away to get some medical help. Yang Shan gave Matt another bow of respect but got waved of too cut that out by the man in question.

"You don't need to do that, you'll get some knee disease if you keep kneeling to me every time we see each other..."

The burly man blushed a bit as he knew that he was overdoing it a bit, but he couldn't give the Senior much for helping his son. They left the town entrance and Matt got a small reward in the form of a feast, then he heard of his manly fighting form as the others started recounting how he had slain the beast. They didn't see him flee from the thing plus they didn't see much besides the one time he exchanged a blow with the monster and sent it flying, so they kind of put in a few good words for him making him look like a lofty battle-hardened cultivator that feared no one. After coughing a couple of times as the tribe members were praising him too much, he drunk and watched as the people danced and had a merry good time before he turned in for the day to wind down, it was about to leave this place but he would remember this place fondly. He remembered to return the camping equipment and the tracking medallion before turning in for the night. He had a lot of points to spend tomorrow.

Name : | Zhang Dong
Affiliation : | Zhang Clan
Spirit Points : | 118234
Cultivation Base Qi : | Core Formation [Early Stage 42%] (Lightning Core)
Cultivation Base Body : | Foundation Establishment [Middle Stage 0%] (Silver Body)
Techniques : | Lightning Qi cultivation art, Silver Body Arts, Thunderlight Sword, Thunder Movement Art, Lightning Javelin, Lightning Punching and kicking arts, Basic and Advanced Fighting Techniques.

Chapter 29

Tapping could be heard as the cultivator sipped on some tea and looked up into what seemed to be empty space, but he could see something there.

* Close to 120k points huh... what should I get... think I'll get the apprentice crafting abode, I'll be able to craft mortal grade weapons, those are mostly used by people in Foundation Establishment realm.*

When it came to weapon grades it went from Common then Mortal then Earth and Heaven, Common grade was used by people from the Qi Condensation realm, while mortal grade was used mostly by people from Foundation Establishment, then you head Earth grade for the core formation experts, then the Heaven graded for the Nescent Soul masters. The latter was a cultivation realm associated with the top experts on this planet, there was a very small amount of those and they were mostly the patriarchs and Grand-masters of their respected sects. Core formation experts mostly occupied the middle standing and were leaders of various top standing clans, but if you wanted to be in the highest position you needed to have at least one Nescent Soul cultivator on your side.

There was a minuscule amount of Nescent Soul cultivators around, but there also was a small amount of Core Formation cultivators around as well. Most people were in the first two stages, forming the core demographic of cultivators. This meant that he would probably have a lot of people to sell his weapons too. He could trade the spirit stones that he earned for points, he wouldn't have to fight beasts anymore. Then he could expand into the Earth grade and even make fitting weapons and gear for himself!

That was the plan so he spent the 28k points for the crafting abode, his points fell to about 90k in a second. He then spent another 10k to get some basic weapon schematics along with crafting materials required to make a couple of swords and spears that he could sell. He was in a good mood so he decided to see how well he would do in the crafting abode. After popping into the closed of dimension he noticed that the room looked a bit bigger than before and the anvil and every tool looked better than it previously did. It was still in the castle-like room but looked better. He selected the classical Jian Sword, it was one of the most popular weapon types around together with the spear.

He got ready and waited for the tune to start, it was a new song this time around as well, hit started hitting and hitting and ended up with a high grade weapon this time. He resumed the bonking, choosing the same weapon once more but this time around he put in a couple of the Qi Condensation creature cores into the mix, he also produced a high grade sword with that but it had a different appearance and patterns than the first one.

He reckoned that the weaker beast cores didn't work that well with the mortal grade weapons and he would need to use up the foundation establishment realm ones to get a similar effect that he got with the common grade weapons. But he didn't have enough of those around to blow he just had a handful and wasn't sure if he should use them up just yet. Though using one to test things wouldn't hurt so this time he selected a Guan Dao Helbard for creation and started bonking those glowing bits on the slab of metal. The metal was higher grade then what he was using on the common weapons and after he was finished he did indeed end up with a perfect grade weapon that gave out a radiant aura. He had used the first core that he got in this world, which came from the monster bunny, maybe this thing would have better penetrating power like the horn rabbits had with this?

He used up all the materials he had bought after creating 6 mortal grade weapons, these things cost a lot to make. He needed about 1k points to have enough resources to produce one, he would need to sell it for at least 100 spirit stones to break even, he wasn't sure for how much weapons went in this world so he would have to visit one of those auction hoses.

There was one more thing that he did while crafting, he was able to engrave a little logo on his weapons so he went for a lightning bolt logo, the bolt of lightning was going through the circle that was crackling with energy. It looked a bit similar to a certain superhero speedster from the previous world he lived in, be he was sure there would be no copyright problems in this world. Branding was an important thing and if he could make high grade and perfect grade weapons he was sure that his logo would be associated with quality. Due to that, he didn't engrave any logos if he made an inferior product below the high grade.

He had still 80 k points to spend, but he wasn't sure about what, he could upgrade his skills but he wasn't sure what he should go for, should he go for more power in general? More defense? He didn't really have any type of defensive skills besides the one used for evading, maybe his body refining technique could be considered a defensive skill?

As he thought about his body remembered his body strengthening technique.

Silver Body : | Silver Body is the next advanced form of the Copper Body refining technique, instead of hard psychical training that is mostly attributed to body refining techniques, the cultivator absorbs weapons/treasures that are metallic in nature to refine his body into a treasure in its own. The higher-grade the treasure is the stronger the body gets. Common grade weapons and treasures have no effect on this technique. The technique can be trained up to the Nascent Soul great circle realm.

He took out one of the weapons that he made and held the sword in his hand. He closed his eyes and started concentrating on the weapon, his body started glowing in a silvery hue and the sword started vibrating. It was a slow process taking about 10 minutes, the weapon started dissolving as time past and the metallic substance that it produced seeped into his pores and he could feel his physique getting stronger and stronger as it gave out a silvery sheen.

Cultivation Base Body : | Foundation Establishment [Middle Stage 20%] (Silver Body)

*Oh, 20% eh? So need 4 more high grade weapons to get up a realm...*

He had 4 more of the high graded weapons while the 5th one was a perfect grade, he didn't want to use that one just yet. So after an hour of absorbing the previously created weapons, he found his Silver Body breaking into the Late Stage. He got a bit crafting crazy now and spent another 1k points to make another weapon, getting it up to high grade as well. But after absorbing it this time around his cultivation budged only by 5 %.

*5%... I'd need 19 more of those weapons...That will put me at 60k points sill...*

He spent the rest of the day just crafting and absorbing the high grade weapons, he couldn't get them to be perfect, the only way was adding beast cores to do that. After he absorbed 19 of those high grade weapons like a madman he broke through into the Great circle and his silvery sheen was even more prominent. But after he tried taking in one last hard grade of those weapons he ended up with a 0,5% boost it would take a bit for him to get it past the Great Circle and into the core formation.

Matt ended up at 50k points after he crafted more high grade weapons to sell the next time he was in a city, having 9 high grade ones and 1 perfect grade.

Then he left to appear in a flash to see that he spend the whole day crafting around, he still wanted to see if he could get some handy dandy skills to help him out in the future. He went through the store, Earth grade skills were the ones used by core formation cultivators so he decided to focus on those, trying to go for the higher grade ones and after going through the lists he decided on some.

Chapter 30

Lightning Forcefield. (Earth high grade) | 17000(11900) | The cultivator is able to generate a forcefield around his body to block attacks, he can also create a sturdier field in the desired spot for more protection or widen the area depending on their cultivation.
Storm Dragon (Earth high grade ) | 18000( 12600) | Cultivator summons a dragon made from lightning, it has a mind of its own and will follow the user's orders, after it dies it discharges all stored energy.
Lightning Dao Avatar Transformation (Earth peak grade) | 30000(21000) | The cultivator transforms his body into a Lightning Dao Avatar, the size increase is dependant on the cultivation base. The cultivator gains destructive power without having to sacrifice speed while still having an increased size.

Matt felt the skill info get injected into his brain one more, the pain wasn't as bad as before, maybe his body skill upped his resistances to this. He was left with 4734, it didn't take long to spend the points but it was a hassle go get them. The best way at the moment would be fighting more beasts at his level, but things at that cultivation level were rare plus he got lucky and fought one that had just leveled up and wasn't used to the elevated cultivation.

He had more skills in his arsenal that he needed to test out, but it was also time to leave this village. The problem with the rage monsters was solved so he had fewer monsters to hunt, also he wanted to see the world a bit more as well. He was a bit more confident in himself now, he pulled up his map and looked at his destination that the system was kind of guiding him towards. Spirit Spring City was located in the Azure Dragon Empire, the map didn't really go into much detail as it only showed him the locations and the names without explaining much.

He looked at the map and the Spirit Spring city was quite a bit away from his location, he was at the edge of the empire that had mostly small tribes and villages around. The next big city that was about halfway towards his destination was called Moonlight City. It was quite large just slightly smaller than the other City that he knew off. He decided to make a stop there on his way as he didn't want to just blindly fly all the time and maybe he could sell and but some stuff in there.

He had asked the tribe people about the structure of this empire with the pretext that he was a traveler from another country. They were happy to tell him about the power structures and how the world worked, that they knew of. He learned the Qi Condensation cultivators filled up the majority of the population, most never getting through the 3rd level bottleneck. Everyone hid their cultivation methods and resources so it was hard for regular people to cultivate. That's why Qi cultivators up below the 4th level were called commoners. After a cultivator reached the foundation establishment-level he or she could create their own family clan, passing down their teachings to elevate it. There was no rule to the size of the clan so they came in various shapes and sizes. After that came the Sects, those mostly required someone to be at least of the Foundation Establishment level but near the top of that. The sect scouted disciples to their location to grow and expand their influence not requiring one to be from the same family lineage. Sects were the biggest fishes around in the empire but it wasn't ruled by a sect in particular but had an Emperor instead.

The Emperor belonged to the Long Clan and kept the Sects in check, but no one knew who would come out on top if the two factions fought. The tribe people weren't informed enough about the prominent sects and clans as any one of them was out of their league. There were many new ones being created while old ones were crushed in a constant struggle for power.

*Guess The Azure Dragon emperor would be one of the top cultivators around here then? But those people like to hide their true power so there might be a bigger boss behind him.*

He gathered some info before heading out along with some supplies that he got from the villagers for helping them out with their beast crisis. He could see the silkypants that he saved all bandaged up but mostly from the beating, his father gave him and not from the beasts. His followers looked at him with a gleam in their eyes while smiling, this made Matt feel a bit uncomfortable on the inside. He would rather have some cute girls look at him like that, but instead he had some hairy burly men do that instead which sent a shiver down his spine.

Matt moved in front of the larger brown-skinned man and gave him a smile, he then stretched out his hand going for a handshake which Yang Shan didn't understand at first.

"This is a way how people from where I come from greet or say their farewells."

He said while grasping the burly man's large hand and giving it a firm handshake, the man looked down but then shook it right back looking like he liked this new way of greeting people.

"Cuth... The corrupted one is dead so you shouldn't have any more beast problems. If you have any troubles you can search for me in Spirit Spring City, that's where I'm heading for now, I'll probably be there for a while..." *Or so I hope...*

He shook some more hands as everyone seemed to like this new sign of respect, was a bit more personal than the bowing.

"Well, I'll be heading out then. You guys take care."

A lot of people were gathered to send him off, cheering and clapping at him as he started floating up into the air.

"Well be sure to recount your deeds for generations to come, Senior. Everyone will know the name, Zhang Dong!"

*Well, at least I didn't use the name Long Dong...*

He nodded to the people and wooshed into the air, his cultivation making the crystal-like sword shine in a bright hue as he was propelled forward to his next destination. The scenery changed to a more open one, it wasn't just trees anymore as he could see people tending to their crops on their farmlands. When they looked up the could see the cultivator dressed in a white robe, his long hair fluttering in the wind along with it. He checked his map as he looked for Moonlight city that he was heading first, but also he spotted a certain spot he wanted to make a pitstop before even going there. It looked like a really tall mountain with a high elevation and that meant a better place to cultivate, he was already halfway done by this point even when doing it in this village, so he should be able to bust through to the middle stage in no time and a few days here and there wouldn't be a problem.

Nothing much happened on the way there, but he did not make it there through the day. He stopped and descended in an unpopulated area, there was not much around besides grass some trees and bushes. He kind of prepared for this type of occasion as he wondered where he should sleep when he was on the move. The cultivators from the stories always dug out some caves and then squatted in there during the night or when they were injured but he was used to sleeping on a bed.

He pulled up his screen and clicked the crafting abode icon that transported him to the candle and fire-lit space.

*Who needs to buy another pricy base if I have this already!*

The store had big and small houses, rooms and even pocket dimensions with gardens where he could reside but they all cost a huge amount. He took out a bed from his ring that he nabbed from the tribe and placed it on the ground, this crafting area was quite large and he could even dim the light in the setting, so why couldn't he use it as a sleeping space? So he turned in for the night and dreamed about marshmallow clouds.

Chapter 31

The crafting abode didn't collapse upon itself and didn't boot him out or anything so he had a good night's rest. It was super silent in there, no soul to bother him. He stretched while yawning and jumped up to his feet, what this place was missing though was a shower and he didn't think that he could install plumbing. It worked for now though, maybe he could find a lake or a waterfall to wash up later, not like he had anybody odor, though he found that a bit odd because even if he did sweat he didn't end up smelling with sweat, guess it was something about this cultivator body of his.

He appeared out in the open in a flash of light, scaring some of the wildlife in the area. Matt chuckled to himself and while munching on a chicken leg, well it was more of an unidentified bird leg, but he told himself that it was chicken. He stretched a bit, the sun already up as the crafting room didn't have any natural, so there was no rising sun to wake him up. He tossed his flying sword out again and took flight, going towards the mountain peak.

The mountain as huge, it looked a lot smaller on the map but it just went on and on till the clouds, guess everything on this continent was bigger than back on earth. He pushed more spiritual energy into his sword and flew up into the air, ascending upwards while the skill shielded him from the heavy winds and cold air.

As he broke through the soft blanket of clouds he could see the mountain peak. To his surprise it was quite green up here, he didn't see any snow around that he expected from a place at this altitude. He looked at the map and then tried to sense the aura of others around here, but it was nice and peaceful. There were a couple of beasts up here, most of the bird variety but they scattered the moment they felt his overbearing aura as he was scanning them.

There was a layer of clouds just below the tip of the mountain he was standing on, the view was just breathtaking. Matt just took a moment to look around the place, there were vegetation and a little spring in the middle. He slowly walked around while the birds flew about, the place felt peaceful, he couldn't feel any dangers around a perfect spot to spend some time to test his skills and cultivate.

He hopped up to the highest point on the mountain top, which wasn't that wide. He had just enough space to sit down in the lotus position on the almost pointy boulder sticking out of the mountain top. He started concentrating, the wind started picking up as he resumed his cultivation. The Qi in the area was a lot thicker than what it was back in that forest village, so sucking it up was a lot easier this time around. He sucked up the water like Qi into his body, nourishing his meridians and pumping his cultivation up more and more.

The storm clouds soon gathered up above him and the ones that were below the mountain peak looking like a blanket turned dark. The animals around the peak started hiding and running away from the incoming storm. The lightning strikes soon filed the entire peak, you could hear booming sounds of thunder hitting against the human cultivator that remained seated in the lotus position. The electric strikes kept connecting with his body periodically, infusing him with more and more Qi. Due to the storm, the cultivation process was a lot faster than before but it was a lot harder as well, Matt had to focus diligently as to not let the spirit energy run wild in his body and not to overflow. Because if that happened he could suffer a backlash to his cultivation, injure himself or even lose some of his progress.

He remained in that one spot, letting the bolts sculpt his body into a better shape he could feel his core expanding slightly more and more as it took the spiritual power in. He was almost in a trance, this was normal for cultivators as when they got the ball of cultivation rolling it was hard to stop. That as also the reason while most of them remained hidden from others, doing it in seclusion not wanting to be disturbed as a lapse in judgment could be very detrimental to their well being.

He was cultivating at least twice the speed than he was previously, but he didn't stop at just doing that. Matt also had some new skills that he needed to figure out. After he got his fill of absorbing spiritual energy that pushed his cultivation past 50% he decided to take a break. First came the forcefield or barrier technique. He clasped his hands, forming a seal as a semi-transparent coating started appearing around him. It looked like a regular circular barrier around a person but looked a bit more unstable with the lightning energies crackling around it. At this moment some dust got kicked up and as it came up to the barrier and blocked its approach, crackling in response. He could tell that inside he was safe from harm but outside the forcefield would discharge electricity at anything that came in contact with the barrier.

He started playing around with this skill managing to make it bigger and bigger covering about an area of 10 meters before he started having problems in keeping it together. He could also shrink it and focus in front of himself, this made the barrier thicker in that spot and it would probably defend against more damage.

Matt nodded and moved on to the Storm dragon skill, he concentrated while waving his hands around in various patterns. This skill couldn't be formed instantly which would be its weakness. After a moment electricity escaped from his body and shoot above his head, the energy concentrated into one spot and started forming a Dragon, it wasn't the western type of dragon that most people were familiar with, it was the more serpentine looking one from Eastern stories. The creature looked like a construct of blue and white light as it gave out electricity, it roared about and circled around his body as if going into a defensive position.

He could feel some kind of strange mental connection with the creature, he could also see through its eyes as it flew around. He tried giving it some basic orders like 'go over here', 'hit that rock' and 'defend this position'. It followed all the instructions to a tee, but when he ordered it to do the Fortnite dance it, it looked at him with question marks above its head.

*I guess not, heh.*

He could actually ride the thing, so it would be an alternative to his sword if he ever lost it, the Dragon was big enough for him to ride while having space for more people. This way of traveling was a lot more draining on his spiritual energy though, so it would probably not be a good idea to use it as a regular way of traveling.

The last but certainly not the least was the Avatar transformation, he took a good breath in before he released the skill. It didn't have any fancy hand movements to activate, he just had to concentrate but it also had a bit of a charge uptime. He could feel his body giving of spiritual energy, the Qi started coating his whole body and expanding outwardly. Growing and growing, he could feel his point of view getting elevated as the technique turned him into a giant made from lightning, the sparks flew everywhere while he looked at his hands and ground below him. Size-wise he was close to 6 meters tall, but he could pump himself up further but that would drain his energy faster and faster. If he increased his cultivation he reckoned he could sustain a larger form for a longer time.

He threw a few punches, his power certainly increasing with this skill. He tried forming a javelin while in this form, which worked as the one he formed was many times larger than his regular one, he could probably take on people on a higher cultivation level than he was with this skill, but he had to be quick as it was quite draining. He tested it out, managing to keep it up without using any other skills for about 10 minutes before his energy dipped below 50 %, he would probably have a couple of minutes of real fighting time if he decided to go ham on someone.

*Guess I should probably use this more as a finisher than the opener, or to give others a scare.*

He powered down moved back to cultivating, he wanted to his core formation middle stage before moving on, it would boost his reserves quite a bit and being more powerful was always the best way to go. It took him about half a week to finally pump his cultivation to 100%, his lightning core churned with energy, crackling and expanding as he broke through his aura filled the surroundings as a lightning bolt directly hit his body. He stood up and tested his new level with a couple of punches and kicks. He felt a lot stronger than before, he could probably take out the corrupted one with one good placed hit if he fought him once more. Going up a level in cultivation was a lot bigger than going up in levels in games, it was quite the big difference indeed. After testing his skills a bit more at the higher cultivation realm he decided to head to the new town.

Chapter 32

Matt traveled through the land, zooming around and taking in the sights. The land was quite beautiful and there were many wondrous beasts and sights to see. He even found himself a waterfall to wash up in, then he tried cultivating under it but the progress was a lot slower as the water made it more difficult to transform Qi to the lightning variant. He thought to himself about his future, he wasn't here for that long and he already almost died due to a wannabe Squidward. The sights were nice and all but spending most of his life as a couch potato while playing games and being as lazy as possible made it hard for him to change the outlook on his life. He was getting better but he still had the tendency to be lazy, though there was not much to do here besides crafting, fighting and cultivating.

*Well, I should be there in a couple of hours if I keep the speed up.*

His flying speed also increased with his cultivation as not only did he have a bigger spiritual energy gas tank, the quality also improved so he spent less while having more. He didn't see other cultivators flying about on their swords, but that was natural as there weren't that many core formation ones around, a foundation establishment person wasn't able to fly much. But see a couple of flying ships, they looked like regular wooden boats and galleons but somehow they were able to move in the air as he did on his sword. Maybe he too could make something like that later one? Did the Dao of crafting include shipbuilding?

He shrugged and flew ahead, he sometimes wished that the cash store would have electronics in them, he could use his old smartphone or an mp3 player, these long trips had interesting things to see, but otherwise, it was quite boring. And would you know it, he got what he wanted as when he was passing by, he spotted a caravan, it looked like one of those merchant caravans that you would expect in fantasy settings. The caravan was stopped by the road, it was getting blocked by some group Matt knew how to hide his aura so that no one below his level could spot him by this point so he peeked down. All the cultivators were still in the Qi Condensation level but they were at a higher level then what the tribe people were ranging mostly from 5 to 12, There also was one person in the foundation establishment-level mixed into the bunch. He was a bit behind the others and was hiding his strength. The leader of the person at the 12th level was from the caravan and as Matt looked at the name above it read Lan Fei, that was a female name right?

He wasn't sure what was going on and couldn't see all that well from way up here so he decided to get a bit closer. He was quite the nosy person it seemed and the boredom was getting to him, as he got closer he noticed that the female cultivator was quite the beauty and how to put it she was quite stacked too boot. This, of course, made him use his heightened senses to zoom in on the lovely peaks, the woman had her cleavage exposed and all. She was wearing what looked like traditional Chinese clothes, just with more revealing parts and sticking to her shapely body quite tightly. He snapped out of it and looked at the group opposite them, they had smirks on their faces as they looked at the woman and the people behind them.

"This is Cheng Clan territory, you need to pay the toll if you want to pass!"

One of the thugs said while smirking at the busty woman who looked angry.

"What's the meaning of this, the Cheng Clan? The only toll is by the city gates, everyone knows that! Plus this area belongs to the Zhang Clan"

Matt perked up at the mention of his so-called clan that he had no idea who was or wasn't a member in, he found himself moving closer and closer as things got even spicier, he was totally not staring at the woman's chest and totally didn't stare as she was talking which made her ample bosom bounce in a lovely way. The Cheng Clan members noticed this too, so they started drooling themselves.

"Hehe, the Zhang Clan has its hands full in Spirit Spring City, they have no power in Moonlight city anymore."

The woman frowned at the people in front of her, if this was true then they wouldn't be able to get out of this without paying. They could not offend the ruling clan of this city if they ever wanted to do business here. But she didn't like the way these upstarts handled things, the moment they got some measure of power they extorting money from people. She gave out a sigh and tried to be professional about it, being the caravan's owner and a merchant herself. The sleazy ways of these people weren't anything new to her.

"How much?"

The men were a bit surprised that the girly didn't complain more but then grinned at her. They looked at each other and then the man in charge stepped forward and while looking at the woman licked his lips.

"100 low grade spirit stones"

The woman opened up her eyes wide and frowned, this was just plain extortion she wouldn't pay more than 10 at the gate and this price was ten times the regular amount.

"Why don't you just rob us, does your clan head even know you are doing this?"

The men chuckled to each other while standing.

"Well, we'll drop the price to 10, if you give us some special service girly~"

The man licked his lips as he moved forward and looked at the woman like a predator. The people behind the woman started complaining but didn't know if they could offend these people, the Cheng Clan might have been an upstart clan but they did have Foundation Establishment elders which they couldn't handle on their own.

"Preposterous, Lady Fei lets just leave, we can just head to another city."

One of the people from the caravan spoke while glaring at the Cheng Clan people, the woman started to think if that would be a good or bad idea, what if they go into the city and they get harassed more, you could never trust those power-hungry upstarts that did whatever they wanted. As she was about to make a decision one of the men in front of them walked out and she could feel pressure pushing her down it was a senior cultivator!

"Why don't you stay, I insist."

The real leader got revealed as the cronies made way for him, the man looked quite old with a wrinkled up face and beady eyes. He was just in the early stage, but this was enough to make the caravan people tremble in their boots. Now they were afraid, they would have no chance of running if this elder jumped in they would have to pay the toll but the problem wasn't that. The Clan people had set their sight on their boss.

"How about your people gather the spirit stones while we have a nice chat over there?"

The old man grinned while poking a bit to the side into the bushes, he turned out to be an old pervert to boot as he also wanted in on that action. The woman showed quite the disgusting face in response while the people on her side took out their weapons, this could turn bloody any second.

"Am I interrupting something?"

Suddenly everyone heard an unfamiliar voice, everyone looked around to the sides but they couldn't see anyone around but suddenly they looked up and there was one peculiar cultivator hovering right above their heads. He was standing straight up, hands behind his back and his feet planted on an expensive-looking flying sword. Everyone gulped as they realized that the man was a core formation expert, just from the way he was nonchalantly flying above them without a worry in his mind. They also could feel his overbearing aura emanating out that confirmed their concerns.

"Ah you see, we were just trying to collect the toll... "

The elder from the Cheng Clan started speaking while looking upwards while sweating bullets, the clan didn't even have one core formation elder in their mids the strongest person being at the great circle of foundation establishment so he could not offend this senior that staring him down.

"Oh, toll? thought the toll was only collected by the city gate? Right?"

"Ah yes, that's right. We must have made a mistake, Senior!

The Cheng Clan members were fast learners and could read the atmosphere. So they quickly gave up on the idea of harassing this caravan and turn tail to run. Matt didn't say much just looked at the people backed away till they were gone, then he looked at the people from the caravan that looked surprised and maybe even shocked a bit.

*A righteous man always has to aid the downtrodden! Even more so if they have...*

He thought while trying not to stare at the woman's cleavage.

Chapter 33

While the honorable Senior Zhang Dong was trying not to look at the woman's ample bosom, the woman in question was thinking about what she should do in this situation. The strange cultivator that appeared looked strong the aura was there as well, he didn't look all that all which indicated that he gained his amount of power at a younger age but didn't really reveal your true age as when you cultivated faster you tended to maintain your youthful appearance even in your older years. This meant that this could be someone within their 30's or some old monster, you could never really tell.

She followed the procedure of bowing at the man, and the people behind them did the same. The Senior above them didn't talk much but looked down in her direction intensely. She didn't know why he was keeping his gaze at her, was he like the other people that just left? He didn't seem like it though. She couldn't detect any hostile aura from this man, it felt kind of soothing and reassuring instead.

"Senior?"

Matt took his eyes of the female's bust after she looked up at him from the bow in a questioning fashion. He coughed into his hand and looked to the side as he gathered his thoughts while trying to think about something else than the lovely mountain peaks before him.

"Ah... yes! I was meaning to ask you, does Moonlight City have an auction house?"

He quickly blurted out what first came to his mind, finally getting a hold of himself. The people stopped bowing then looked up at the hovering man, he had the looks of a warrior even though part of his face was covered by the robe's hood. Zhang Dong at this time was feeling a bit silly for staring at the lovely lady for that long, hiding his slightly blushing face behind his robe as he turned his face to the side.

"Yes, there is an auction house in the city, it's called the Red Tiger auction house, you can't really miss it, it's in the pleasure district of the city."

Lan Fei replied quickly while getting to the point, her gaze looking up and a somewhat calm smile on her face as she just wanted to get to the city and relax.

"Ahh... thank's for the info... "

Matt started feeling a bit awkward, he didn't really have any experience in talking to women all that much, the experience mostly stopping with small talk at work without anything meaningful besides that. He went grasped the back of his neck which was his tick when he was feeling awkward and just nodded at the people. He didn't really have much to say to these people and didn't want to make them feel uncomfortable as they were giving them those kinds of looks.

"Well then, see you around."

He took off flying towards the city while feeling kind of silly for staring at the bouncy girl, guess in this kind of situation the hero would strike up a conversation with the beauty and then they would fall in love or something. But he felt like he would be considered some kind of weirdo if he stayed around people that he had no relations with.

Lan Fei and the others looked at themselves as the Senior that appeared in a flash, vanished just as soon as he came while not doing or saying all that much. The shrugged while looking at each other and then moved their caravan towards the city, there was the problem with that upstart clan, but they thought that they wouldn't try to pull something in the city, there were other clans in there and there were laws. Plus that was probably why they tried to extort them outside, the woman gave the order out to move on while reminiscing about the cultivator in white, he sure was a handsome man a shame that he left she thought to herself while smiling.

Matt wooshed towards the city, seeing it on the horizon as he wasn't far away. He could see the various Oriental styled buildings and structures, it was surrounded by a big wall. There were four big gates coming from each side of the city and he could see a castle structure in there as well and the streets were looking busy. He remembered that there was a toll to pay before one was let into the city, so being the law-abiding citizen that he was he slowly descended from his position to what looked like a big line of carts and people that was slowly moving in and out of the city.

"Damn, that's a big line... "

He was hovering low enough to catch the attention of the people below him, they all looked up at the cultivator and wondered why he was there and staring at them. Matt didn't know that if you had a certain standing in this world you could cut in line, being powerful had its perks in this world. The people started whispering while Zhang Dong was feeling awkward once more from getting so much attention, but he was slowly getting used to the attention but it was slow progress.

"Hey look, mommy, a man standing on a sword!"

"Is that a cultivator? Why is he just standing there, does he want something from someone?"

"Hey, doesn't he look kind of nice?"

"A powerful Senior has appeared!"

He was making a commotion that alerted the guards that also looked in the direction, seeing a large man on a sword. They brought up some jade slips that were used for communication by cultivators and alerted the people in the city about an unknown cultivator in white, who was flying on a sword and in front of the west gate to the city. It didn't take long for some cultivators in the later stages of Foundation Establishment to appear. They tried measuring the man's power level, but they couldn't get a read on him, it looked that he was stronger than them.

Matt was wondering if he should just move into the city instead, the people were making room for him as he tried to approach the line, parting like the red sea as they thought that he wanted through. He ended up by the gate soon while the people were still looking at him with curiosity. The experts from the city came out to greet him in front of the gate, greeted him by clasping their hands which Matt mirrored while hopping down from his sword.

"Greeting Senior, what brings you to Moonlight City?"

They asked while being polite, the cultivator's face twitched a bit as he looked at everyone making a big fuss. He really wasn't used to this rock-star treatment, everyone calling him senior this, senior that.

"Ah yes, I heard that you needed to pay the toll to enter the city? I just came to sell some things at the auction house."

The city cultivators looked at each other then back at the cultivator in white who didn't seem to know that people at his level didn't need to pay anything.

"You don't need to pay the toll Senior, you can just come into the city, here we will guide you inside."

He felt stupid now, and just followed the people that beckoned him inside, there were three cultivators and they all looked to be in their 50s a bit old but not too old. They explained to him that the city requires the common people to pay the entrance fee but strong people like him or from powerful families didn't have to, it was more to keep the riff-raff out. He asked them about the auction house and a place to stay, they saw that this cultivator was a bit quirky but he felt uninterested in causing a ruckus. They guided him to the best hotel in the city and informed him about some locations in it before parting ways and reporting to other people in the city.

He couldn't even tell them his name before they left, but the way the clan people that he was harassing the caravan were speaking he left that he should wait and get more information before he revealed that he was from the Zhang clan. It supposedly ruled this city as well before something happened, maybe he could get some info on that.

He found himself in a big room, it looked quite costly. The door closed behind him while a serving lady took her to leave after guiding him to one of the more costly hotel rooms.

*I have to stop doing this, can't keep others just lead me around at their pace, I'm supposed to be some battle-hardened warrior.*

He wallowed a bit in self-pity as he should learn to say no, at least he had a free room and boarding now, guess it paid off to be a top cultivator.

*Though I also could learn a thing or two from those people, might have to act like that if a scary cultivator appears with a higher cultivation level.*

He flopped on the soft bed that as a lot better than the one he had stashed in his storage ring, his next step would be to sell the things he made, he needed to know if he could earn Spirit points with crafting and if he did, how lucrative it would be.

Chapter 34

He placed all of the items that he wanted to sell on the floor, they included the 9 mortal high-grade weapons as well as the perfect grade one. He also had the crimson common grade items out, he didn't want to sell the beast cores, for now, he might as well ask for the going price for those later at the store himself. There were various shapes and sizes, war hammers, swords, axes, and even a bow. He wasn't sure how much he could get for them at the moment but he hoped that he could make some money, if he could then he would have a nice money and point-making option for himself instead of just murdering monsters or other cultivators, the later one he wasn't that keen on doing at all.

Zhang Dong had a big window in his hotel room, it was a really tall building and he was occupying one of the topmost floors. He could see down on the bustling streets, there were people coming and going just doing their thing. He still didn't really know what to do with himself, should he really go to Spirit Spring City, would he fit in there? After giving out a big sigh he flopped back on the king-sized bed and looked at the ceiling, that had some dragon engravings on them. The whole room looked extravagant he wouldn't be able to afford a lushes room like this in his previous life but here he could just flex his cultivation muscles and people came on running. He didn't really care about luxurious lifestyles all that much, but he wasn't against it either.

He stared at the ceiling for quite some time before moving his lazy ass off the bed, he would also need to do something about not being motivated enough. First came the auction house, then maybe he could gather some info about his so-called downtrodden Clan that fled the city for some reason.

*I bet this place has some relaxing hot springs as well.*

He kind of started liking the warm spring feeling that this culture had to offer, but he still could go for a normal shower. He paced up his things, looked at his robe in the mirror and decided to head out it was the middle of the day so he might tour the city for a bit before the auction house opened, it was in the pleasure district apparently and it only opened at night for some reason. So he headed out, trying to not stand out but his clothing was kind of giving him away as it was kind of exquisite, he started thinking that it might be a good idea to get himself a new robe, he could probably make one himself but he would have to use that dreaded DDR game again.

While our hero was trying to not stick out like a sore thumb within the masses the caravan with the lovely lady that had the peaks that men desired arrived by the gate. They managed to get through it without much trouble and paid the normal toll of 10 low grade spirit stones. The members were relieved that nothing else happened on the way as they headed into the city to unload their gear. This caravan wasn't a single unit, they hired guards from guilds that were in the city while having some of their own more trusted people with them as well. They were also carrying letters, people and other various things that they could earn money with. They started unloading their cargo and got busy with work, their purpose was profit they just as Zhang D. came here to sell items at the auction and the market, they had some low grade treasures ranging from common to mortal grades but mostly on the lower levels.

The guards surrounded Lan Fei as they went around unpacking things, she was the leading merchant of the group so everything went through her. They didn't think anything would happen in the city but they didn't want to repeat what happened previously, the strange cultivator probably wouldn't help them if they got into trouble once again.

"This place was a lot safer when the Zhang Clan was running things, merchants weren't getting robbed in broad daylight like this."

"Shhh, Miss Fei you shouldn't be talking like that, what if they hear you."

The oldest guard said to the woman, he looked to be the oldest from the bunch and was the most trusted soldier from the bunch that this woman had. She belonged to a long line of merchants, she had been the leader of this caravan for a couple of years now and was slowly making a name for herself as this wasn't the first time she was in this city. She reluctantly nodded at the man that she knew was right, those type of people she was going against were the petty type and their reputation was more important to them than the lives of others.

"Yes, you're right, let us just unpack and transport everything to the auction house, but be careful the pleasure district is a shady place. We have to watch our backs"

She said while wrapping her form in a loose robe, she didn't like it but she knew that women tended to be singled out around places like that. She would have to be careful, she thought that it was a shame that the world was like this but this was the reality. The people were rotten and everyone had to fend for themselves, the person that helped them today was the oddball out. She thought about the man once more but then shook her head, It would be nice to have him around as a bodyguard but that was a pipe dream.

Fei got her head back into it and started going through her inventory, checking if anything got stolen or damaged. She had to inspect everything they wanted to sell before giving it to the buyers, her good name depended on good quality merchandise. This would take a while but they still had time before the auction house opened up.

So time passed and nothing major happened, she and her men started gathering all of the items that they wanted to sell and headed off to the auction house. Little did they know that after they left a familiar figure walked out, it was one of the men from the Cheng Clan he was looking in the direction that the people left while grinning. He left after a moment and went to inform some other members that the caravan people were on the move. They had done their research on these people and knew that they didn't have any strong backing, they were just regular merchants, the female's father was in the foundation establishment-level but he was just one man and didn't have many warriors behind him. The Cheng Clan had nothing to fear, they wouldn't kill them, they just wanted to show what happened to people that go against their clan. This was the early stage of their Clans rise to power, they were still under a stronger clan that could replace them with another family, so they wanted to prove themselves as well.

They were planing some fun after the Auction ended, they had their people on the inside so they would get the girly and her men into a separate area and give them a good thrashing. Their elder showed interest in the woman before, he wanted to have a good time as well. They had everything planned out, they also knew that the cultivator that came to the rescue of those people wasn't associated with them and entered the city earlier. They thought that they might have overreacted a bit when they first saw him, and it was them that offered him that hotel room as well, though they weren't brave enough to keep tabs on him as they knew that he would probably know if someone followed him around.

While this was happening, Matt was munching on some dumplings. The food was still new to him, he was sitting in some high class restaurant after he pulled out a gold coin the people in the establishment looked at him with sparkling eyes and gave him the royal treatment so he was enjoying some nice food and drinks while watching the city from a window by the table he was sitting in.

*This kind of life isn't that bad.*

Chapter 35

The meat buns were devoured while he asked for more, the waitress returned with a smile with another plate while Zhang Dong munched away. Having cash on yourself was a nice feeling as in his previous life he mostly survived on cooking himself some noodles and chicken here and there. Plus the frozen dinners if he didn't feel like doing much, but this food was really good even though he didn't really know what the meat in there was. He burped into his hand while hoping that no one heard, then rubbed his belly that didn't seem to expand that much.

*Hm, where did all of that food go. Well, I guess no more Mr. skinny fat in the future.*

He paid for the food with the gold coin, but this time around he got the change back, leave it to a big restaurant to have enough cash. He smiled at the waitress before going out, resulting in blush from her in response. He wasn't quite used to his good looks and didn't really know that you could use that for benefits.

*Okay, I still have some time to burn before the auction house opens, though I need to get there a bit sooner than the others as the sellers need to present their items for inspection first.*

He headed out into the city in the form of a tourist, looking left and right while at least trying not to look weird while doing it. People were giving him strange looks here and there, girls kept turning their heads while the men squinted their eyes at him. He wasn't using his cultivation at this moment, so others didn't regard him as a lofty senior but just as some good looking guy walking about. He was a bit flattered at the response he was getting from the ladies, but he wasn't here to pick up girls that much but to tour the place instead.

He visited a bathhouse as well, paying for the more exclusive one as he kind of got into the big spender mindset. There weren't many people around here at this time, so he could enjoy the large bath on his own. Dipping his large frame into the water after washing up and looking up at the ceiling while relaxing, taking baths instead of showers might have not been such a bad thing after all. He stayed there for about 30 minutes and ended the experience with a nice full glass of milk, a big mustache left on his upper lip in the process. He smiled at some kids that pointed that out and then headed back out into the city, the day looked nice and it would probably be a nice day, he felt it. Of course, he felt it wrong as after stepping out of the bath building he heard some people screaming.

There was a dirt road right outside, it was a bit narrow so you had to watch your step as there were horse carriage vehicles going back and forth which didn't leave much space for the pedestrians. They were pulled by various creatures, there were regular looking horses here and there but you could also see things like tigers or huge wolves doing the pulling. A commotion was happening about now as you could see people running to the sides of the buildings and off the road to safety. In the distance you could see two carriages speeding side by side while getting pulled by beasts, one was a big tiger while the other looked like a big hyena. You could see people on those carriages shouting at each other while smiling and smirking, having some bottles in their hands, they were clearly drinking.

They appeared a bit away from where Matt as at, he had some time to get a good look at them. They looked like some older teens having some kind of race while drinking booze. The people bolted to the sides while trying not to get run over while others pushed their carts to the side to make way for the rowdy youths behind them. They were probably some young masters doing silkypants stuff as always, guess no place was safe from those Zhang Dong thought to himself as they even had one way back in that tribe he visited. He didn't intend to do anything about it, the people looked like they were going out of the way and he already caused a big commotion when he was entering the city he didn't need people gawking at him even more than they already were.

Though fate had different things in store for him as the most common thing happened in this situation. A child at around 4 years of age tripped, fell and started crying while the mother was trying to pull that child and some other kids to the side. Of course, she pushed the two kids to the wall and then started quickly running back to get her last child back that was rolling on the road crying her little heart out. But the woman was just a regular person, so she wasn't very fast so at the moment that she was picking up her fallen offspring the people riding the monster-drawn wheeled vehicles arrived at the spot. She couldn't do much besides grabbing the child and trying to shield her with her whole body, hoping for the best while apologizing for getting them in this predicament.

Matt's face fell as he saw everything playing out, most people turned their faces to the side as they didn't want to see the daughter and mother pair to get smashed to pieces. He almost forgot what sort of world this was, people beneath a certain degree of power were worth less than dirt to those lofty young lords and clan members. They didn't have any problem in running over a mother and child in broad daylight. It's not that the people didn't care but they couldn't do anything in the face of real power. The people on the top tended to remain there and if you didn't have the tendency for slaughter you mostly didn't get far either. He didn't like that ... he didn't like that one bit...

People looked on in horror as the saw the two beasts run towards the defenseless woman and her child, they knew who the people in the carriages were. They were some Cheng clan members, of course, some from the younger generation. They moved along the city as they owned the place now, it was pretty chaotic the previous clan that was keeping the peace wasn't like that. But they couldn't do anything about it, they gritted their teeth as they looked at the poor woman. Suddenly something happened, they could feel a huge aura sweep over the place and a strange cultivator appeared right where the woman was standing. He waved his hands in a strange way and a strange translucid shield appeared in front of him and the woman. The shield was sparkling with lightning energy and looked deadly to the touch.

The two beasts felt the suppressing defensive ability in front of them but they couldn't stop, the shield wasn't wide so they tried to dodge to the side but they still ended up hitting it. The monsters got shocked and bounced off to the side while the carriages got propelled into Zhang Dong's forcefield ability the people on them looked in horror as they slammed into the sparkling wall which was placed at an angle so the carriage flew upwards while spinning and crashed on its top end. They both landed in a similar fashion with the bests getting yanked over as well.

The Cheng clan members were scattered on the ground but there were still some of them on the inside of the carriage. No one got really hurt though, all these people were cultivators and they could take some hit and this was just a regular vehicle crash. Two youths climbed out of each carriage along with some other men, they were the main silkypants and had their guards in the carriages along with them.

"Who dares! I am Cheng Tong, I'm the third son of the Cheng Clan head, I will have your head!"

One of the youth's barked out while looking around, his hair and robe in disarray as he got thrown about in his carriage like a rag doll.

"Ye, we are from the Cheng Clan, we rule this city!"

The other youth from the other vehicle spoke up, probably also a son from the same family.

At this moment a big vein appeared on Matt's forehead, this was the most stereotypical situation he could find himself in, saving people from some stupid snotty silver spoon-fed kid.

"Oh, you want my head?"

The two youths and their guards that were helping them up looked in the direction of the voice and could see a mad looking Zhang Dong. Energy was exuding from his body at this moment and his eyes began to glow. He took one step forward and his whole body was covered by a sheet of lightning energy. The Cheng clan people took a step back as they felt the oppressing aura, they gulped as the lightning clad cultivator took steps towards them. With each step he kept on growing, after two he was 4 meters tall and crackling with energy. Two more steps and he was 8 meters tall and after a final one, he was 10. He looked down at the bewildered Cheng Clan members that were directly below him now with a frown on his face.

"So, come on up here and take my head."

Chapter 36

You could hear a pin drop as everyone was looking at the scene, the Cheng clan members were really tense as they could feel huge cultivation fluctuations from this person. He was in a giant lightning form, looking down at them like ants and they were worried that they would be crushed to death. The silkypants squad had personal guards at the Foundation Establishment level but they knew that this senior was at the Core Formation stage, plus it wasn't any regular stage, it felt like he was in the late or great circle stage. They used their jade slips to send for backup but they knew that they were in deep shit as they didn't even have anyone in the core formation stage in their clan, the patriarch was a great circle of foundation establishment.

"Honorable Senior, please appease your anger they were just kids from the junior generation they didn't mean anything bad!"

The guards of the young masters moved in trying to diffuse the situation, clasping their hands and bowing back and forth while trying to get the young brats that caused this mess to apologize. Cheng Tong wasn't that stupid, even though you might think otherwise. He knew well that he would be royally fucked if this cultivator decided to give them a beating and his parents wouldn't be able to do anything. Even if they asked a stronger clan for help they probably would decline as well. So he dropped down to his knees and started apologizing as well.

"Senior, forgive this silly Junior, I didn't realize that you were passing the street. Forgive my lapse of judgment"

Matt looked down at the kowtowing bunch getting even more mad as these people were quick to submit to a higher power while ignoring anyone below them and treating them like dirt. He made his best haughty cultivator impression and snorted loudly, his size amplifying the effect as the Cheng people trembled in their boots.

"I'm not the one you are supposed to apologize. Apologize to them!"

Zhang D. Turned to the side, his big frame having an increased weight to it as well which made his feet thump against the ground. Behind him was the child and mother duo, still trembling in the same spot not really knowing what was happening. His large finger pointed to the trembling couple that looked up at the lightning infused avatar form that the cultivator was in, which made her almost pass out on the spot.

"If I didn't step in you would have crushed this poor mother and her child, do you have no respect for life at all?"

They were making a huge scene in the large city, the Cheng clan lord was on his way as well as he got notified about the fiasco that one of his sons had created, he just wanted to give that no good son of his a beating. By the time he got there, he could see his offspring bowing his head to some woman holding her child that looked bewildered, to say the least. The problem wasn't that though, it was the 10-meter tall lightning giant standing next to that with his hands crossed over his chest in an intimidating fashion while looking at his son. He didn't know what was going on but he knew about the crash that his son had caused. He appeared in the street and tried to get Zhang Dong's attention.

"Greetings honorable Senior, I apologize for my son's behavior, please appease your anger."

Matt looked at the man that appeared, he looked to be in his 50's and was a bit on the chubby side. He gave him a glare which made the Cheng clan patriarch shiver as he felt the other cultivators overpowering presence wash over him.

"You should teach your kid how to behave in public if you are in a leadership position."

He didn't want to be making a scene but these people started to piss him off with their outdated mindset. He started shrinking as he went back to his regular appearance, the mother gave him a big bow before moving back to where her other children were and backed away. She was just glad that she was alive and that her children didn't need to live without a mother. The Cheng clan members started gathering together as the stronger elders came on over, they didn't know if they would have to fight this person or not but he seemed to have calmed down for now.

"Thank you for being so magnanimous Senior, I'll be sure to discipline my son and his friends! Also, I'm the city lord so if you have anything you want you only need to ask."

Matt looked at the man that was clasping his hands together while hunched over a bit, he looked like a sleazy merchant more than a Clan leader at the moment. He wanted to be done with the lot and just harumphed like a proper mad expert and removed himself from the vicinity while the Cheng clan members looked at him with fear. After he was gone people started whispering while the Cheng Patriarch showed an angry expression. He gave his son a thwack on the head while barking out at the people around.

"What are you lot looking at, be gone!"

He released his cultivation making the people disperse in fear. Then he told his people to gather all they could find about this unknown cultivator, he had to know if he came from some big sect or clan, or if he was some solo cultivator instead.

"You idiot, I told you to do your stupid stunts where people can't see you, why did you have to do this stupid thing in public."

He hit his son one more time, a big lump appeared on his head, he then told him to go back home and not come back until all of this blew over. This strange senior had some weird thing about protecting other people. He didn't get the info about his clan member's collecting toll outside the city as they did that stuff on their own, otherwise, he would have probably forbidden them to go through with what they were now planing. He ordered everyone to conduct themselves with care around the cultivator dressed in white and then left.

At this time Matt was in a secluded alley grasping his chest as his heart was pounding a bit, he managed to stay composed while showing off his cultivation but he still wasn't used to acting like that.

"Well, at least I didn't pussy out totally this time around... think I'm making progress, but still I don't think this will fix the problem..."

He knew that this wouldn't really fix the problem in the city, he knew that if he wanted them to listen he would need to force them to do it. But he wasn't ready to go on a rampage in this city, so the most he could do was to intimidate the people under the guise of an irritated senior cultivator.

He gave out a sigh and then moved out of the alley, he moved towards the auction house in the pleasure district while it was getting late in the day hoping that he could get past that without any problems popping out.

"Knowing my luck I'll run into some slave princess that will want me to save her country or something."

He hurried up taking big strides and after some time arrived in the district, there were many colorful buildings in this place. There were restaurants, theaters, and casinos but also other more raunchy places this was kind of where the seedy people liked to hang out and make money. He could see some food stands and some ladies in provocative outfits standing around trying to invite customers to their establishments, one even tried to invite him in as well but after he gave her his deadpan look she backed away.

Our cultivator had no courage at all to go into one of these places at all, even though he kind of wanted to but he found himself frozen while looking at one of the establishments.

*No... I have to be strong... a gentleman doesn't need to use those sorts of places... I should go to that auction house and sell those items... then just go to bed, starting to feel tired...*

He strode off to the auction house, passing many people before arriving in front of a big building that had a big red tiger above the entrance. This must be the one that the busty cultivator lady was talking about, this made him recall those massive pillows that she had.

*Okay focus, selling first.*

He shook his head and moved up to the entrance where he got stopped by some guards, they asked him about the reason he was here. They told him where he should go if he wanted to sell after letting him come inside. He stepped up to a lady behind a counter and told her that he intended to sell some weapons and that he heard that you had to give the weapons up for inspection.

"Ah yes, sir, what kind of weapons are they?"

The woman asked while fixing her glasses a bit, she looked like the librarian type.

"Ah yes, some perfect grade common weapons and some high grade mortal weapons, plus one perfect grade mortal weapon."

The woman didn't react when he mentioned the common weapons, but she perked up after he mentioned the high grade weapons, even more after he said that he even had a perfect grade one.

"Also I have a core formation beast core, could I get it appraised? Not sure if I want to sell it."

The woman opened her eyes wide and stood up, she bowed to Matt while telling him that she needed to get a more senior clerk and appriser. After a few minutes, he was lead to a room in the back to get his items checked, the people gave him thumbs up on all the weapons their eyes sparkling a bit at the high grade and perfect grade mortal weapons that were a weapon that a Foundation Establishment cultivator could use well. Matt then brought up the tennis ball-sized core that gave off a faint eerie light and set it on the table, the appriser was an old man with a monocle that moved in close and started examining the item.

"This is indeed a core formation beast core, where did you find this?"

The man asked while looking at it.

"Find it? Oh, I just slew a core formation beast and that's what was left from it."

The appriser was a bit astonished at the cultivator's words, but if he beat the beast that he had to be quite strong.

"You should be able to get about 1 thousand low tier spirit stones for this core, or 1 middle-tier spirit stone."

A note from Kuropon

I'll probably be slowing down with the chapters a bit, have been writing a lot lately need to chill out a bit.

Chapter 37

He took the orb back from the old looking man and placed it back into his storage room. The appriser squinted his eyes as he saw that, he could tell that the cultivator used a storage ring. He did some mental calculations and counted that the core would give him about 10k points if he traded it for spirit stones, would it give him more if he absorbed it instead of the spirit stones? He wasn't so sure about that.

The two people inside the room looked at the man that made the core vanish and figured that they should probably alert the auction house owner. If this person can really beat a beast at the core formation stage it would put him at the top end of experts in this city, that might have not even had one present in it at the moment.

"Ah Senior, let us take care of your items for you, also we can offer you a booth to watch how the auction is going if you so wish."

"Mmh, sure a booth would be nice. I also have a question, do you perhaps have something that writes down the going prices for various weapons and items? Ah, and do you have prices for resources like metals?"

Matt asked, he wanted to know the going rates for the things he could sell along with the resources, he wished to calculate if it would be better to buy crafting resources from the people instead of doing it in the cash shop where he needed to spend the spirit points. He wasn't sure if the auction had any of those around or if they would even hand him something like that.

The female clerk and the appraiser looked at each other, those were trade secrets that they had but they just couldn't hand over the going prices for items that they are selling as that would probably lower the profit margin if people knew the exact price a given item was worth.

"Uh, we'll have to ask the owner about that, we're not in the position if giving those pieces of information away Senior..."

"Ah sure, go ahead I'll just wait in that booth, don't really have anything to do at the moment either.

He nodded while the lady guided him to his VIP booth that would let him see down into the auction house. The auction house looked a bit like an old-timey theater with these booths being elevated over the chairs and stage. They had red-drapes and comfy chairs, he was even brought something to drink which was wine. He gave it a sip, it was quite tasty so he drank the whole glass quite fast while looking down below at the gathering people.

*Well, I guess they need to gather all those items together, that might take some time.*

About at this time, the appraiser was talking with the auction house owner, which was an older cultivator lady. She looked like a nice grandma on the first look but she had a glint in her eye. She listened to the worker who recapped the appearance of the person that brought in the high quality good that was the core formation beast core.

"So, did he look like someone we should be cautious off, could you get a read on his cultivation level?"

She asked her worker.

"No Madam Wong, I couldn't detect any cultivation fluctuations he must be quite powerful to be able to hide his aura so well, or he could have a treasure on him. He looks like a fairly well off master, the robes that he was wearing are fit for a core formation expert also he had a high grade storage ring as well, not one of those knockoff ones that have barely any space to store a sword in them."

The woman rubbed her chin while leaning back in her chair, they were in her office and there was a big double-sided glass window behind her, she could see the auction house and all the people below. She glanced at the spot Matt was sitting in and saw the good looking cultivator that was gulping down the free wine they offered to their customers. The moment she looked at him, he could sense that someone was looking at him. There was a big tinted window there, he could kind of tell that there was someone behind there, thanks to his heightened senses.

Madam Wong felt the gaze of the man on her, their eyes met. He didn't show much of expression and was just looking, but she felt cold sweat run down her back. The man was able to notice that she was looking at him, she had various levels of magic treasures blocking the view inside the room and no one should be able to know that she was in here. Also while Zhang Dong was focusing on the old lady he gave off a hint of his real cultivation base. She turned around and looked at her appriser that was wondering if something was wrong, the woman looked pale now.

"Give the Senior what he wants, don't offend him!"

The man nodded while being slightly perplexed but he wasn't one to ask questions. He got out and gathered the jade slips that had the numbers of the items that were sold there. There had even compiled them to show an average price if he was interested in them along with items that cultivators used for pill making, crafting like metals and other various things. He handed it to a waitress lady to deliver to the cultivator, they should have asked him about his name as he didn't introduce himself, he thought.

Matt stopped staring at the auction house glass panel, moving his head to the side to focus his gaze on the people in the auction house. After a moment he got the jade slip with the information. The serving lady bowed at him before stepping out letting him examine the jade slip in question.

*Oh, it's a jade slip. Cultivators use those for storing information or as phones if I remember correctly. I'm supposed to put my spiritual energy into it to get the information out, let's see...*

Matt concentrated and his spiritual energy entered the jade scroll looking item, the databank of the sold items quickly rushed into his head as he did that, giving him a little scare. It was a bit different than the thing the system did with the information injection, the information was there but it didn't force its way into his brain, he could slowly digest it bit by bit. Guess that was a plus and minus to that, as it wasn't painful but slower. For the time being, he decided to look at the prices in there and compare them to the store prices to see if he could make a profit later on, he still had some time but people were gathering in the auction house and more seats were getting filled up.

First, he looked at the mortal grade weapons, he found out that he would probably lose out if he ever tried making low grade or middle grade weapons while buying resources in the store. Maybe break even with the middle-grade ones, but the rewards varied depending on how many people were buying. The high grade ones would give him an up to a 50% profit. So if he spent 1000 SP to make one high grade item, he would earn up to about 150 spirit stones that would net him about 1500 SP in return. 1 Spirit stone didn't always give him 10 SP in return the giveback varied as well. Then came the perfect weapons those would give him the biggest profit margin, something between 300 - 600 spirit stones, but he needed to use beast cores for those, if he subtracted the core cost then he would gain about 2k spirit points from those and 500 spirit points from the high grade ones.

*So I can profit, but I guess hunting beasts might be a bit faster, I gain a lot more for foundation establishment beasts, plus the cores will be free then. But still a good way to earn something on the side. I wonder if I make too many weapons if I'll destroy the balance on the market and the prices will go down, maybe I shouldn't overdo that. I could also do it wholesale or trade with some clans that have a lot of spirit stones...*

Time past while Zhang Dong was doing quick mental maths with the jade slip in hand, the auction was about to start and the night was coming, the city lit up with various colored lights. Nighttime came and the pleasure district got busy, for some people this was the real start of the day.

Chapter 38

While Matt was up alone in his VIP room, trying to math away while scanning the jade slip the auction was about to start. The seats were quickly getting filled out but not like there wasn't enough space for everyone. There were not super rare treasures coming in, so it would just be a normal day like the rest for the people inside.

Zhang Dong stopped calculating his potential gains and perked up. He looked down at the people sitting down, they all were in robes and were all wearing those oriental style robes. Though their appearance didn't fit the culture as there were various types of people around if you compared them to earthlings. Black, white they all kind of mixed together a bit guess this world was very racially mixed. He didn't know if all countries were like this, or if this empire was a rarity. The people also had various hair and eye colors, with colors like purple and even green here and there. Giving everyone a more fantasy-like appearance.

He also noticed someone familiar and jiggly sitting in one of the chairs of the auction house. It was the woman that he saved just before arriving in this city. He remembered that they did indeed have a caravan so they probably were coming to this city to trade and auction their items. He coughed into his hand and moved back into his room a bit, not really wanting to stare too much as he already did.

*I got to get used to women too... why do they have to be so ... bouncy.*

He gulped while leaning back in his chair and taking another sip from his wine, his focus then turned to the stage where another lovely lady appeared. She had an hourglass figure and you could see her long legs sticking out from her blue dress.

"I am your humble servant Fan Ru, I welcome you all to the Red Tiger auction house fellow Daoists. The rules are the same as always, the highest bidder wins."

She clasped her hands and gave out a little bow and also a wink to the audience, probably making some of the men's hears flutter in response. After she clasped her hands the curtain on the stage got raised and you could see a pedestal with an item on it, it looked to be some types of pills that were in a small bottle.

"The first item is a bottle with 10 Qi Replenishing pills, suited for cultivators of the Qi Condensation stage. Let me remind you that every item in the auction house can only be traded with the use of spirit stones."

The bidding started as some people started raising their hands, the bottle didn't go for much as it was just for the Qi condensation stage cultivators. He could see people raising their hands in the air and shouting out the prices out loudly, this was the first time he had been at an auction house so it was a new fascinating experience.

"Going once, going twice, going thrice! Sold. Fellow Daoist in the blue robe, please behind the stage with the agreed amount of spirit stones to receive your item, or you can wait till the auction is over to do so as well."

The lady said while the item was removed another one was placed in its stead. It took some time for the bidders to examine the item, the lady also described what it did and tired giving a short explanation to up its sell value, the auction house did earn a small percentage from selling the items, so it was in their best interest to have them sold. The items were sold in sequence, from the lowest grade to the highest grade. You could even see some people coming in later as they weren't interested in the cheap stuff. Finally, the time to sell his crimson perfect grade common items came and they were laid out on the pedestal.

"These are all common perfect grade weapons, they have all been strengthened by beast cores and are suited for cultivators of the fire attribute."

Matt perked up at the explanation as he knew that the cores added some attributes but he wasn't quite sure what they changed in the weapons and now he knew. He kind of randomly added cores while crafting to see if something worked or not, he'd have to examine the things he made more throughout the next time around or just write down the effects by trial and error. He also brought out a dagger that he previously created, but his appraisal skill only told him that it was a high grade dagger. There was something about the appraisal skill being an evolving type, so after checking that he kind of hit his head, he could spend his points to upgrade the skill. Maybe if he increased it enough he could see more stats on the items. He would remember to check this out the next time he crafted something as he didn't want to do it around here just yet.

The Spear, two-handed Hammer, Greatsword, Axe and a Jian Sword that he made didn't sell for much he got about 20 spirit stones for the five, so 4 a pop but they were kind of easy to make and the resources were just regular metals and Qi condensation cores... but he would have to make big amounts of those while spending the exact time creating mortal weapons instead.

After those items were sold to someone they started bringing out items fitting for Foundation Establishment cultivators, the items he made were all high grade so they would probably only come out at the end. So more time passed while Zhang Dong looked out from his booth at the auction house, he didn't want to buy anything as he didn't know what was useful or not. The items ranged from beast cores, weapons to just regular looking plants but they were called mystical herbs. Finally, after an hour had passed one of his high grade weapons appeared out in the open, the cultivators looked at it with greedy eyes as high grade weapons were quite popular among the foundation establishment Daoists. He rubbed his chin and looked down as the people started raising their hands and the bidding wars started. The first weapon was a nice sharp looking spear.

"80 Spirit Stones! ... 100 Spirit Stones ... 140 Spirit stones ... 145...!"

"Sold for 145 Spirit stones to the Daoist in the green robe."

The weapons appeared one after another and all the bidding kind of ranges from 120 - 150 spirit stones, the least popular weapon was the bow, maybe because it didn't come with any arrows and it sold for 120 spirit stones. He still counted it up, 9 weapons the gains 120 - 150, so that would put it at 1080 - 1350 Spirit stones. So he lost 1000 points for the resources and sold it for 120 - 150 spirit stones, he would gain 200 - 500 points for the items, which was good or not? He did gain spirit points for just playing a game it was worth it, but he should make weapons that were more popular. Afterward, the perfect graded weapon appeared, it was a silvery looking spear, he made it with the monster rabbits core and thought a spear would fit the core as the rabbit used a horn to penetrate people.

"This is a fine perfect grade spear, it has enhanced penetrating power and works well with earth Qi."

The bidding started but it was much higher as they started out at 250 spirit stones right from the start, which was already a 100 more than for what he sold his best high grade weapon. The rowdy Daoists shouted out numbers after numbers and the price ended at 550 spirit stones. Which would net him quite a bit for just one item, considering the manufacturing cost. He would have to check the core prices to see how much he would lose if he bought a core from the cash store.

Some other items came out, but nothing above the foundation establishment level. He just waited around looking at the stuff that got sold, wondering if he should invest in some recovery items after he gets his spirit stones. He would gain something around 9 or 8 thousand points if he converted everything to spirit stones, which wasn't that bad as a start.

"Not bad, I will have to check out what I need for crafting and see if I can buy it around town, maybe I can earn more like that."

Though the process of making the weapons then going to the auction house himself was a bit tedious, if he compared it to flying around the forest and trying to find monsters to hunt it might be a bit better. But he could also use the monster parts for crafting as well, so hunting as also handy. For the time being, he decided to head out and get his stones, then head back to his hotel and rest for the night. The people were leaving as well and he couldn't see the woman from earlier around, they all must have gone to pick up their money as well.

Chapter 39

'Fifteen minutes earlier.'

Lan Fei looked on as the last item that she brought out was sold, she also was part of the bidding wars getting a couple of items that she thought she could sell for more in another city further along. She knew the amount that she could spend and wasn't wealthy enough to go for the high grade items so that was more or less it for her in here. She didn't really care about the high grade weapons that were brought out and were getting bid on now.

*Okay, guess it's time to gather up the merchandise and leave this city, I'm having a bad feeling about this place.*

She thought to herself, there was also apparently some commotion on the streets with some cultivators offending some big shot. It was apparently the Cheng Clan which made the woman feel a bit better, though apparently he didn't really trash any of them too much just some young masters getting a schooling and nothing much besides that.

*Heh, guess if you got power you don't really care about the little people beneath you that much.*

She had two warriors on each side where she was sitting, she gave them a signal to move out it was time to get the money and the items and then return to the caravan. They would stay the night and then go early in the morning, there was no reason to remain here plus the clan in here was kind of sketchy. She didn't want to end up with having to bribe them and lose most or all of their profit.

"Okay men, time to head out, let's wrap this up."

"Yes, Lady Fei."

Both of the men nodded and got out of their seats, they remained a step behind the lovely lady while keeping guard. They eyed the other patrons menacingly as they knew that their lady tended to attract men a bit much. But she also was quite good at mediating and talking her way out of situations, most people were more or less reasonable. But there also were people like the men they met today before the city, those were hard to reason with as they were drunk on newly gained power.

They exited the main auction hall, people were still going in and out of it. The walked over to one of the workers and gave their information so that they could get their items and spirit stones. The auction house gave special numbered tokens to the sellers and buyers to identify everything later. The worker took out a jade slip and searched for the number, his eye twitching a bit as there was something else in the jade slip that looked unusual, it had something to do with you know what clan.

"Miss Lan Fei is it?"

He asked while the woman nodded and confirmed her identity. He kind of knew that this wasn't anything good, it said that if any of the workers in the auction house come across Lan Fei they should guide her to a certain area in the back of the building without asking any questions. Plus anyone not following this order would be severely punished if they ever found out that they ignored it.

"Ah yes, this way please I'll guide you."

They didn't see much out of the ordinary as they were guided to the back. This wasn't the first time that the people were in this particular auction house so as they walked they noticed that there weren't being lead to the usual room, it was further in the back where the auction house invited the more important guests. This was a red flag, but maybe there wasn't space in the regular rooms? Did someone important want to make a lucrative deal with them? They didn't know but Lan Fei looked at her men and nodded making a decision to take the risk. They could see some guards placed along the way but that was normal, an auction house had to have protection.

They walked into a dimly lit room and there was someone sitting with the back to them, the person that guided them inside quickly made his way out as he didn't want to stay here any longer than he had too.

"I have guided the guest in, I'll take my leave now."

The woman and the guards looked behind them as the door was shut and two people stood by it now, the light was turned on and the person that was looking like a James bond villain turned around to reveal himself. It was, of course, the previous foundation establishment elder that tried to extort them and his cronies. He smirked while more people from the Cheng clan came out, they quickly grabbed the two accompanying warriors that Lan Fei came with and pulled them away while they were thrashing about.

"Well, if it isn't the lovely caravan owner, I'm glad that we could see each other again~"

He said while grinning side to side in his chair.

"What's the meaning of this, the auction house is supposed to be a neutral area why are you causing trouble. Do you think Madam Wong will just take this, she has connections as well, the Cheng Clan is overstepping their boundaries!"

The woman shouted at the man while backing away but her men were getting restrained and the door was blocked off by some Cheng clan members.

"Madam Wong? That old crow? She doesn't need to know anything, I made arrangments so that we wouldn't be interrupted. Plus why would that old crow even lift a finger to defend some random merchant lass? If the news doesn't come out, she won't do a thing, he he he. This place is sealed and soundproof, I pulled some strings to get you here no one will bother us. This is a special room, only big shots can come in here, you should be honored that I spent so many resources to arrange this."

The man licked his lips while standing up, his aura radiating in the room as it forced the woman down to her knees from the increased pressure.

"Why are you doing this..."

She asked while an angry look in her eyes, she didn't show fear as she knew that would probably be something that this perverted old man would get off on."

"Why am I doing this? Because of you, I lost face due to that weird cultivator, made me look weak and pathetic. No one can embarrass members of the Cheng clan!"

He said while moving closer and closer, his hand moving to grasp the woman's chin and forcing her to look up to him.

"So, you're too afraid to confront that Senior so you've picked me instead, how pathetic."

She replied while spitting right in the elder man's face, the man getting surprised as the spit landed on his cheek. His face turned red and he delivered a slap to Lan Fei's face making her bleed and fall down to the floor.

"You damn slut, after I'm through with you even your own mother won't recognize you!"

He grasped her long hair that was in a ponytail and pulled her towards a bed that was in the VIP room. This room was made for many things and sexual ones were included. The Elderly cultivator was mad, his eyes red with anger after getting spit on. He planned to have his way with this woman, then to order his men to do the same while her guards would get beaten to an inch of their life. Then he would leave a permanent scar of the woman's face so that she remembers this day before tossing her out bruised and bloodied as a reminder to not offend the Cheng Clan.

Lan Fei was trying to trash about, but the stronger cultivator was using some strange technique to sap away her vitality. She couldn't move well, her cheek hurt due to the hard slap. She still showed a look of defiance that made the man in front of her even madder but she didn't want to show weakness in front of a bastard like this. She could see the man going to his robe to remove his pants while grinning in a devilish way. She started cursing inwardly, this is how things in this world worked. The woman knew how it was, but she still felt indignant about it.

While the Cheng clan members were grinning side to side and stomping on the woman's guards ready to see a good show something happened. The door that was supposed to be locked suddenly was flung open and they could see one of the people that was supposed to be guarding it on the other side get thrown inside the room and landed flat up against the wall, out called and with shattered teeth. Then they saw a person walk in, their eyes going wide as they could identify this person. Oh, they remembered him alright, it was the cultivator that screwed up their previous extortion attempt and now he was standing there in the doorway, looking awfully mad while giving them the stare down.

Chapter 40

The auction was over and Matt stood up from his seat, no one dared to enter his room fearing that a powerful cultivator could go ape shit if he got disturbed. They placed a nice lady at the entrance to the booth to serve him drinks or anything that he wanted, but Zhang Dong didn't really notice her as he was focusing on his calculations and looking how the auction went. He only stood up right at the end and spotted the woman there, giving her an awkward look.

"Oh right, where can I get my spirit stone, I want to cash out."

He asked while talking as if this was some kind of casino and he had won some cash. The woman nodded and guided him through the noisy auction house, people were everywhere still picking up their items and spirit stones that they earned so a lot of workers were rushing about not wanting to keep the cultivators waiting.

Matt moved slowly through the crowd but as people spotted him they started whispering, he made a scene while coming to the city and even a bigger one when he crushed the young master's carriage in the racing accident. World of mouth traveled fast, information about a strong cultivator that was easy to anger spread through the city like wildfire. Though he was easy to anger he apparently was quite mild in dishing out punishment as he let the silkypants and his friends go, along with the Cheng clan that were a part of it. They didn't know if he feared the clan or if he just didn't bother with weaklings. This world was ruled by the size of your fist, so it wouldn't be odd if a strong cultivator walzed in here and crushed that clan that let their children be so overbearing one of these days.

Though there also was a reason that the Cheng Clan wasn't that afraid of getting retaliated against, they had their backing which came from other large organisations. So some people assumed that the strong cultivator didn't want to tussle with the real powers in the back that could come back to bite him in the butt later on, which was a smart idea.

ZD turned to the side as he noticed that people where talking and looking at him in a strange way. The moment he did that the cultivators whistled with hands behind their back and pretended that they were looking at something else. One person even evaded his gaze and started looking at the ceiling.

*Man, they sure are afraid of me. Do I look like some psycho or something?*

He still wasn't that long in this world but by what he experienced in the village back in the forest, he knew that people tended to be tense around people like him. At least they didn't attack him or bother him too much thanks to that, there were good and bad things about his new found fame.

He fallowed the servant lady into the back, the corridor started looking more and more high class the further he got. Guess he was really receiving the vip treatment, which made him chuckle on the inside a bit. Matt didn't think that he would be put in the shoes of an elite but here he was. The lady bowed and opened a certain room for him but before he entered he noticed some people standing in front of another room that wasn't that far away from his own. He could swear that he knew one of those guards, but he shrugged and entered back into the room that the girl guided him.

There was a dandy looking man in there, if he didn't know better he would have called him Alfred or something. The mustached man brought out a bag filled with spirit stones, they were small but he did earn quite a bit with his weapons so it was nice and chubby.

"1850 low grade spirit stones, all accounted for would you like to count them yourself fellow Daoist?"

Matt grasped the sack with the stones in and looked at it, he didn't feel like counting and he really didn't think that the people in here would dare to rip him off.

"No it's fine I trust your auction house, oh right I'll return this to you."

He placed the jade slip that he got with the going rates of items and placed it on the desk by what the man was standing at. The man took the slip away and pocketed it.

"Thank you sir, I hope you'll come and do business with us again, the red tiger auction house always welcomes new business partners ."

Matt decided not to ask about further business just yet, he also wanted to check Spirit Spring City's auction house and market, maybe he could get a better deal there. He thought that it was about time to leave so he bade the man farewell and started walking out. As he was outside he took a look at the guard once more and then it hit him, it was that guy that was bothering those caravan people. He squinted his eyes wondering what those people were up to, he then thought about that busty woman, she was in the auction house as well, they couldn't have...

Zhang Dong moved towards the Cheng clan member in question while the gentleman looking person behind him frowned, he didn't like the way this was looking. He whispered something to the lady that guided Matt here and she took off running somewhere while he himself remain to monitor the situation.

The Cheng Clan member noticed the cultivator walking towards him and he instantly knew who he was. They people that were here weren't around when he was making a scene in the city road so they didn't know he was here. They were busy with puling strings to set this up at the auction house and didn't bother to ask for current news. The large man was now standing right in front of him and looking down at him. The cultivator glanced down at him and then looked at the door for a couple of seconds, while he was looking at the door his facial expression started changing.

Matt was focusing his senses inside the room, it had some treasures that could block others from peeking inside but that was for people below the core formation level. He got quite good at sensing the flow of spiritual energy during his cultivation, the lightning Qi arts were one of the most difficult techniques that a cultivator could train. So it let him peek inside and he didn't like the thing he could see one bit.

Before the guard could shout out for help he got his head grasped by the large cultivator. Matt grabbed his whole jaw below the nose and lifted him upwards with one hand. The man squirmed around while grasping the larger cultivators muscular forearm, but he couldn't budge it one millimeter. Zhang Dong delivered a kick to the door that blasted it open he then threw the man inside before walking in. The Cheng clan guard hit the wall on the opposite end of the room and slid down, bloody nose and out cold.

The people inside were greeted by the appearance of the cultivator that they met in the morning. He looked quite pissed and was mostly looking in the direction of the Foundation Establishment elder that was pulling his pants down at the very moment.

"What the hell are you bastards doing!"

He shouted out, his aura filled the room lightning shooting out from his body as it made the area they were in tremble. The people inside the room started going down to their knees as the oppressive aura pushed them down. Matt had enough control of his aura attack by now, that he could target the Cheng Clan bastards while leaving the woman and her guards with no pressure to fight against.

The woman felt the pressure that the elder was giving out vanish and she could move up from the bed, she recognized the person that barged in the room, it was that strange Senior that previously gave them a hand and it looked like he was here to save them again.

"S-senior show mercy, w-we didn't know"

The rapist elder said while being squished on the ground and trembling, he was getting most of the aura attack from the group.

"Didn't know what? To not rape people? The hell are you even talking about."

The elder assumed that this woman was probably this man's or at the least he fancied her in some way. The idea of him just being a decent person and just coming to help without wanting anything in return didn't cross his mind. Lan Fei and her men were a bit surprised but the sudden help as well, the woman helped her men up that had taken some damage from stomping but they were mostly alright.

Matt was thinking about what he should do, he was angry after seeing the attempted rape, should he punish the man? But if so, how should he punish him? He didn't feel like an authority figure but he wasn't stupid, he knew that if he brought the man to the authorities of this city they would probably let him go with no punishment. They would probably not even punish him for the rape but for the fact that he offended someone stronger than the clan could handle. But he wasn't a ruthless cultivator, he couldn't just kill him and be done with it either.

He came to a decision that was somewhere in the middle and hoped that it was the right one, he stepped up to the old man while everyone was focused on him not saying a thing. He pulled him upwards by his robe's collar and the man was now dangling in front of him with fear in his eyes.

"N-nooooo S-senior show mercy."

The man pleaded as he thought he was a goner now, but instead of killing him Matt placed his hand against the man's body. He was aiming for the dantian, lightning Qi crackled as he released a blast and destroyed the man's source of cultivation rendering him a regular mortal in the process. He thought that this was the best thing he could do as the man would probably have a miserable life ahead of himself now. Some might say that he was too lenient, but he really didn't have that killer mentality that some other cultivators had, at least not yet.

Crippled the cultivation of Foundation Establishment early stage target, earned 2000 Spirit Points

Chapter 41

The senior Cheng Clan member collapsed on the ground with his legs twitching, he was alive but his cultivation was crippled and he was just a regular human being now. If his past crimes came back to haunt him, it would now be his own fault. Matt gave out a sigh as he stopped suppressing everyone in the room with his aura, the henchmen were all passed out and convulsing on the ground from the overpowering aura that hit them but they were all alive. He started going around and pushed his finger into the peoples dantian, crippling their cultivation as well. He ignored the prompt the system gave him for now.

"Are you people alright?"

Zhang Dong took a step towards the female cultivator and her guards that were standing together on the side. The looked at the large man coming towards and didn't know how to react. The clasped their hands and gave of a bow of appreciation, they were truly grateful of this magnanimous Senior that came to their help, they would never forget the things that he did for them. While Lan Fei was doing her bow he fell forward, she was still feeling weak and the overwhelming auras in this room were a bit much for Qi Condensation cultivators. She found herself getting caught by the manly cultivator in front of her. It looked like she was giving him a hug with her breasts pressing into his frame.

Matt could feel the soft sensation against his body as the woman fell into his arms as he tried to catch her and instead ended up hugging her. He froze for a second, she gave off an alluring smell and was soft to the touch. His inexperience showed as his face started turning a bit red, the man not really having much experience with women.

"Ah... uh s-sorry about that..."

The woman leaned back while the cultivator was flailing his arms around, his face looked red. She stared at him with her large eyes and after a second gave out a second.

"Pffff... well that's unexpected~"

*This Senior looks to be very 'pure' on the inside*

She gave him a wink while smiling, the woman wasn't a stranger to female and male relationships so she could tell that the man in front to her had very limited experience in those kinds of things. This surprised her a bit, but it wasn't that rare to have cultivators train all their life and not play around with girls. But this man in front of her was acting really cute so she felt like teasing him slightly, the tension leaving her body as she felt that this man in front of her was a genuinely nice person.

He rubbed the back of his neck while looking at the two guards next to the lady. The guards weren't that surprised that the woman was making moves at the Senior, she did tend to use her sex appeal to get better business deals and all.

"How about we leave, I'm sure those clan people won't try to pull anything with me around."

Zhang Dong said while trying to move things along, he didn't really want to stay here anymore plus the girl was giving him strange looks.

"Oh my(Ara ara), Senior. That would be wonderful."

You wouldn't think that this woman was just a minute away from getting rapped by the way she was acting. But Lan Fei was a tough cookie, something like this didn't phase her one bit. She was more focused on gaining the support of a powerful being then about what happened with that old pervert back there. Guess you could say that she as used to these kind of things happening, you had to grow a thick skin if you wanted to survive in this world. She was all smiles and moved right next to the man in white, she looked up to him with those large green eyes and gave him an alluring smile, which made our inexperienced cultivator heartbeat increase.

"Senior, I'm still a bit weak, you won't mind if I lean on you right?"

"Lean on me, uh sure?"

Though she did a bit more than lean on him, the sneaky vixen wrapped her arm around Matt's and now they looked like a couple walking together. The man blushed even more as he walked through the corridor, the two guards walking behind them while thinking that their mistress was overdoing it with the act a bit but the cultivator in white seamed to be taking the bait. Women were scary creatures they thought to each other while looking as their leader pushed her ample bosom into the man's arm.

People looked at the scene of them walking, the auction house personnel were alerted to the fiasco that happened. They arrived at the scene to see the Cheng Clan members collapsed on the ground, they started pulling them out while some others tried to apologize to both the Cheng Clan and the cultivator that beat them up. But when they tried to approach him he was with some lady that was sticking to him like glue and giving them shifty looks as if they were approaching a deer that she hunted.

"Ah... sorry about that, those guys tried to hurt my friend here..."

Matt explained while the woman stuck to him like glue, he was a bit perplexed as she didn't seem that weak she should be able to stand on her own by now. But he said that he would escort them out and protect them from those clan members that might try to pull something.

The auction hose members were shocked that someone tried to rape this overpowered Senior's friend and were very apologetic. They even tried giving him some spirit stones but were told by him to give those to the caravan members in question that were the real victims. He, of course, told it in a very awkward way while the girl was sticking close to his arm. Was she going to stick to him like this for the rest of the walk? well, it did feel kind of nice though...

The caravan members were sure to pocket the extra apology reward as fast as they could, along with the spirit stones they won at the auction. After the people in question left, the Cheng clan members were relocated into another room. Madam Wong waited for a representative of the Cheng clan to arrive so that they could explain themselves, this was supposed to be a neutral zone away from the cities leading clan. She could not have people feeling intimidated by the ruling power, otherwise, they could just force anyone to stop bidding and get things cheaper. The lady had a high cultivation base and many connections so she didn't fear that upstart clan one bit. Also, the ones that worked for her that were responsible for this, would be getting a special reward as well...

While the auction house owner was fuming in her office the white-haired cultivator was getting stared at by the passerby. He looked like some young lord with a lady around his arm and guards walking behind him, looking mean. People parted to the sides and let the people through while giving the man envious looks after spotting the woman that was clinging to him.

The woman in question was chuckling inwardly as whenever she did something alluring the man would react like a teenager. He would blush, he would start stuttering and tripping over his own words while not trying to stare at her cleavage. She didn't think a person with this amount of strength, could be this childish. Even if he was inexperienced most men would give her dirty looks and have a glint in their eyes, but this one made an effort to avert his gaze holding it in, she found this kind of commendable. This kind of made her want to eat him up even more, plus he looked like a rare good kind of guy this almost never happened with the more powerful cultivators.

"Ah, so this is the place you guys set up so uh... So I'll just be in my hotel if those people try to do something just tell me."

He described the location and name of the hotel that he was staying at and was about to leave, but the woman wiggled closer to him again.

"Oh, that's the most expensive hotel in the city, would Senior let little Fei see it?"

The caravan people had a deadpan expression on their faces after they heard their boss lady refer to herself as 'Little Fei' She would probably strangle anyone in their group that referred to her in that way.

"Y-you want to see the hotel I'm staying at?"

"Yes Senior, I heard they have delicious tea there too~"

She replied while still holding on to him, the man not knowing what to do in this situation so he just agreed being the weak-willed sob that he was.

"Well... okay then ... "

The two walked towards the hotel building while the caravan people discussed how their lady boss was able to see the bigger picture. Everyone from them knew exactly what she was doing and thought that was a normal thing to do. Why wouldn't you suck up to a powerful cultivator if a chance presented itself? They just hoped that this cultivator was as harmless as he seemed, you never knew so they still worried about their boss.

Chapter 42

The cultivator was sweating a bit while looking to the side, the lady was still there and he just didn't know what he should do. He wasn't that dumb, he realized that she wanted something from him by now. The man had very limited experience with women, not like he didn't like them or anything. In his previous life, he was that one guy that stood alone at parties, getting invited by friends but never knowing what to do there. He was approached by girls here and there, but he never knew how to talk to them or how to keep the conversation going. He was a classic introvert that just felt bad at social gatherings so after a while he just stopped attending them.

This woman was strange though, even though he was stuttering all over the place and looking awkward as hell she just giggled to herself and didn't seem to be bothered by it at all. He was kind of on the fence about this whole thing, one part of him felt excited that a beauty like this was interested in him, the other part was terrified as he didn't want to make a fool out of himself.

The woman was about 170 cm, she had long black hair that was done in a ponytail style. She was wearing one of those Chinese style dresses, the skirt part went down to about her ankles but the sides were open, so you could see her shapely legs. She had high heels on her feet and the top part of the dress had a cutout part that let you see the cleavage. And boy or boy, she really did fill out that piece of clothing well. She had that classic hourglass figure but was a bit more top-heavy. The rear end didn't fall behind much though and those legs were nice and toned, probably due to the martial arts background that she had. Her eyes were big and green her face as more adult looking than cute.

He had a hard time focusing on anything with the woman wrapped around his muscular arm, after a while, he found himself in front of his hotel room. Lan Fei finally let go of his arm as he welcomed her in, she looked around the large suite that had quite a bit of things included. The room was large, she could see a fireplace being set up by the wall along with a couch that pointed in its direction. There was a toilet and bath included as well. The large bed could hold multiple people in it and the windows showed the view of the city.

There was some tea provided by the hotel and a magical treasure like a kettle that was used for boiling, there was no electricity in this world so everything runs on spiritual Qi that could be stored in various ways.

"Okay, tea right?"

He went right towards the tea kettle to prepare the tea, just trying to do something else as the woman finally let go of his arm and was now looking around the large room. She was touching the furniture and for some reason pulled the drapes together, sealing off the view at the lit-up city which was bustling with nighttime activities.

*Okay, calm down she's just here for some tea no need to lose your head about it. We'll just chat a bit and then... uh then what?*

He was so bewildered by the situation that he didn't think about the obvious reason why the woman was here in the first place. But he did realize it after he turned around whit the teacups in his hands and the woman was lying on the bed. She was on her side in a seductive pose but that wasn't the problem, the problem was that she was naked. Zhang Dong dropped the teacups to the ground out of sheer surprise. He couldn't take his eyes off the woman's shapely curves that were being presented.

"Uh...huh...?"

"Well, are you just going to stand there? I just wanted to show my appreciation and by the looks of things, Senior is appreciating the view~"

She said while giggling, her breasts bouncing slightly as she noticed how Zhang Dong's lower area was reacting to the provocative scene before him. The lower brother was looking vigorous which kind of made the cultivator bend forward a bit as to hide it.

"W-well, y-you know..."

*God damn is this really happening! Did my lucky day finally come?*

Matt wasn't about to look a gift horse in the mouth, even though he was an awkward sob there was a limit to being incompetent. He still was a man, so he started frantically fiddling with his pants while looking between the naked woman in front of him and his clothes which were his greatest enemy at the moment. He finally was able to pull his pants down and kicked them to the side along with the rest of his robe, he started going towards his undies but then he suddenly stopped and looked at the woman that was beckoning over.

*Wait! I can't do this!*

"Uh... I'll be right back ... just wait for a second!"

He vanished into the bathroom area of the room to the surprise of the woman that was waiting for him on the bed. She wondered if the man wasn't interested or something. Matt, on the other hand, was frantically clicking through his system cash shop looking for a specific item.

*Aha! They have those here, system be thanked!*

He poked the air and a small packet popped out, it was something people from earth were very familiar with, yes it was a packet of condoms. They had a cultivator theme though, along with a drawing of a sharp sword standing upwards. Safety came first, so after 'armoring up' he returned to the room while the woman peeked back up as the quirky Senior was right back and looked like he was in the mood. He climbed on top of the bed to the female cultivator that was all smiles, he reached out to her and she reached back.

-A night of bad smut later.-

He woke up, feeling like a new man like a big weight had been lifted from his heart. The woman was in the bathing area of the room just freshening herself up after the nightly session. She guided him through his first encounter, opening up his eyes to a new world in the process. He would remember this night for the rest of his life even more, due to the fact that it took him so long to get his cherry popped. But even more, after something was about to happen.

"You never told me your name Senior~"

The woman walked out while back in her clothes, still bouncy as ever and swinging her hips side to side in an alluring way.

"Oh, didn't I? Well, guess you can call me Zhang Dong."

He smiled thinking nothing of it while giving the girl the name that the system gave him, he couldn't really tell anyone his earthly name here. After he told the woman his name, her facial expression changed.

"Zhang? The Zhang Clan from Spirit Spring City?"

She asked while thinking about something.

"Ah yes, did you hear of my clan before, they are in Spirit Spring City."

The gears started turning in the woman's head while looking at the man that was smiling back at her. She was a merchant so after getting into this city she sent someone to gather info about the Zhang clan that previously used to own this place. She found out that it was a big clan but it failed in a big expedition. It wasn't anything new, a big clan goes on an expedition to some sealed of realm or for some treasure hunting and chews of more than they can handle.

The clan lost their Patriarch in the expedition along with all of their core formation elders, the rumor was that they just had one core formation elder back in the city. Everyone knew what happened to big family clans that lost their power to defend themselves, they would get poached by other big clans. The woman thought that this man would be her meal ticket out of the merchant work, but instead, if she associates with him she could get labeled as a clan member as well and then go under with the rest of that clan.

"Ahh, Senior... I think I should go back to my people, You don't need to walk me back..."

She quickly removed herself from the room while Matt was trying to figure out while the woman did a 180 on him and stormed out of the building.

"She started acting strange the moment I said my clan name... was that it?"

Matt tilted his head to the side and thought about the setting where his clan was supposed to be down on its luck.

"Is the clan's situation that bad, that people won't associate with me due to it?"

Matt felt hurt a bit after the woman that he had an intimate night just fled the moment she heard about his family situation, he would also have to get to the bottom of that as well. He flopped back onto the bed and looked at the ceiling.

"God damn little Fei, you don't need to drop me like a sack of potatoes the moment you hear my last name!"

Chapter 43

The man wasn't sure how he should feel about the whole encounter, he thought he would feel happier after doing the deed but instead, he felt hollow on the inside after the woman left. I guess it wasn't all that great if there weren't any feelings involved. But not like he didn't enjoy his encounter, he still had a stupid expression on his face as he thought back to the night.

*Uh, I'll consider this a win..."

He went into the bathroom to clean himself up a bit dejected that the woman was gunning more for his status than himself, then he dressed and headed out to ask people about the Zhang Clan. The rumors were widespread so it wasn't hard. Apparently the Zhang Clan was void of any elders at the moment and all of their heavy hitters died in some exploration attempt of some ruin or holy ground. Those were things akin to dungeons that had sealed of spaces and you never knew what dangers lurked inside, it wasn't anything new you could gain a lot but also lose your life.

*Guess that's why Fei gave me the cold shoulder, she thinks that I have no backing now and will get hunted by other clans if they see me...*

He still felt a bit dejected but could understand the woman's decision and not like they had any deep relationship bonding them anyway. He needed to make a decision now, either head to the Zhang Clan and check out if he could salvage the situation there, maybe it wasn't as bad as the rumors said. Or wait it out then make the decision. Not like he couldn't take another identity if he wanted, this would probably be the intelligent thing to do, but would the people from the Zhang clan die if he didn't go there?

This would probably be the case, but that didn't really sit well with him. Would this system place him in a hopeless position? He didn't really have a hard time, the enemies weren't that tough and he was getting better and better at fighting. He also considered his personal strength to be in the later stages of core formation due to his cultivation method and added bonuses from the Dao he had.

He didn't know why but it just didn't feel right to abandon those Zhang Clan members, from what he heard the people around here much preferred them to the Cheng Clan that was gaining power. He couldn't just abandon them now after he knew that they were in danger. Also, he was slowly starting to change a bit, the winning battle with the tentacle monster brought something new. The feeling was strange, but it made him itch for a fight.

It was one thing to battle beasts and fry big bug monsters with his lightning bolts, it was another thing to do the same thing to other humans. He didn't know if he could hold back and not kill someone by mistake either. While this was going through his mind he tossed out his large sword and started going up into the air. He glanced in the direction of the caravan as he flew above them for a moment, they were leaving the city. The woman noticed him looking at her from afar, she just gave him a little bow before looking away and heading out of the city.

Matt gave out a sigh and looked at his system map, this city was a halfway point if he counted the forest as his starting point so it would take him a bit to get there. So he pushed his spiritual energy into it and with a thunderous sound, he bolted towards his new destination. The people in the city were alerted to his loud takeoff, the Cheng Clan members glad that he was finally gone and that they didn't suffer much besides that one pervy elder of theirs, but he could be easily replaced.

He was going fast and the scenery rapidly changed below him as he increased his speed, he decided to do some mental training while he was at it. Checking all of his inner knowledge that he received from the system wanting to know what he had imprinted in him concerning fighting other cultivators. He also counted that he would have a bit over 25k spirit points if he started absorbing the spirit stones he got. Though he wasn't sure what to spend it on yet, he also had enough skills he didn't really need anymore. They were all higher grade and powerful. Though he was running low on those healing pills, he might have to spend some on those.

At about the time that Zhang Dong was speeding towards his destination, other things were happening there.

Spirit Spring City was at full alert, their defensive formations were all active, a bright golden shield was covering the whole city. You could see cultivators sitting in lotus positions powering the defensive shield that covered the whole area. Some of them were getting dragged away on stretchers, their bodies drained from their spiritual energy as they were switched out with other cultivators. On the other side of the shield you could see people as well, they were pounding on the shield with something that looked like siege weapons. There were balistas and cannons, firing of colorful shots of energy that were hitting the golden shield making it rumble.

Back inside, there was one old cultivator looking at the spot that the weapons were firing at. His hair was white, his face had a scar running from his eyebrow down to his cheek. He had a beard and was about six feet tall, his eyes had a golden hue to them. He had a frown on his face, his hands were behind his back as he squinted at the spot that was getting bombarded.

"How long do we have?"

He asked one of the people next to him, there were older people like him. On his left it was an older lady, looking to be in her sixties and on the right side it was an old man about the same age.

"A couple of days, a week at most Elder Jin"

The woman said while also looking in the same direction.

"Any word from outside?"

"No sir, we sent out a plea for help to outside families and a call to arms. Some have come to aid us but no one that could turn the tide. There is probably no more help coming. We have no way of contacting clan members that weren't inside the formation after it was activated as well."

They had lost their Patriarch and the core members of the Clan, Elder Jin was the only core formation cultivator left around and he was also only of the early stage. Zhang Jin gripped his fist in anger as he remembered the day that they got ordered by the sect to examine a new formed holy ground that was unexplored. They couldn't refuse but the area was an enigma. The Patriarch was forced to join the expedition along with the other elders as well as the junior members. Afterward, they found all the spirit tablets with their names cracked and crumbled, indicating that they had perished. They kept this hidden for some time, but after a couple of months the other clans figured it out.

The sect that ordered the campaign didn't want to get involved, they just told them to work it out on their own accord, it wasn't their fault that their people weren't strong enough to manage an easy exploration mission. They got used then abandoned and they couldn't do anything about it. They could try bargaining with the other clans, but at most they could offer their women and children as slaves, the men would probably be killed. But that wasn't their style, they would fight to the end.

"I didn't think that my Zhang Clan would end like this..."

The man looked at the city and the people around them, this was his family. The clan survived for many hundreds of years and the future was looking bright, who would have thought that this would have happened? He would go down swinging, he was old, he didn't fear death but he was worried about the younger members. He planned to stall as long as he could so that at least the women and children could get away, he already discussed this with the warriors from the clan. The reason that they were still keeping the shield up was just a faint hope that someone would come to their aid, this tactic was about to pay off...

Chapter 44

Zhang Dong was soaring through the sky in Spirit Spring City's direction, he didn't see many people during his journey and he was getting bored. He tried cultivating while flying on his sword, but he found it rather hard to keep it flying forward while absorbing the spiritual energy from the surroundings at the same time. He almost suffered a backlash, so he gave up on the idea of getting his cultivation up while traveling. He slowly got used to this cultivator body, not really needing rest or sleep that much.

He didn't just do all nighters though, but he still flew fast with a couple of stops here and there. About two days passed like that and it was getting dark outside. He could hear some random beasts roaring in the background every time that happened but they weren't really a problem for him. Though for your average cultivator it was mostly not a good idea to travel at night without a larger party. He got used to traveling during the night as well, finding the moons in the sky to be quite beautiful as they lighted up the night-sky.

As he was drifting through the night like a white ghost, he noticed something in front of him. He squinted with his eyes and focused at the spiritual fluctuations coming his way. He saw a pair of cultivators running in the direction that he was flying from, though he was quite a bit further away. It was a female and a man, they both had similar looking light blue robes. The man was dragging the woman forward a bit as the two seamed to be fleeing from something or someone.

Matt tried looking behind the two people that were frantically running while holding on to each other. But before he could see anyone behind them an arrow pierced the fleeing man's shoulder. He did falter though, he tore the end of the arrow that was coming out of his shoulder and threw it to the side and kept on running with the woman next to him. They were slower now, the man started falling behind the woman that was now pulling him along instead.

Zhang Dong flew increased his speed towards them, he could see about 10 people behind the pair and after he got closer he could tell that the woman and man were actually more of a boy and a girl in their middle teen years. His vision was enhanced so he could see how the people that were chasing them had smirks on their faces.

*Why am I constantly running into people in trouble...*

He asked himself while increasing his speed, hoping that he would make it.

Zhang Liu and Xue were members of the unfortunate clan. They were brother and sister, he was 16 and she was 15. They were away from the city, gathering resources in the mountains which wasn't an odd thing to do for Clan members of their age. They were out of the city while the other clans and cultivators invaded. They couldn't get back as the defensive formation as already running. They had to look on in horror as their home was getting bombarded by the invading forces. They wanted to help out but they weren't stupid, they both knew that they were far too weak to help out. They swore in their hearts to take revenge after they escaped. But the two were discovered while they were making their escape and were now getting chased by the forces that were attacking their home city.

Zhang Liu felt a sharp pain in his shoulder where the arrow was stuck in, his little sister was pulling him along while he was trying to keep up. He was in much pain, sweat covering his body while the enemy cultivators were hot on their tracks.

"I'll hold them off Xue, you run take revenge for our clan!"

He knew that he was a burden by now, maybe if he held the attackers of a bit his little sister could get away.

"No big brother, I won't leave you to die!"

The little sister didn't want to let her brother just die here, her hand was tightly clenching his hand as the two were running in the fields. The problem with this was, that the enemies had a good archer and there were no trees or rocks to duck behind. You could heer an arrow whiz through the air followed by a loud scream.

"Oh no, big brother!"

Zhang Liu screamed out in pain as he felt a sharp pain in his calf as the arrow pierced the lower part of his leg, going right through it. He fell face-first onto the hard ground, wincing in pain. He looked at his leg and then to his sister, he knew that he was done for. There was no way that he could escape like this.

"Please, Xue you must save yourself, run and forget about me..."

The fifteen-year-old girl teared up as she went down to her knees, pulling at her brother as she tried supporting him upwards but instead got pushed away by him.

"Run, I'll stall them."

He stood up with the help of his good leg while turning his back to his little sister, his eyes were focused and he was ready to fight till the end. He could hear other people coming and soon could see the ten cultivators in matching yellow robes coming out. His sister looked at her brother's large back, she remembered how once he carried her back home when she fell asleep. She whipped the tears from her eyes and instead of escaping stood next to her big brother, fire in her eyes as well.

"If we have to die, then we will die together big brother!"

Zhang Liu looked at his little sister and shook his head, he knew that she was very headstrong and there was no use arguing when she got like that. There was also no more time as he looked in front to see the cultivators moving to surround them, grins on their faces.

"Well, what do we have here, two Zhang whelps. Thought you could get away?"

One of the men said while grinning.

"Hey the girly on the left isn't half bad, let's have some fun with her!"

Another sleazy looking man said while licking his lips while glancing at Zhang Xue.

Lui instinctively moved in front of his sister to cover her, but it was looking bleak he could only glare at the people with his fists outstretched. The sister started backing away while in her combat stance, she had a saber with her. The two were backing away, they didn't want to be surrounded by their enemies that were moving closer and closer.

"Let's just kill the guy off, no use keeping him around."

The sleazy man said while holding out a bow, three other cultivators did the same as they took aim for the youth. They started infusing their spiritual energy into the arrows, their penetrative power and speed would be increased the chances of the boy surviving this were meek. But just before the enemy cultivators could release their arrows a strange sound could be heard, followed by a big explosion that was just a couple of meters away from the band of ruffians.

The ten people backed away in horror as the dirt and rubble headed their way. They covered up while jumping backward, not sure if there was a new enemy or if there was some magical bomb treasure buried in the ground that made it explode. But soon another explosion occurred right behind them, then another one to the left side and the right side. They stopped in one spot as they got boxed in by the blasts, they had no idea what was going on as the explosions were happening too fast and they couldn't even see where the attack was coming from.

"Hey you, stay where you are, don't move a muscle."

They heard a man's voice coming from above, everyone looked up to see a man standing on a cristal sword. He was holding what looked to be a bolt of lightning fashioned into a spear, they figured that it was probably that man that was attacking them.

"Why are you attacking these people, ten grown men against two kids just doesn't look right."

The man asked while looking at the brother and sister duo, that were now hugging each other not sure what to do. Was this man going to save them? But if he hears that they are from a weak clan that is about to get eradicated he won't probably help.

"Good Senior, those people are from the Zhang Clan, we are from the honorable Tsai Clan. You probably heard what happened to the Zhang Clan it's already done for, the elders just ordered us to take care of anyone that runs away. Our honorable Patriarch is also taking part in the seizure of their treasures.I'm sure he would have a chat with you if you are willing."

"Seizure of treasures? Or do you mean cleansing?"

The man asked while moving closer and closer to the people, the Tsai Clan members hoping that the name of their clan would provide backing.

"Well yes hehe, I'm sure you know how things like that work Senior, they were just unlucky."

The man looked at the ten cultivators that were getting more confident he then looked back at the bleeding youth and the girl that was standing next to him, the two terrified and tense.

"You want to kill all of them... Well, guess I'll have to introduce myself. My name is..."

He jumped down from his sword onto the ground, he was right between the two Zhang Clan members and the Tsai Clan members.

"Zhang Dong."

After telling them his name, he pointed his finger at the cultivators standing together and a sphere appeared around them. The Tsai cultivators were shocked after hearing that the man was also from the Zhang clan. They started punching at the barrier but after hitting it once they got shocked by lightning instead.

"Don't worry I won't kill you, even though you tried to kill the boy and take advantage of the girl... but your cultivation days are over."

After saying that, lightning started hitting the people inside the sphere. The people were all Qi Condensation cultivators and even though they were in the top part of it, they were nothing to him. The lightning prison destroyed the people's cultivation bases leaving them all charred and injured yet still alive.

Crippled the cultivation of Qi Condensation targets, earned 225 Spirit Points

The two youths looked at the man that took care of the enemy cultivators in surprise.

"Senior U-uncle Dong?"

He almost tripped after getting called an uncle but kept it together. Zhang Dong took out one of the healing pills and handed it to the girl that looked at the pill with astonishment as she could tell that it was quite potent.

"I guess you can call me that... Those guys won't bother you anymore, give that pill to your brother after removing the arrows. Could you tell me about what is happening in Spirit Spring City."

The two felt relieved, they didn't know if this uncle that they didn't know could turn the tide but he was a powerful cultivator, this they could tell. They told him about the defensive formation and how they were being attacked by other clans, the enemies apparently had at least 3 core formation experts in their mids, maybe more. The two couldn't really tell as they were focused on escaping.

"Okay... you two should probably stay here..."

He said while hopping back onto his sword, he was deep in thought but seemed to make up his mind after which he shot like an arrow towards the Zhang Clan headquarters with a solemn look on his face.

Chapter 45

Matt left the teens alone and flew in the direction of the city. His facial expression was stern as he looked in the direction that he was going. There were many enemies and he didn't know if he alone could handle them all by himself. Just flying in there without a plan wouldn't be such a good idea either. But he couldn't just let one of those horrible clan cleansings happen, they would kill every member of the clan didn't matter if it were women and children. The people in these kinds of worlds had some twisted logic and no one seemed to bat an eye about it. Did he have to change his mindset and join the other cultivators, or could he pave out his own way?

He was more in the mindset of taking out the snake's head. If he took out the so-called patriarchs from the invading clans, the others should give up. He didn't know if he should sneak up on them and try to take out one of the core formation cultivators before engaging the rest in a fight, that would probably be the smart way to do it. He also thought about shouting out to the crowd and trying the intimidation route. But if that didn't work he would have given away the element of surprise for no reason. He also could take out one of them in a show of force, then try to scare them off. Zhang Dong didn't think that he needed to defeat all of them if they retreated he wouldn't be chasing them down.

He kind of wanted to go with the diplomatic route but that was somewhat unrealistic, even more after he saw that those people even tried killing some kids that were running away. Matt as slowly trying to shift his values a bit towards the 'kill or be killed' mentality, though he was just doing the cultivation crippling instead of the killing part.

He gave out a sigh as he went from having the night of his life to now going to rescue some people he didn't really know. The only thing compelling him to do it was a skewed sense of morality that he had from his original world, the system set him up as a member of this Clan and it might be bad if he let it get eradicated. He had already learned a way to hide his aura and unless he got really close people shouldn't be able to detect him. So he straightened up, slapped both of his cheeks to pump himself up and glided towards the direction from where those kids came from.

Sometime later at Spirit Spring City.

Zhang Jin was looking at the golden shield that was flickering now, the time running out a lot sooner than expected as the invading clans increased the rates of the bombardments. The people in the city were sitting ducks and they didn't have a way to retaliate, the most powerful treasures were the ones the Patriarch had and he was now dead. They had some attacking formations to their disposal but the more powerful ones required more core formation cultivators that they didn't have, it looked bleak.

The clans that were attacking them weren't all that strong if you compared them to the Zhang Clan before their elders perished. There was the Tsai Clan, the Wong Clan, and the Wu clan. The strongest one was the Tsai Clan with their Patriarch recently breaking through to the late stage of core formation. The weakest one was the Wu Clan, their leader was just in the early stage and there were more or less just here for the scraps. The Tsai Clan came with three core formation cultivators including their patriarch, two were from the Wong Clan and the last one belonged to the Wu clan.

The six middle-aged looking men were standing together, there were three cultivators in red robes standing in the front belonging to the Tsai Clan while the other clan elders stood a bit to the side. They were looking at the weakening shield and smirked.

"It's almost time, that shield won't last for much longer. Get everyone ready and surround the city so that no one can escape."

The Tsai Clan Patriarch with the highest cultivation barked out the orders and every other clan elder headed out to inform their subordinates. Two cultivators remained in the same spot, which was the Tsai Clan patriarch and another member from his clan.

"Patriarch Fang, some of the disciples haven't returned that were supposed to hunt for any remaining Zhang Clan members."

Tsai Fang looked at his fellow clan member and just shrugged.

"They're probably having their fun, leave them we have enough clan members here to clear out this city. Punish them if they come back empty-handed though."

This cultivator was wearing a red robe with white patterns in it, it made it look fiery. His hair and eyes were also red and as you might have thought this clan's specialty was fire. The man looked on as the glowing shield got thinner and thinner due to the constant impacts, a smirk on his face while his hands were behind his back. He moved his hand to his cheek where a big scar could be seen. This scar was something he received quite a while ago when he was battling the Zhang Clan Patriarch in his younger days. To this day he couldn't forget about this disgrace. It was him that organized this event, he wanted to remove anything related to the man that injured his face.

"Hah, are you seeing this Zhang Clan Patriarch, your clan will fall and everyone will burn. Just too bad that I can't see your ugly face while this happens."

You could hear a sound akin to glass shattering as a big fireball exploded in mid-air against the shield, the defensive formation finally running out of juice. The Clans outside the city gates cheered in unison while the people inside gasped. The time has come, the Zhang clan was outnumbered and outgunned. But they wouldn't be going down without a fight, after the shield got blasted away you could see a hail of arrows getting shot from within the city, accompanied by cannon fire from magic cannons that were mounted on the city walls.

The invading cultivator core formation elders snorted and took flight on their flying swords, they held their hands up into the air as they activated a magic technique blocking the cannon fire and arrows with just the five of them. The Tsai clan Patriarch didn't feel like taking part as he just wanted to enjoy the screams and watch a good show. The arrows weren't much, the cannons might have been able to strike down a foundation establishment cultivator but to these elders, it was less than a mosquito bite.

But while the invading clans were cheering their core formation elders on, something happened. While all the powerful cultivators were focusing on defending the city's cannon fire, thunder sounded behind them. The Wong clan member suddenly had a chilly premonition as he tried to move quickly to the side, but before he knew it he felt something wedge itself into his right shoulder. It looked like a spear made of energy, all the other elders saw it lodge itself in the man's flesh exploding after impact. The man fell down to the ground, his right shoulder blow off, his right arm just dangling about while looking quite gory. The man was more or less out of commission for the rest of the fight as he was losing a lot of blood and only managed to swallow some life-saving pills before collapsing on the ground.

Soon people started turning around to watch as lightning spears collided with all of their siege weapons. Everyone was running for their dear life as they got sneak attacked from the back, the rest of the core formation elders started evading the lightning bolts but the fellow up attack was mostly aimed at the gear that soon was just a pile of scrap.

Everyone could feel an overbearing aura descending from the sky and they finally saw Zhang Dong that was holding on to one of his lightning javelins, tossing it out. The spear of lightning split into smaller ones and bombarded the cultivator weapons on the ground turning all of them into scrap wood and metal in the process. There was also a big lightning dragon wiggling around his frame, roaring in thunderous booms that made the lower level cultivators ears bleed.

"I am Zhang Dong, leave this place if you don't want to die!"

Dong said as menacingly as he could while sweating inwardly hoping that the people would just turn tail and run.

Chapter 46

The cultivators from the Zhang Clan trembled with wide-open eyes as all of their arrows and cannon attacks got deflected and blocked by the invading forces. Zhang Jin was holding on to a big saber and all the remaining Zhang clan members were heavily armed. The time had come to defend their city, the normal people were hiding in their homes shaking and crying, they didn't know if they would survive this either.

But suddenly they looked on as one of the powerful enemy cultivators exploded in mid-air, he fell to the ground like a sack of rocks then stopped moving. Then they could hear loud booming sounds in the distance as many lightning javelins descended from the sky, trashing everything in their paths but not really killing anything just destroying the weapons instead.

The people looked at the cultivator that was descending in awe and got excited after hearing his name, he was a member of their clan. People turned to each other trying to recall someone by that name, but they couldn't recall anyone. Though Zhang Jin opened up his eyes and looked at the man, his face looked very similar to someone he remembered.

"It can't be, the boy still lives... He still lives!"

The man took out his own flying sword and jumped on it, he told the other two elders that were close to him to continue attacking the invading clan members while he would assist the cultivator that just arrived. The two tried to stop him but before they could say anything their grand elder flew of charging into the mids of the battle with his big saber in hand.

Zhang Dong was looking at the other five remaining cultivators, Tsai Fang joined the rest of them and now they were all looking at him. He kept his face in a neutral state managing to show no emotion, but if you looked closely you could see one of his fingers twitching and sweat forming on his forehead. The cultivators were trying to measure the situation, they could feel that this cultivator was at least on par with the Tsai clan patriarch maybe a bit stronger. They all came here with the mindset that the city would be easy pickings and none of them was actually willing to risk their life if it came down to it. They outnumbered him five to one, so they should be able to beat him but he was able to incapacitate one of them with one aimed blow so they didn't want to risk it.

"Who..."

Tsai Fang was about to say something but before he could do that he could feel someone charging at them from behind. It was, of course, Zhang Jin charging with his saber in tow. He smashed into the weakest elder of the group that was from the Wu clan, forcing him back.

"Don't worry Dong'er! I'll handle him, long live the Zhang Clan!"

Matt twitched as he looked at the bearded elder hacking away at one of the enemy cultivators. Messing up his plan of having a diplomatic solution to this fight.

*What did he call me, Donger? What the hell is even that you old bastard!*

Any motion of having the men give up on attacking the city was thrown out the window with Zhang Jin's sudden attack. The three Tsai Clan members and the Wong clan patriarch turned their faces to Zhang Dong and got into their battling positions. Everything became chaotic as the now many core formation cultivators were flying around and throwing some flashy techniques at each other.

The people on the ground didn't just wait though, they continued with the siege of the city even though their heavy weapons were now destroyed. The Zhang clan people started firing their canons again while tossing people down from the walls and trying to defend the gates.

A big battle was about to take place, the moment the invading forces managed to scale the city walls fighting would commence inside. People were getting injured left and right, without the support of their core formation elders the attackers were suffering loses and many cultivators started looking like pincushions. For the time being the Zhang Clan was managing to hold them off, the deciding factor would probably be the battle that was taking place above their heads as the cultivators flew around on their swords.

Zhang Dong just dodged a fireball while his lightning dragon was getting roasted by two other Tsai clan members, they certainly were looking like fire benders or something. The fourth enemy he was fighting was quite annoying as well as he had a big bow and was firing off some strange green energy arrows at him. He couldn't really do much besides dodging left and right, his clothes slowly getting ripped. His aerial combat expertise was close to nil, but the other people couldn't hit him either as he was faster than them, his flying sword was of a higher quality which let him zoom around the battlefield quickly. The old guy that interfered with his diplomatic talks was nowhere to be seen as he dodged around like a slippery eel.

"Stop running you, coward!"

"How about no?"

The quartet was getting mad as this guy was just too squiggly and they couldn't get off a good hit on him. They tried firing some larger skills but that took too long to charge up so the white cultivator could just evade it. Plus this lightning dragon was quite annoying as well, the enemy could summon it again and when they managed to whittle it down it exploded with a resounding boom filling the area with chaotic lightning energy.

"He can't run forever, there are four of us sooner or later he will run out of spiritual energy!"

Matt knew that they were right, he couldn't just keep evading and blocking their attacks forever. He did have a big tank of spiritual energy but he was one against four. He did try attacking a couple of them here and there with his ranged attacks but when he aimed for one, two others would try to slash, pierce and pummel him from behind. He had to think about something fast, he needed to take out one of them first. He couldn't run forever, so he finally decided on a tactic and went for it.

His first target would be the annoying archer from the group, so he used his lightning dragon to attack one of the red-robed cultivators and while the other ones tried to go for a backstab he encased them in his forcefield skill. While they were distracted he charged at the archer who was firing of green energy arrows at him, he did his best Jedi impression of batting the energy bolts away with his light sword. He managed to close the distance, the man defended himself with the bow as he thought that Matt would surely swing that light sword down at him.

Instead, the Wong Patriarch got surprised as the man abandoned his weapon and directly attacked him instead. An afterimage was left behind on the flying sword that was discarded, the enemy cultivator then found himself in a chokehold as the two started falling down to the ground. Matt started squeezing with all his might and he could hear the man's bones shattering in the process. The addition of the lightning Qi, made the man light up like a Christmas tree. This was a very unorthodox way of fighting, the Wong Clan member was not expecting something like this but soon he found himself losing consciousness. The man was tossed aside like a ragdoll, Zhang Dong was able to guide his sword back to his feet once more.

The other three attackers that remained managed to resolve Matt's skills and were now looking at the white cultivator that was back to hovering on his sword. He had choked the poor guy out, shattering his bones in the process. He didn't know if he had actually killed him, he couldn't really check, but to a cultivator of this level, a broken neck wasn't quite fatal.

The three cultivators looked on in shock as they saw one of their allies get taken out by the Zhang Clan member, it didn't look good for them as they barely had an upper hand at four vs one, but now they were down to just three.

"Tsai Clan members to me!"

The people were all from the same clan, so as their leader shouted out they heard his call. They hovered close to each other and started doing some strange hand motions like they knew what their leader had in mind. Zhang Dong was panting a bit as using his skills in rapid succession as starting to drain his reserves as well, so he wasn't really able to react to what those people were doing.

Soon molten rock and fire started forming around the cultivators encasing them in it. It started with just a big molten rock core but soon expanded. The think started taking a humanoid appearance, big blazing legs and huge arms sprouted from the middle part that the enemy cultivators were in and soon they formed an appearance of a giant made from volcanic rock and fire. It didn't have a head but a volcano instead, molten rock and smoke coming out from it. Its arms were huge and rocky as well as its legs, there were cracks in its shell, fire, and lava spilling from them, it was about fifteen meters tall.

The giant cocked its arm back and threw a punch at Zhang Dong that tried to evade it, but the attack sent molten rock and wind pressure towards him along with a big amount of spiritual energy forcing him off his flying sword. He was flung to the ground making a loud booming sound as he hit the hard ground and created a small crater in the process. Matt could feel his bones quivering from the impact, this was the strongest hit that he had taken since getting to this world.

People noticed the giant that was crushing down from the sky, the huge thing landed a bit away from the city walls. The giant monster gave out a loud roaring sound and then charged in the direction that Zhang Dong got sent flying towards. The man in question gripped his head that had blood coming out of it, it was the biggest headache that he ever experienced. People gasped as they saw the friendly cultivator down on the ground, he didn't look too good and the fire monster was running towards him. But then they saw blinding white light from the spot Zhang Dong crashed in, the light started expanding upwards and to the sides. The enemy cultivators didn't know what he was doing but they wouldn't let him finish so they made the fire golem throw another punch, its giant hand producing sonic booms and tossing dirt and debris everywhere.

Chapter 47

Another blast occurred as something collided with the giant's rocky fist. The force from the collision made everyone tremble in the vicinity, making them stop with the fighting as they looked in shock at the lava giant. They could see its extended rocky fist, stretched out as it was trying to throw a right hook. The cultivators then saw a slightly smaller fist pushing against the boulder one. It was a fist made from lightning energy and it belonged to the cultivator in white. He had transformed into a white lightning giant, he was slightly shorter than the rocky giant but he was still huge.

Zhang Dong was inside of his Avatar transformation technique, panting and wheezing. He had to increase the size of the skill to something that would drain his reserves quite fast. The blood that ran down his forehead evaporated inside the skill as his body turned to lightning. He grasped the lava giant's extended fists as the cultivators inside were probably shocked. He pulled the monster closer and clogged it with his left sending it tumbling backward while lava and fire sprayed everywhere.

What followed was a good old fashioned brawl. The fire monster didn't lose its balance but moved in to hit the lightning giant back as well. It managed to connect to the torso which sent Zhang Dong backward as he almost flew back onto his big butt. He managed to balance himself with his feet then went back to punching and kicking his enemy.

You might think that two giants at about fifteen meters of height would be slow and lumbering. But these two were producing sonic booms each time they made a punch, you could guess how much power there was behind a fist that size if you added speed too it. The two were about equally matched, though the white giant was a bit more nimble while the lava rock one was more sturdy.

The other cultivators that were near the battle zone backed away and the fighting stopped for now. The two sides started watching the frantic battle each side cheering their respective seniors to win it. Both sides kind of knew that this duel would be the deciding factor of the coming battle, it could go either way as the two looked evenly matched for now.

Zhang Dong was keeping up but he felt like vomiting blood right now, time was passing and he wasn't really making much progress versus this rocky monstrosity. The more time he spent in this form the worse it would get, he had a limited timer and he didn't know if the enemy could hang on longer. It was still three against one though, so he would probably be the one running low on spiritual energy so he needed to end the fight fast.

Both of the giants collided once more, their hands grasping into each other. Zhang Dong in avatar form pushed his fingers into the rocky golem's and started squeezing. You could hear lightning crackling and rocks sizzling with lava as the two were now pitting their pure strength against each other. The lava monster started pushing Matt back, it had more mass behind that rocky body. The white giant started getting pushed down, going down to its knees while the other monster clenched its fingers down and pushed slowly trying to rip them apart with all its might.

The cultivators inside were sweating profusely while remaining in their positions, they never thought it would be possible for someone in core formation at the middle stage to fight against their formation like that. But it looked like he was running out of steam so they pushed their cultivations to the brink trying to crush the white giant's hands. But suddenly they felt a mighty force pushing against then, the lightning construct gritted its teeth and gave out a strange shout that sounded like loud thunder. It slightly increased its size as it pushed back against the combined might of the three cultivators that tried to resist but soon they got pushed back, their giant's hands were crushed to dust, fire, and lava dripping out.

Zhang Dong pushed his cultivation to the limit, forcing his avatar transformation to the limit as he pulverized the lava giant's rocky digits. He didn't let up as he delivered a swift kick to where a person would have his crown jewels, cracking the spot in the process. The enemy colossus was on the defense as it tried to protect its large body, but the lightning giant managed to plunge its fist through the defense into the exact spot that the enemy cultivators were sitting in.

The lava construct started crumbling, the last hit connected injuring the cultivators inside. The three of them flew out while vomiting copious amounts of blood. They looked terrible as they all hit the ground, tumbling for a good amount before coming to a stop.

Zhang Dong canceled the technique quickly, his vision was going blurry as he felt weak. He had used up most of his spiritual energy to defeat the other giant, this had left him weak and tired. The battle wasn't over quite yet as the Tsai Patriarch was still standing, while the other two members were out cold and deprived of most of their spiritual Qi.

"You damn Zhang Clan whelp! Do you think you can defeat me? You will die, everyone from this clan has to die!"

While the cultivator was shouting some cliche bad guy lines at him, he was slowly gathering his strength. This would probably be the last one, after this, he could rest.

"How about you go choke on a d*ck, you discount Fire Lord!"

His body hurt everywhere, he might have been taking the form of lightning but every hit that he took while fighting those three bastards left a mark behind. He was quite pissed off at the moment, maybe it was the rage that he felt or something else but the tension that he felt before he started battling was gone, replaced with something else. Tsai Fang pulled out a sword and charged after processing what the younger cultivator shouted at him. His attack was met with a crackling lightning sword, that when it collided with the enemy weapon. Sparks were thrown up into the air, the sizzling of heated metal could be heard.

The two fighters swung their weapons against each other, both managing to slice flesh as the wounds on the two increased. They were quite drained from the previous exchange of techniques so this was more a battle of skill and perseverance. The Tsai Clan patriarch won out in experience but Zhang Dong had a stronger body and cultivation technique that even though it was in the middle stage, still outperformed Tsai Fang's late stage cultivation that was of a lower grading. You could say that he made up his lack of fighting experience with higher stats.

The two pushed against each other weapons but there was one problem. Zhang Dong's lightning sword wasn't really a graded weapon, it was a skill that he constantly had to pump his Qi into. So after a moment, the Tsai Fang's sword started wining out as it pushed into the thundering plasma. Both fighters were tired as they pushed each other weapons against each other in a battle of strength. But just at the moment where the discount fire lord was about to push through Zhang Dong's sword, he felt a discharge of lightning Qi run through his body as the lightning sword technique detonated momentarily stunning him for a fraction of a second.

This was enough for Zhang Dong to deliver a lightning punch to the man's jaw, teeth with blood flew in the air as the cultivator in red retreated in surprise. Or at least he tried but instead, he felt pain in his gut as a kick landed there right after, propelling him backward into some boulders that he smashed in the process. The momentum was on his side now so Matt threw himself on his enemy, punches and kicks rained down on Tsai Fang that was quickly turned into a punching bag.

He tried retaliating, his face all bloodied the scar on his cheek even bigger than before. He realized that he made a mistake, the cultivator in front of him wasn't letting up and the attack formation that he and the other cultivators used had drained him of most of his Qi as well. He needed to run, he tried throwing a magical treasure that would help him achieve just that. Yet the cultivator in white was using some strange martial arts as he wrapped his legs around his neck and while they were going down to the ground he started yanking on one of his arms. Tsai Fang could hear a snapping sound as his arm broke due to the submission hold Zhang Dong implemented, he screamed out in pain but then got clobbered in the mouth once more almost passing out due to that.

Matt looked down on the man he was holding down with one hand, he was on top of him, his last hit had incapacitated his opponent as he wasn't moving. He had won the fight, his enemy was bruised and battered. He could probably end it right here right now, one good punch in the right spot would put this man out of his misery. He was angry, he wanted to resolve this situation peacefully with the least bloodshed as possible but instead, he was forced by the circumstances to fight for his life. He raised his fist upwards, lightning energy coursing through it. The man below tried to say something but just gurgled due to his missing teeth and blood inside his mouth. He looked pitiful, but there was still defiance in his eyes as he looked at the fist.

Zhang Dong clenched his fist, aiming it at the head. But he hesitated, he looked at the miserable old man in front of him. He didn't know who he was, he got pulled into this whole fiasco by circumstance. But as Matt was wavering with his decision Tsai Fang took his chance. He was an experienced fighter and he had crawled his way up by killing his enemies without mercy. He didn't have any second guesses as he grasped his sword from the side with his uninjured hand and plunged it directly at Zhang Dong's face. This turn of events surprised the cultivator in white, he didn't know if it was just his body's reaction to the attack or due to the skills he got implanted into his mind.

He dodged to the left, a big gash appearing on his cheek while his fist descended downward. A loud boom could be heard and a lot of dust got kicked up into the air. What greeted Zhang Dong after he punched down was a body with a missing head and a massive hole in the ground behind it. He had reacted to the threat of dying by punching downward and killing the Tsai Clan patriarch in the process. He just looked with a blank expression on his face at the dead body his hands trembling while blood dripped down from them.

Tsai Fang Slain ( Core Formation Late Stage ) Earned 185000 Spirit Points.

Chapter 48

The whole place was smoking a bit, so the people around couldn't see what happened just yet. Zhang dong looked at his bloodied hand then back to the dead corps of the cultivator he killed. He jumped back, his heart pounding as he looked on in horror at the man that he killed. He felt all kinds of emotions right now sadness for the fact that he took a life, anger for the fact that the man left him no choice as it was a do or die situation, fear for not knowing what he should do now also a bit of relief as the battle was over.

He shook his hand, the man's blood still dripping down from them. He started rubbing them, shaking his palms around as he tried to get the red liquid off. He had to get a grip, he might have defeated the strongest cultivator from the bunch but there were still others around. He closed his eyes while breathing in slowly as he tried to calm down his heart rate, somehow getting a grip on himself. He tossed his emotions to the back of his head while looking away from the spot he defeated the man, fatigue washing over him as he finally felt a backlash from using his skills too much.

About this time the area became clear off all the smoke and debris, the people could finally see what transpired. They spotted the cultivator in white standing upright, with his back turned to where someone laid on the ground. On closer inspection, they noticed that the person there was just a headless body, by the robes it was the Tsai Clan Patriarch dead and unmoving.

"Oh no! The Patriarch is dead!"

The Tsai Clan members shouted as they looked at the body in horror.

"Everyone look, those Tsai Clan elders have lost!"

The Zhang Clansmen shouted so everyone could hear them as they looked at the person that was standing next to the body. Their so-called clan member had defeated the core formation experts single-handedly. About at the same time, Zhang Jin flew back on his sword, he looked a bit beaten up but he was still standing. He had a cultivators head in his hand that he tossed down, it belonging to the elder he pulled away previously. He looked around while holding onto his bloodied saber then pointed it at the passed out cultivators that Zhang Dong knocked out.

"Zhang Clan members hear me, Attack!"

The elder went after the defeated core formation cultivators, he didn't want to risk them getting back up. He could feel that Zhang Dong was quite drained, so he thought that this would be the least he could do after the younger man defeated the strongest fighters on his own.

The invading people looked on in horror as all of their leaders were slain before their eyes, the enemy core formation seniors were still out there and one was powerful enough to defeat five of their best fighters on his own. The cultivators that were next in the leadership role quickly shouted out, ordering people to quickly retreat to their own cities.

"Everyone fall back! The elders are dead, retreat towards our domains!"

They didn't come here with all of their resources, they still had some powerful cultivators back home to protect them. So they turned tail and escaped while the Zhang Clan people continued firing arrows and cannons at them constantly, they even left the protection of their city walls invigorated and out for blood after they witnessed the huge battle that the cultivator in white had with the Tsai clan elders.

Zhang Dong gave out a sigh, his hands finally stopped shaking as he looked to the corps on the ground once more. He walked up to it, thinking that the whole thing was a bit surreal. Just about a month ago he was back in his own apartment playing some video games while now he had punched a man's head clean off.

*Not sure how I should feel about this, it was him or me... he didn't give me much choice...*

He explained to himself while the bearded cultivator elder showed up behind him. The person looked like a grizzled fighter, with that scar on his face, the beard only adding to his looks. He slowly moved next to Zhang Dong and also looked at the dead Tsai Clan Patriarch with disdain in his eyes.

"He got what was coming to him, well done Dong'er"

Matt almost tripped after the man called him donger again, he had no idea who he was but by the way he was calling him he had to be someone from his family. Both his parents were dead, or so said the system window that he read before. His mother Zhang Biyu and father Zhang Peng, this guy was called Zhang Jin and looked old. He was either his grandfather or an uncle from either side of the family, he didn't have any nifty family tree anywhere to help him out though.

"Ah yes, I haven't been to the clan for a long time, surprised that you recognized me."

He said while trying to prod for the man's identity a bit.

"How could I have not recognized my own grandson! You have turned into a fine young lad."

He placed his hand on Zhang Dong's shoulder and nodded while looking at him, with praise in his eyes. He was really proud that his grandson managed to return and save the clan in its darkest hour. Plus he was an expert that greatly exceeded him as well, he was just the person that this clan needed now.

"It's just a shame that your parents couldn't be here to see you grow up, such a shame."

The whole thing was kind of awkward as the old man started reminiscing about the old days while the person next to him had no idea what he was talking about. It would have been great if he had the memories of this Zhang Dong but there was nothing besides the short bio in the system.

"Ah yes, a shame... During my travels, I suffered a bit of a setback, so my memory from my childhood is a bit hazy... I don't remember much about the clan after I left for my journey."

He tried thinking out an excuse for him not recognizing people in the clan too well, he didn't really want people to start popping up left and right that he couldn't recognize.

"Ah is that so... Well, at least you remember your old gramps!"

The man chuckled and pulled Matt into a bearhug, making his caught as he was still a bit injured from the previous fight.

"Ah yes, sure grandpa..."

Zhang Jin squatted down and removed the Tsai Clan leader's storage ring handing it to Zhang Dong with a smile on his face.

"I'll collect the rest of the storage rings from those bastards you defeated, how about I let the juniors sort the stuff out in them, we'll see if there is some good stuff in there for you later."

Matt called his flying sword to himself, as Zhang Jin took a glance at it his eyes sparkled as it was quite the nice looking flying sword it was a lot better than the one he had. But there were also all the flying swords that he retrieved from the fallen core formation cultivators, this old man was quite swift with looting the corpses.

"Well, don't think there is a reason to chase after them though... Also, there was a pair of kids I met on the way here, those guys are escaping in another direction so they should be fine though."

Zhang Dong said as he looked at the retreating cultivators and also at the ones that were running out of spirit spring city, ready to slaughter everything in sight. The escaping invaders had a head start though, so it would be hard to catch up unless he or his grandpa helped out on their swords. Zhang Dong had enough of fighting for one day though, he just wanted to lay down and stare at the ceiling.

"Oh? If that's what you want."

Zhang Jin's booming voice filled the area, ordering everyone to stand down and just salvage the siege weapons for resources. This old man was quite materialistic as he also ordered everyone to retrieve any usable arrows, nothing was to be left on the battlefield. He also informed some foundation establishment cultivators to go pick up the kids. Afterward, he turned towards the city and flew ahead of Matt that was trailing behind, he wobbled in the air before deciding to use one of his healing pills. This somewhat refreshed his tired body but didn't really do anything for his spirit. His clothes had mended themselves once more, he wished he could add that enhancement to his aching body.

*Well, I guess I don't need to worry about ever looking like a hobo.*

He was finally here, the city that he was supposed to go too. But what was he supposed to do here now? He didn't really know but first, he needed to take a bath, to wash off this stench of blood.

Chapter 49

The battle was over, some people had died some were injured and some were even missing. Cultivators were running back and forth all over the place as the City became busy again. Everyone that was hiding came out, people were looking for their loved ones some leaving the city in the search as there were a lot of people that didn't make it before the city was sealed off. People were rejoicing, people were crying a plethora of emotions was seen as the city got revitalized.

A lot of focus was placed on the cultivator in white that called himself Zhang Dong. Some older clan members could vaguely recall someone by that name that used to live here, but that was a long time ago. But even though they didn't know the man, they knew that he was probably going to be a big player in their clan. He had more or less singlehandedly saved the clan from extinction or a life of slavery. They had sparkles in their eyes as they looked at him flying through the air, their elder Jin next to him. The man in question was trying hard not to scratch the back of his neck as he felt the thankful gazes of the masses.

*Guess I'll be staying here for a while? Or should I leave? I can probably leave whenever I want... but if I leave will another clan attack them again when they find out?*

He felt tired after the battle had ended, the city was bigger than Moonlight city. He could see many eastern styled buildings spreading in all directions, they were all in various shapes and sizes. There were also many bodies of water spread around the city, those were probably the springs that the town was known for. The city was more or less circular in shape, massive walls surrounded it from all sides. There were gates placed on all four sides of the city, the east, west, north, and south gate. The city started out flat, but the further you went in the elevation of the buildings increased. Right in the middle of the city, you could see a massive structure, it was at an elevated point and was surrounded by another large wall. There were three towers build into the wall, placed on what looked to be boulders or small mountain peaks and you could see some structures on those peaks.

Inside after you passed the gate you could see more eastern styled buildings placed around the wall in the inner part. Right in the middle, there was a giant spring, it looked more like a lake at this point. In this spring there was another hill and on that hill, there was a castle-like structure. There were bridges going to this structure from the three mountain peaks, plus stairs leading up from the main gate this looked to be the main area of the Zhang Clan. There were various basins with water build into the castle structure and water was running down from them into the lake below. Forming many waterfalls in the process, the soft sounds of water and fish could be heard all around.

The whole City was quite large, it was many times larger than what Matt was us too. He and Zhang Jin landed in the main Clan abode in the middle of the city. If there was one thing that this world had to offer, it's the wonderous sights. The view from here was breathtaking as he could see the whole city. This place seemed rather peaceful and quiet, koi fish were swimming around adding to the tranquility.

"Ah, this is probably the first time you are here. Only the core members are allowed to enter the inner sanctum, also you were just a young lad back there. Though you seem to have retained your youthful looks."

Matt had no idea what his pseudonym Zhang Dong was in this clan, he knew that his father was supposed to be some kind of elder while his mom died while giving birth and that he left over 10 years ago.

"Also a shame about what happened to your father, that monster came out of nowhere. It was truly heroic what Peng did, he saved a lot of lives that day. But let's not bring up old wounds, I'm glad that you are back Dong'er"

Zhang Jin patted Zhang Dong on the shoulder while the man in question's face twitched at the mention of Dong'er. The man realizing what a silly naming choice this was and now he was stuck with it for his life.

*Can you change your name in this world? If I join a more powerful clan only my last name will change...*

The name of the leading clan popped into his head as he was thinking about changing his name. It was the Long clan, he would be getting an even sillier name if someone got him to join that one. He coughed into his hand and turned to Zhang Jin a neutral expression on his face as usual.

"Ah sorry, I seem to have forgotten many things about the clan, but that beast that murdered my father is now dead, it won't be bothering anyone else."

Zhang Jin perked up at that, his son had been avenged by his grandson. He had carried the shame of not being able to protect his own child, then losing his grandson as he vanished from the clan never to be seen again. But now he was back and he was on the level of the old Patriarch, plus he was still very young he probably didn't yet reach his peak!

"You just made this old man's day, it's truly a blessing Dong'er. I would really like to introduce you to the rest of the elders and family members, but first... we have to talk about other things."

The man moved to the side of Matt and looked out into the city, people were running around, injured were getting brought in and resources were getting gathered. The old man played around with his long beard, he looked like he was thinking about something while looking into the distance.

"Zhang Dong, become this Clan's new Patriarch!"

Matt's face twitched as he stepped back, the man had just arrived today and now he was told to run the place.

"Wait, what? You want me to be the Patriarch?"

"Yes, I'm sure you have heard about what had transpired. Most of our senior members have died, even quite a bit of the core and inner members of the junior generation are gone now. Your appearance gives hope to our Clan!"

"Wait, I have no idea how to lead... how can I be the Patriarch of this clan, I don't even remember how things work here...Why don't you be the Patriarch instead?"

The old man chuckled while patting his grandson's shoulder.

"Oh, you don't need to worry. You don't really need to do much as the Patriarch, the juniors will handle most of the things. The other clans just need to see that the Zhang Clan has a powerful leader again, you can just cultivate in freedom and let the others do the bothersome things. I'm not as strong as you, people wouldn't accept that. Also having a young leader that has a bright future ahead of him will invigorate the clan members!"

The man started laughing kind of not taking a no for an answer from his 'grandson'. The gears started turning in his head as he thought about some things they should take care of.

"You just relax and leave everything to your old gramps here, you just cultivate and get stronger. I'll assign you a junior member to lead you around the premises they'll explain everything in more detail."

While Matt was thinking on a way to decline the offer the old man was in his own world, not really listening to what this grandson of his had to say. He soon stormed off somewhere while Zhang Dong had a perplexed look on his face, things were happening too fast.

*What is that old geezer doing, doesn't he just want to dump the responsibility of the clan on me instead?*

He gave out a big sigh and crossed his arms over one another as he looked out at the city. The scenery was beautiful, this place sure looked like one that you would retire in. The spiritual energy also felt a lot denser around this spot he was in, probably something to do with those springs around. After a moment he heard some footsteps and a person that looked to be in his early 20's appeared before him. He was wearing a scholar robe and was wearing a strange hat. The robe was quite long and didn't look like it was meant for fighting, the boots the man as wearing were bent upwards, reminding Matt of jester shoes.

"Senior Uncle Dong! , Elder Jin... uh, Grand Elder Jin told me to guide you to your quarters!"

The man said before tripping on his long robe as he was frantically running at Matt, looking quite tense. He slid forward on the slippery marble ground towards him, his face down and the hat falling off as he came to a stop.

"Uh... you okay there buddy?"

He didn't know if he should laugh at the man tripping over his own robe, but the scene of the blunder made him feel a bit less tense for some reason. He seemed to forget about the bloody battle that he just had. Matt helped the younger man up to his feet, which the man was surprised by, thanking his Senior uncle by kowtowing several times and apologizing. This made the man laugh due to the comedic way the other was acting.

"Pff... okay, okay. Guide me to my quarters"

The two soon left, the Patriarch to be was now getting lead around the main Clan building and taking in the exotic sights. While this was happening the other clans were getting the news of the Zhang Clan surviving the onslaught of the other powers with the help of one specific cultivator. The whole area was in a buzz as everyone wanted more info about the new player that was strong enough to defeat so many core formation experts. The two teens were rescued as well as they met up with their Clan members and were told the good news, their eyes sparkling in anticipation and reverence as they heard about the big battle that took place in front of their city.

Chapter 51

Matt opened his eyes, a small boy was poking his thigh. He recognized this child as it was his nephew, he looked around noticing that he was in the back yard that belonged to his cousin. He didn't know how he got here but the youth was holding on to a ball and he wanted to play. He could see some other family members around as he stood up from his chair. The boy smiled and started kicking the ball towards him while he just kicked it back. The boy miskicked to the side that made the ball tumble away from him, so Matt decided to go after it as it was still closer to where he was.

He bent over to pick it up, but then when he turned around there was no one around anymore. The whole place looked devoid of life, his family members nowhere to be seen. He tried calling out but no one replied, then he noticed something. The ball that he was holding had a strange texture to it, he looked down to see that he was holding on to a man's head. The head belonged to the man that he had slain not so long ago, tears of blood were coming out of the dead looking eyes that gazed at him with disgust. He screamed out in shock waking up to find himself in the same pool that he had dozed off before.

He panted a bit while grasping his chest for air, not much time had passed since he had entered this room and no one came to bother him. He gathered his thoughts and stood up, the water running down his muscular body as he grasped a tower that was on the side. He gave out a sigh while gathering his thoughts trying to forget about what happened today.

*Uh, still not used to this shit."

He frowned while walking back to the main bedchambers, pulling up his status screen to focus his thoughts at something else.

Name : | Zhang Dong
Affiliation : | Zhang Clan
Spirit Points : | 192084
Cultivation Base Qi : | Core Formation [Middle Stage 5%] (Lightning Core)
Cultivation Base Body : | Foundation Establishment [Great Circle 0.5%] (Silver Body)
Techniques : | Lightning Qi cultivation art, Silver Body Arts, Thunderlight Sword, Thunder Movement Art...
Dao : | Dao of Heavenly Lightning, Dao of Smithing and Crafting
Other : | Senior Aura

*Guess none of those other core formation cultivators died, only got those points for the fire lord guy...*

He didn't manage to cripple any of the other elders in that fight, he didn't get any spirit points for most damage done to the enemy either as you tended to get in some games. Zhang Jin had finished off the defeated cultivators, but the one that he took out at the start had gotten away, not like he really cared that much for them. He took out the ring that he got from the big baddie and scanned it with his spiritual sense, discovering quite a bit of spiritual stones in there. There were even some middle-grade ones in there, but just a handful. If he absorbed those he could probably get the next level of the crafting abode, which would let him make earth grade weapons and clothes.

There were also some beast cores in there, some cultivation manuals and a couple of weapons. He pulled out a spear and tried to examine it.

Grand Fire Spear Earth Lower Grade

He wondered how much he would gain in his body tempering technique if he absorbed a weapon that was above the grade it was currently in. Previously it went up by 20% if he used high-grade weapons while being in the middle stage, so it should be at least that, might be more as this time around it was a weapon that was not just one small grade above but a whole realm above.

*Should I try it? But it takes a while to absorb what if someone walks in?*

He shook his head as he was still new to this place, he needed to figure out how he stood with this so-called Zhang Clan of his. He was supposed to become it's Patriarch apparently, so he tried to remember what a Patriarch is actually supposed to do. From what he knew, they were the leaders of the Clans, some were hidden in the background and didn't show themselves to the public while some took an active part in the Clan's business. His grandpa told him that he shouldn't worry too much and that he wouldn't really need to run things.

Matt went back to fiddling with the spear, but instead of absorbing he dumped some points to level up his apprisal skill. He wanted to know if anything would show up and it was just 100 SP for the first one. Nothing seemed to change at first, but after he kept looking at it another window popped up.

Name | Grand Fire Spear
Grade : | Lower
Attribute : | Fire
????? | ?????
????? | ?????
????? | ?????
????? | ?????
????? | ?????

*Oh, it did work. There are more stats to see now... could have figured out the attribute through the name... The rest are just question marks guess I need to invest more points to see the rest...*

The next level cost 500 and the next one 1000, he also dumped in 2000 points to get another one in.

Name | Grand Fire Spear
Grade : | Earth Lower
Attribute : | Fire
Durability : | Medium
Condition : | Fair
Advanced Grade : | C-
????? | ?????
????? | ?????

*C-? is this school or something... though that would mean that it's slightly below average if it goes from F to A ... should I dump 5000 SP to get the next level... uh... think I'll stop for now, I'll see how many points I have left after I clear out those spirit stones... also Zhang Jin said that he would give me more of the spoils later... He looked stingy though, hope he doesn't scrooge out on me. Unlocked Durability and condition as well, guess that will come in handy when buying things. Don't want a weapon that will break after one swing even if it has high attack power.*

Matt placed the weapon back into the storage ring and started examining some other items. His Crystalline Flying Sword came out with a pristine condition with an advanced grade of A+, guess it was on the top end of high grade flying swords. He also brought up one of his skills, wondering if it would show any other statics now.

Name : | Lightning Qi Cultivation art (Upgradable)
Grade : | Immortal Low
Attribute : | Lightning
Advanced-Grade : | B
Qi Limit | High
???? | ????

The statics were self-explanatory, the Qi Limit just meant that he had a big gas tank, guess the higher the more Qi related attacks he could do. The thing that was the most peculiar was the 'Upgradable' part in the brackets, he didn't remember it being there before. He hovered his finger over that and it took him to a new menu with some more options now. But it looked like a skill tree in a game this time around, with only two options for the first branch.

He didn't have many options, one only said Empowered Lightning Qi Cultivation art and the other said Gray Lightning Qi Cultivation art. It kind of made it seem like it was a choice between two major schools that he had to take. He hovered his fingers to see if there was another explanation and there was.

Empowered Lightning Qi Cultivation | A superior version of the Lightning Qi cultivation art, further upgrades unlock other options.
Gray Lightning Qi Cultivation | A darker path unlocks for the cultivator that follows this cultivation art.

*I guess the gray one is the dark side choice... Though shooting black lightning at people would be cool... hope I won't get pink lightning with the other choice...*

He didn't want to go with some kind of evil cultivation art, then end up looking like a wrinkled up raisin. He also wondered if this was actually a good thing. Should he upgrade his cultivation art, or get a new one later. The system said that this would last him up to the great circle of core formation, he would have to get a new one when he wanted to get to the next level. But the prices for nascent soul cultivation manuals were quite high, plus he had to reach the great circle stage first and level up his body tempering skill too.

He looked at the skill tree from the empowered lightning qi cultivation art, he could see a skill tree leading up to the Nascent Soul. He just needed to unlock two of them to get to the Nascent soul one. There were even color options for golden, violet and azure. The colors probably meant something as the Nascent Soul would be in that color later on.

*Hm, guess I'll decide on that later on... *

Also, he recalled the battle from today, then the dream he had and decided to look up something else in the cash shop.

Void Mind | 20000 Spirit Points | The cultivator abandons his emotions for a sharper mind, nothing can faze a cultivator that studies this technique.
Tranquil Mind | 30000 Spirit Points | This mind technique helps keep the cultivator's demons at bay and helps to calm down his emotional state. It improves the state of mind to keep calm under pressure.
Berserker's Mind | 15000 Spirit Points | Exponential increases the cultivator's battle strength with the side effect of entering an enraged state.

He focused on the tranquil mind technique, he could really use that. He realized with the last battle that he wasn't getting accustomed to this world fast enough, the problem was his attitude. He didn't have that killer personality and a lot of times he froze, not knowing what to do. During this fight, he hesitated almost causing him to die in the process. He felt a bit disgruntled about killing the guy, but he knew that he was a typical murderous cultivator with a high body count. If he wanted to improve, he would have to change his mindset. He would probably have to take lives in the future, but he didn't want to end up as a senseless murderer.

The rest of his current skills just showed the advanced grade and instead of the Qi Limit it just showed had a marker for how much spiritual energy you needed to use the skill. Like his javelin skill was quite low, while his avatar transformation was at high. He would probably be buying some stuff after he got the rest of the things those enemy cultivators had, or at least what the Zhang Clan gramps didn't pocket himself.

A note from Kuropon

So was thinking, do you guys (the readers) want to vote on the color of the lightning he'll get later one, guess those three choices can be expanded on. Though I'm leaning towards violet or gold ,as azure is kind of plain.

Guess I'll put the link Here.

Chapter 52

He wanted to start absorbing spirit stones and spending all of them on upgrading his cultivation, as well as getting that mind skill to ease his troubled mind. But at about that moment the doors to his new penthouse apartment opened up and his good old gramps walked out with two people that were closer to Zhang Dong's age group. The man looked a bit stern and calculative while the woman looked somewhat motherly with a smile on her face.

He almost did a business greeting in the form of a handshake while looking at the other male from the group, but then placed his hands behind his back and gave the people a nod. The two clasped their hands as they did a formal greeting and didn't talk, they let Zhang Jie do that instead.

"This is Zhang Ya and Zhang Kuo, they are my disciples and can be trusted, we need to talk about a couple of things."

The two looked up at Zhang Dong, trying to feel him out.

"Ah, I guess you want to talk about me becoming the next Patriarch, are you sure about that Gramps?"

The two people twitched a bit after they heard the man call their clan's only core formation elder gramps. The man in question just grasped his belly and laughed out loud in a jolly voice.

"No one ever called me gramps before, but yes it's about that. Some members are against you becoming the new Patriarch, they don't want someone from the side family to be in that position."

The man shrugged, kind of not caring about what those other clan members thought, he didn't put much weight in the purity of the blood, all Zhang Clan members were equal in his eyes. He was more interested in their character, drive and actual battle prowess.

"Well, not like they can do anything about it, they are mostly hot air. If they offend you in any way, be sure to give them a good thrashing!"

"Also Ya and Kuo will help you out with your Patriarch duties, if you need anything just give them a call, they'll be your guides around the clan grounds don't need to worry about making these two work hard!"

The man laughed some more before giving the two people behind him a pat on the shoulder. The female just smiled while the man rolled his eyes slightly.

"It's a pleasure to meet our Clan's savior, it's going to take some time to set up the ceremony and banquet."

Matt tipped his head to the side while looking at the woman, question marks appearing next to his head.

"Ceremony, banquet?"

This time the man stepped out and replied.

"Yes, the Patriarch candidate is adorned with the title during the ceremony, all the core clan members have to be present during it. After the title is bestowed we host a banquet, then it's customary for the Patriarch to visit the city so that everyone can witness his grand appearance."

While the man was talking the woman slowly went behind Matt and started patting him down. He noticed that she had a measuring tape in her hands.

"We need to prepare your robes for the ceremony, your white battle robes aren't suited for the festivities also the color isn't very eye-catching."

The woman said while chuckling to herself and doing her measurements, her eyes were sparkling as she did it making it seem that she was really into this task.

"We still have to make repairs to the grand formation, account for the loss of lives in the attack and prepare for any further intrusions."

"Do you think someone will attack us again?"

Matt asked.

"No Senior, we should have eliminated the core fighting strength of the clans that attacked us, the Tsai Clan will probably try to hold up in their domain, the Wu clan lost their Patriarch that was their strongest cultivator the Wong clan retained some of their cultivators but don't think we will see them again. Due to Senior showing his power, the other Clans will probably think twice before planing anything. We should be safe for now, unless one of the stronger clans or sects gets involved."

Matt just nodded while stretching his hands out so that the woman could measure his arms, she giggles when she managed to take the measurements of his biceps. He didn't really tense up like the last time a woman was touching him, guess the previous encounter did change him slightly.

"It will probably take about a month till the ceremony, you can just take your time and get used to living around here after it's official we'll talk about retaking our lost assets. I bet those bastards are shaking in their boots right now."

Zhang Jin said while clenching his hand. The clan had lost most of its assets and was chased out of cities that they were managing, one of them being Moonlight City that Matt previously visited. After a while, the measurements were done and the woman excused herself to prepare the ceremonial garb, the stern-looking man also excused himself leaving Zhang Dong and Jin in the room alone.

"I didn't want to say it next to the juniors, but you should prepare yourself for the future. This will be turbulent times for our Clan, we might have won the battle this time but we don't know what will happen next. The Dark Palm sect might be a problem later as well, they were the ones that forced our Patriarch to act in that failed expedition. But in their eyes we were just a tool that could be used, let's hope they order some other clans to finish the job instead."

The Zhang Clan was more or less a medium-sized clan, they had their territory but in reality, this belonged to the Dark Palm sect that was the real hegemon in the area. They used the clans to manage the cities and resources for them, taxing them for 'protection' and using that to grow their sect. There was no rule against clan members joining sects, it was common for them to do so as if they were deemed worthy they would inherit powerful cultivation skills. But the further you were on the ladder the more you were expected to put the sect on a higher pedestal than your clan or previous life. That was also the reason why most sects only recruited younger members as it was easier to indoctrinate the young.

"But you probably don't want me to prattle on all day, so I'll leave you be for now. Maybe if you look around your memory will return."

Zhang Jin said while heading out, but stopped after Matt asked him a question.

"Um, aren't you forgetting something?"

The man looked back at his grandson's face, he was squinting at him and looking at a certain place. He followed that gaze and noticed that he was eyeing his storage ring. This made him sweat a bit as he thought he could pull a fast one on his grandson that might be busy with getting to know the ropes around here.

"Oh, ho ho.... silly me... here..."

He tossed Zhang Dong a storage ring, just one as he did say that he would have some people sort through them. He scanned its content to see some more spirit stones and resources, it looked to have similar things to what the Tsai leader's ring had so he reckoned that was the stuff from those two other elders inside. He didn't spot the bow that one guy used that he choked out though, did he get away or was gramps holding out on him?

"Well, then my dear, loving grandson... grandpa will be leaving..."

"Wait... didn't one of them use a bow weapon..."

Old gramps twitched and caught a couple of times into his hand, before taking out another spatial ring and tossing it over.

"Oh, it was just such a nice bow, so I just couldn't resist... forgive your old grandpa."

The man laughed while looking at Zhang Dong that had a deadpan expression on his face as he pocketed the storage ring.

"You sure are a piece of work gramps... I'll make you something better than the bow, later on, just provide me some resources."

Matt knew that there were enough spirit stones in those rings to let him buy the next stage of the crafting abode, then he could make earth grade weapons next.

"Oh, you are also adept in the Dao of blacksmithing? What a talented grandson I have!"

The man just laughed while removing himself from the room as he got caught with his hand in the cookie jar, he would let Zhang Dong have some time to himself before seeing him again. The man in question just gave out a sigh while moving back to the room, he had to examine all the items and start absorbing the resources, it was time to level up!

A note from Kuropon

Merry Christmas everybody :3

Chapter 53

A pile of dust could be seen on the ground, it was the remains of the spirit stone that Zhang Dong had absorbed. He noticed that not every lower grade spirit stone gave him exactly ten points, they mostly ranged from seven to ten while the middle graded one gave him a hundred times that amount a pop. He now had quite enough points to spend on the crafting abode upgrade along with the tranquil mind skill which he did. He felt a slight migraine as the knowledge got injected into his brain once more, the process getting less painful each time.

The first thing he did after that was going to the ground, spring water around. He started cultivating this skill, hoping that it would relieve the stress he was feeling. He took a long breath then exhaled, his breathing slowing down as his body relaxed. His bodily functions slowed along with his breathing, the noises beside him getting quieter with each passing moment. He felt his spiritual energy inside his body, moving through his meridians. His mind was getting clearer with each passing moment, he was becoming one with the surroundings if someone were to enter they would have a hard time spotting him even if they were looking directly at him.

There wasn't anything grand happening, not flashy effects taking place. Matt just sat there, his breathing was nonexistent at this point as his head was void of any thoughts. He didn't feel fearful, angry or spiteful, he managed to reach a state of tranquility. He opened his eye, the day had turned to night as he stood up and looked outside. The city was covered in yellow lights, the springs were giving off a greenish hue as the light bounced off them.

"Well, it did calm me down."

He felt the stress levels declining significantly after he was done with his cultivating, even after he recalled the death of the man he slew, he still felt relaxed.

"I don't feel any different..."

He placed his thumb to his chin while doing a test, he recalled the night that the had with the busty cultivator. His lower area reacted to the stimulation, showing him that he still felt emotions. Asking your little brother was the proper way to get a feel for your emotions, yes...

"Hm, maybe it works more on negative emotions."

He wondered if he would be harder to anger now, but he would need to face an opponent to see if this technique would affect his fighting potential. Keeping calm under pressure was quite the big deal, he felt a lot calmer than before.

There were some things that he wanted to do, first buy the crafting abode, then see how well he could craft the earth ranked weapons. He also wanted to get his body tempering up a notch and then try to enhance his cultivation skill to the advanced version. With those boosts, he should probably be able to fight people even stronger than at the late stage of core formation. He had a month's time till the Patriarch ceremony was supposed to happen, so he had enough time to test things out.

After buying the abode he entered it, it had increased in size and he noticed that there were some other things he could do now. He could edit the items now, he could also reforge old ones. For instance, if he created a high grade sword, he could reforge it with some materials like the beast cores that would improve the advanced grade and add special effects. He did some tests on the cheap common grade items, he could keep boosting the weapon past an A+ into an S grade after that it would jump a grade. So he could well just keep upgrading one weapon that he liked, instead of forging new ones in the hopes of getting the stats he wanted.

He also needed a real weapon, he saw the limitations that his sword skill had if he paired it against an earth graded weapon. Also, he needed to constantly use up spirit energy to keep it going.

"A shame though, it's super cool looking."

He lamented that he had to give up on one of his favorite skills, who didn't like playing around with laser swords?

"Wait there might be a way though..."

He thought about something, what if he could find a weapon that he could combine his thunderligh sword skill? He started scrolling through the many sword diagrams he could get and after a while found something that could work. It was a longsword, it had some dragon patterns in the hilt while the blade looked to be made from some semi-transparent metal or crystal. The thing about it was that in theory it was supposed to absorb external sword skills letting the blade have a second form. So if you pumped in fire Qi into it, it would start forming a flame sword.

He bought it, but even just the schematics cost him about 10 thousand points as it was an earth grade weapon. He wanted to try crafting right there and then, but then he looked at the costs of the resources that had increased by quite a bit. He needed to dump at least 60 thousand into making one weapon so if he failed he would be losing quite a lot. He recalled the prices for earth grade weapons on the low end and they sold for about two thousand spirit stones up to four thousand, he would need to make a middle graded one just to break even.

*I bet this rhythm game will just get harder, I had it easy with the previous ones because my cultivation was already high. I should upgrade my cultivation technique and my body tempering before doing this.*

He had decided on upgrading his cultivation instead of buying a new one later, he was already used to it so changing midway could be detrimental. He pulled out one of the weapons he got from fighting the enemy clan members, it was a lower graded earth weapon. He started absorbing it as he did previously with the other weapons, it took longer as this was a higher graded weapon but even with just one it pushed his cultivation of the great circle to 40%. His eyes gleamed as he took out another weapon moving his cultivation up to 80%, his silvery body started changing color slightly as it started looking somewhat golden.

He took out another lower graded earth weapon, it slowly started dissolving into liquid metal and getting fused with his body. This time around the change was different. Many cracks could be seen on his body, they looked like spiderwebs. The sound was akin to steel bending and breaking as chunks of the first layer of his silvery skin started peeling off and drooping to the ground. The process took a while but afterward, his skin started gleaming with a golden hue.

Cultivation Base Body : | Core Formation [Early Stage 5%] (Golden Body)

He was drenched in sweat, the golden luster subsiding after a while. Matt started poking his body, trying to feel if anything was different but couldn't really tell. He should be sturdier now but he needed to test it out first. The bow that he had as a middle-grade weapon, plus he had the Tsai Patriarch's saber which was also a middle graded weapon. He had absorbed three lower-tier weapons that were the flying swords of the weaker cultivators he fought. He still had that fire spear though, so he took it out.

*Okay, hope this works...*

Matt grasped the spear closer to the pointed tip and pointed it at his hand. He then started pushing it into his palm, trying to check if it could pierce his now improved golden body. In theory, he should be able to tank the hits and to his surprise, the spear wasn't able to cut him. He tested it further, poking himself harder not getting more than a scratch. Then he took out the saber that was used against him previously and poked the tip with his finger. This weapon was a grade higher so after some poking he got cut, blood run onto the weapon while he pulled his hand away. The small cut healed itself rather quickly, showing that his body tempering technique wasn't just about defense there was some added regeneration involved.

He looked inside his storage ring, in it, he had three middle-grade weapons and 3 lower graded earth weapons, this wouldn't get him past to the middle stage but he didn't really want those weapons he wanted to craft one of his own for use.

*Man, this is one expensive technique... though the good thing about it is, that it's fast to level up if you have the resources.*

He absorbed the rest of the weapons and then left his crafting abode, for the time being, it was time to upgrade his cultivation technique. The bathing area looked like a good place to do this, the walls were enhanced to keep the spiritual energy inside and the water in there was rich in Qi. Plus he could open up the ceiling to take in any incoming lightning strikes, he sure hoped his new neighbors wouldn't mind some thunderous weather though.

In the middle of the pool, there was a platform to sit on, it was directly under the roof that could be opened and was probably used by the previous Patriarch to cultivate. Matt didn't know if the process would be painful or not, so he hesitated before clicking the Empowered Lightning Qi Cultivation upgrade and gulping afterward. The moment he did that, information started rushing into his brain again but this time around it was quite a bit more painful. Lightning energy started forming around him making rumbling sounds, the Qi inside of his body started getting switched out. The pale blue lightning that he used changed to a deeper blue color as you could see it getting discharged into the surroundings.

The upgrade cleansed his body from some impurities that were formed during the cultivation of a lesser graded method, making his sweat glands push out dark looking goo in the process. The usual vomiting of black blood soon followed, but it was a lot less than what happened when he first arrived in this world. The change was more or less contained and he managed to not pass out in the process.

Name : | Empowered Lightning Qi Cultivation art (Upgradable)
Grade : | Immortal Middle
Attribute : | Lightning
Advanced-Grade : | B+
Qi Limit | B+

Matt stood up and gathered some Qi into his fist, throwing a punch upwards into the opened ceiling and watching as his lightning attack got discharged. He sure felt a lot stronger now, he felt that he might be able to battle that volcano construct without needing to change into his avatar form and win. That monster battle power was in the upper echelons of the late stage, maybe on the cusp of getting into the great circle. In theory, he should be equal with core formation experts in the great circle realm, if he reached the late-stage himself he should be able to tussle with multiple of such opponents at once. He had the tropy cultivation art that broke the level boundaries, maybe if he upgraded it further he could go up against a weaker early-stage nascent soul cultivator.

About a day had passed since he got to this room, but he didn't really feel like leaving just yet as he started to get into the zone with his cultivation. He decided to sit down and gather up some energy, the process was more or less the same but the upgraded cultivation technique showed him a way to purify the energies in the surroundings even more. The purer the Qi he absorbed, the stronger he would be and this wasn't even the final form of this technique. Soon the sky turned black and lightning bolts rained into his cultivation/bathing chamber. The clan members thought they were getting attacked but after Zhang Jin went to check up, they noticed that it was their Patriarch to be. They could feel the terrifying energy fluctuations coming out of his chambers so there weren't willing to bother him to stop, the storm clouds only remained directly above the main building and thanks to the reinforced cultivation chamber the thunderous sounds were somewhat contained.

Chapter 54

After getting in the zone Zhang Dong breathed out, the area filled with lightning energy that crackled through the spring water. About a week had passed since he got here, he never left this room and didn't really feel like eating during his cultivation period. His cultivation had gone up to about 20 percent which was a lot slower than before but still was quite fast if he compared it to people around this world. He wondered if it was due to the level of his cultivation method which was in the immortal grade.

He decided to try crafting his weapon before heading outside as he was cooped up in this room for far too long, there were sights to see. So he entered his crafting abode, he had about a hundred thousand points left, this would allow him to have two goes at it at most. The things that he found in the spatial rings weren't really useful for crafting as for this sword he needed something called crystal alloy. After he got the position he needed to check if he could get some free crafting materials as he didn't want to spend all his points on those. He just wanted to boost his body refining skill further and maybe earn some dosh on the side.

He selected the weapon schematics and brought out the core of the Cthulhu look-alike monster to boost his chances of crafting, he even threw in some random foundation establishment monster cores hoping for the best. A new kind of music started playing and as he thought it was a lot more fast-paced than before. But thanks to his tranquil mind he wasn't tense, he started hitting the spots as he was directed to but even with his enhanced cultivation and body, he wasn't able to hit everything perfectly. Maybe due to luck or the number of cores that he dumped into this crafting, he managed to get a high grade one.

The weapon didn't look all that grand, but after he used his thunderlight sword technique the sword started to shine, literally. The weapon got coated in plasma-like light, electricity shooting from the blade. Matt swung it around and it made familiar wooshing noises, the blade was covered with bluish light and you could feel the spiritual energy emanating from it. He didn't really have anything he could test this weapon out on, be he felt that it would probably slice anything below a high graded earth weapon in half. He still had some points left, so he decided to dump five thousand into his apprisal skill again.

Name | Spirit Infusion Longsword
Grade : | Earth High
Attribute : | None
Durability : | High
Condition : | Perfect
Advanced Grade : | B
Special traits : | This weapon can fuse with the users Qi and increase its resistance and sharpness in the process. Works best if the user combines it with weapon constructs techniques.

He deadpanned at the added explanation window as it was more or less the same thing he got when he was buying the blueprint for it. He left his crafting dwelling afterward he had about 45 thousand points left but he would save those for later, he didn't really have anything he wanted to get. Maybe a technique that let him shoot beams out of his eyes? Or lightning breath? Those sounded a bit silly but probably would catch people off guard. Maybe he could come up with his own techniques if he tried, he had the Qi control down and he had that Dao of lightning knowledge. He also didn't have many healing pills left, so maybe it would be good to stock up on those for later use. He could regenerate somewhat, but that required him to use up his stamina. So maybe some Qi regeneration pills and stamina regeneration ones would be good too.

He also found out something after he examined his clothes after the special trait window got revealed he found out that was more to these clothes than just self mending. These white robes could actually change color and also blend into the environment if you didn't move for much. All of this could be done by inserting some spiritual energy and giving a special command to the robes. He could even upgrade them to add new functions, but it didn't come cheap.

Matt played around changing the color to black and red, then blue. Guess if he covered his head with the hood no one should recognize him as the cultivator in white if he ever needed to lay low. For the time being he changed it back to white as he walked out of the previous Patriarch's room, well now it was his. There were some people around so he just gave them a nod while passing, they seemed a bit tense as they saw him walking towards them but they just gave him the usual bow of respect.

He felt kind of strange walking around this place, everyone was showing him the utmost respect, no one talked to him. Was it rude to talk to someone of a higher status than you? Or were they just being shy, well not like he wanted to talk to the unknown people he was still an introvert that liked his peace and quiet. But now he had to take center stage on some kind of inauguration ceremony to his new position. It was already a big step for him that he didn't just refuse the position and leave this clan instead. But he would rather stay here, than wonder the lands as some rouge cultivator with no place to call home. Also, they had quite the nice springs around here, Matthew was quite fond of taking long relaxing baths.

After walking for a bit he noticed that someone was walking behind him when he turned around there was no one to be seen. He could feel the presence of two people behind the corner, they had been following him for some time now. Were they some bodyguards that were supposed to keep tabs on him or something? Were they assassins that were sent by some vengeful clan? Probably not as the two people were in the Qi Condensation level, he could probably snort them to death at this point.

"So, are you two going to come out. Or are you going to be following me for the rest of the day?"

He crossed his arms over one another while waiting, soon the stalkers were revealed. It was the brother and sister duo that showed a lot of courage while standing up to the Tsai clan pursuers. The two teenagers walked out while holding their heads down, probably not knowing what to say to the man in front of them.

"Oh, you're the two kids from last time, glad you are safe. Did you two want something from me?"

The two raised their heads, perking up a bit as they were glad that their uncle remembered them.

"Uncle Dong, we just wanted to thank you for what you did."

The girl said while bowing in a graceful fashion, Matt raised an eyebrow at the 'uncle' part. Most people would put Senior in there, or even in front of the uncle part, but those two made it seem like he was their real uncle. Did he have any siblings that he didn't know about?

"Uncle?"

He looked at the two children in front of him, trying to see the resemblance. They looked more or less like what your typical male lead and female lead in a cultivation world. They had dark hair, auburn eyes, the girl was a jade-like beauty, though to him she just looked pale. The boy had a serious-looking face, a bit too serious for his age.

"Ah yes, our father was your cousin..."

He noticed the change of tone when the girl's father was mentioned, she also slumped her shoulders a bit. The boy replied afterward instead.

"Our father went to the expedition with the previous Patriarch, they never returned..."

Zhang Dong placed his hand on the male's shoulder, not really knowing how to react so he kind of gave him an awkward pat on it.

"My condolences, I'm sure he was an honorable man. I'm sorry about not recognizing you two, I left the clan a while ago and my memories are a bit hazy from that time..."

He tried to change the uncomfortable subject, wondering what these two wanted from him.

"Great-grandpa Jin told us about that, no need to apologize uncle Dong!"

The boy exclaimed in a somewhat startled voice.

*Great-grandpa Jin? So that would mean that they are from his side of the family? That would mean...*

He figured out that him being from the side family, would mean that old gramps had a harem going for himself. He shuddered at the thought of having multiple family members that would start popping up from nowhere.

"Ah yes, Gramps... So, what do you two need?"

He rubbed his chin while looking at the kids that started fidgeting side to side a bit. It looked as if they were trying to ask about something but weren't sure how to do it. After a moment both of them looked at each other, nodded to themselves and dropped down to their knees to kowtow.

"Please Uncle Jin, take us in as your disciples!"

They both shouted in unison while their foreheads hit the marble floor. Matt started recalling that tribe he met in the forest, as they were fast to drop to their knees.

"Wait, what?"

Chapter 55

The two were prostrating themselves in front of the man, he was a bit dumbfounded by the whole thing. He didn't know anything about teaching people or guiding them in any way shape or form.

"You want me to be your master? I just met you two. Why would I even take you in as disciples?"

The two kept their heads down, not looking into his eyes while trying to get his approval.

"Please honorable Uncle, we want to be strong to protect the Clan. We almost lost everything before you arrived, we can't let it happen again."

The girl from the group did most of the talking, while the boy mostly just said yes and nodded his head, which only caused him to hit the ground with his forehead. The whole scene was quite uncomfortable for Matt as he had no idea how to even train those two if he agreed, also this would be quite the long term binding contract. Masters in the cultivation world tended to be treated as your own parents, sometimes they were put on an even higher pedestal. He didn't really want to be responsible for teaching them some strange things, which would get them killed later on.

"Don't think that's a good idea... I need to go take care of a couple of things... so see you around..."

He just bolted out of there, trying not to think about it too much. The kids would probably forget about it, leaving him alone. Also due to the fact that he didn't eat much for the past week when he was cultivating and making items, he was famished. He wondered if he should just go to the city and find himself a restaurant, or ask someone about food, he could probably get some here if he wanted. Matt was curious about the city though, it looked nice from the top of his peak top apartment. Would it be a problem if people recognized him in the streets? Though not many people had actually seen his face.

He looked around, there were some people here and there doing their thing. No one was really keeping tabs on him, he didn't have any bodyguards as no one in their right mind would want to attack a cultivator that could take out four core formation cultivators. He figured ol' gramps probably gave the order to not interfere in his business too much unless asked directly. Matt thought that he would probably get the rundown of the place only after he officially got the Patriarch spot.

For not he just hopped onto his sword and flew around the city a couple of times before coming down into an empty alleyway. He swapped the color of his robe to a brown one, this being quite common. He finished his disguise by covering his head with his hood, he also debated on putting on some cool shades to hide his eyes but have up on the idea. A cultivator with dark shades would just look out of place around here. Also, he could use his cultivation to mask his appearance somehow. If people tried looking at his face they would see it blur slightly, but that only worked for people below his strength level.

He mingled with the crowd, slipping from the empty alleyway. He Hit some stalls on the way, getting some noodles and slurping them as he continued to walk. There were quite a lot of things to see, from street performers playing on their zithers to various monuments and statues. He had spirit stones and regular money so he wasn't a scrooge as he tipped the street dancers while enjoying the day.

The day seemed quite peaceful, he walked into one of the larger restaurants that looked quite busy. By this time he knew how things worked in these types of places. The people with more money would get better treatment, in most restaurants the higher you were seated the greater your status was. So after flashing the serving lady some spirit stones he was guided upwards into a more peaceful booth where there weren't as many people around. He ordered something similar to kung pao chicken, though the paultry used for it had some spiritual Qi in it so the taste was somewhat better. Spirit Spring city also was quite famous for its spirit mineral water, so he ordered that with it instead of alcohol.

He thanked the cute serving girl that brought him his food and then started munching, the view outside the window reminded him a bit of the previous city he visited. He hoped that he wouldn't bump into some spoiled brats on his way out though, as this time around they would probably belong to the Zhang clan. It would be quite the sight to see if the future patriarch would get run down by his own clan members. The thought of brats made him recall the two kids that begged him to become their sensei, he wondered if that would even be possible. He brought up his system screen, by this time he was quite sure no one was able to see it beside him.

*Would this thing even help me with disciples and stuff like that, didn't it give me some prompt about clan building when I got here...*

This system was kind of wonky, it would sometimes hide things from him and only show them later. Was there some kind of trigger for it, maybe his power level counted or some steps needed to be taken to unlock things? He glanced at his system screen, it looked like a computer screen just hovering there. His eyes twitched as there was indeed a new icon there, it looked like a scroll with some Chinese symbols on it. He poked at it while wondering what was inside. As the window changed he could see that there wasn't much inside, but there were a couple of tabs. There was one for disciples when he clicked it the inside was just empty. There was also one for disciple candidates, that showed up with a red '!' mark. It looked like a friend invite, but there was more. He could see a window with some statics for both of them.

Name : | Zhang Liu
Age : | 16
Cultivation : | Qi Condensation 9th level
Potential : | B
Trust : | 70%
Alignment : | Chaotic Good

Name : | Zhang Xue
Age : | 15
Cultivation : | Qi Condensation 7th level
Potential : | B
Trust : | 75%
Alignment : | Neutral Good

He looked at the prompts and numbers, taken aback by the D&D styled alignment one. Also, the trust percentage was quite high, was me saving them enough to bring it up so high? The potentials were the same and quite high, B should probably be above average as you started off from F with the worst kind.

*I guess they have potential, but wait... if this is letting me see those stats... could it be possible to change their potential later?*

The system was quite overpowered it had really many functions, but it also needed a lot of points to run on he didn't think changing someone's actual inborn potential would come cheap.

*I do have all those manuals in my storage ring, they always appear after I buy skills and I have all the ones I got from the start too.*

He had all the materials he needed to teach people his skills, even the Dao of lightning passive skill had a big manual coming with it. The techniques had basic manuals for Qi condensation practitioners if it was feasible for them to learn a weaker version of it. Like his cultivation art went from the noobie stages up to the core formation stage. The stages you needed to take to go from Qi condensation to foundation establishment, forming your lightning Dao pillars were all explained. He also had the knowledge in his brain, so in theory, he should be able to teach plus if the system let him spend points on his disciples it would be even easier.

The two seemed like promising candidates, they were good kids and had high potential but he was still on the fence about the whole thing. He was never really good with people, to begin with, now someone wanted him to guide them while he himself didn't really have things figured out. But maybe this would also be a good way for him to come out of his shell. For now, he moved the thought to the back of his mind and went back to eating, he wasn't really in a hurry. He finished his meal but was still quite hungry so he wondered what he should order next while looking at the menu.

At the same time, he could hear a woman's scream followed by some plates breaking. When he turned around he could see some people sitting in a booth not far away from him, bothering the serving lady that was serving him before.

"Oh little missy, look what you did. You dropped all the food."

The man laughed while the girl was hiding her rear end behind the serving tray. Probably one of the men had touched her there.

"You perverts!"

The woman replied while fuming with anger.

Matt kind of facepalmed as these things kept happening around him, wherever he went there were some people in trouble. Some damsel or kids in distress. Did he really have to go over there, or could someone else handle this, weren't there any bodyguards around here?

One guy from there was in the foundation establishment level, probably the leader the rest were probably just his goons.

"Listen here girly, big bro here is a big shot in a big clan, you little Zhang clan can't hold a candle to it! Be glad that he showed interest in you!"

The big bro in question was a sleazy looking man, he just licked his lips and yanked on the girl's wrist making her fall into his lap.

Zhang Dong doubted that claim to fame, as the group was quite shady-looking and didn't conduct themselves as people from a prominent clan. Their clothes were quite shabby as well, so they clearly were low on cash.

*Aw shit, here we go again.*

He was slowly getting used to this, so he just stood up from his seat and slowly walked over to the booth the goons were sitting in. They quieted down after seeing the unknown cultivator. They tried to say something, but before they could do anything the man grasped their leader by the face, lifting him up while not letting him speak. The man thrashed about, kicking, punching and trying to move Zhang Dong's hand away, but to his horror, it wasn't budging at all. The whole group kind of figured that this man was strong from the way that their leader was just squirming around not being able to break free.

The female escaped and went behind Matt who turned his head to her and asked.

"Hey, could you open that window miss?"

While the girl was still getting ahold of herself he tested something out. He could only analyze people's names and cultivation levels from afar. But what if he had direct contact like when he identified items. It did work, the man did indeed lie about belonging to a clan he also had a fitting name for his attitude.

Name : | Hoo Dung
Age : | 65
Cultivation : | Foundation Establishment early stage
Affiliation : | Dung Gang
Alignment : | Chaotic Neutral

*Dung Gang huh? Well, at least he isn't evil...*

The girl looked back nodding, she didn't say much and just followed the order. As soon as the window was open, the cultivator walked over to it, just holding the thug with one hand while his feet dangled around. The rowdy character was chucked out of the window, he made a nice arc before falling face-first into a pile of horse excrement.

"Hah, bullseye!"

He then turned back to the rest of the thug squad while shrugging.

"You guys still here?"

The group looked at each other and then started running to get to their 'captain' just leaving the place altogether while hanging their heads low.

"Hey miss, could you bring over some meat dumplings?"

He sat back in his booth while the female employee thanked him, the restaurant owner showed up later to as he was grateful as well. Security around here had dropped since the Zhang Clan was busy with other things like the siege and the Patriarch ceremony so they didn't blame them that much. Matt just ate his fill, probably staying there another hour as he got a good deal.

Chapter 56

Time moved on, his daily routine consisted of cultivating in the night, getting three hours of sleep as he didn't need more, going to the city to sightsee and eat delicious meals. Then go back to the Zhang Clan stronghold while trying to evade the two teenagers that pestered him about accepting them as his disciples. He started noticing a strange occurrence though, whenever he went out to town.

The man was just enjoying the sights while trying to tour the ten million large city, but whenever he did that trouble was always around the corner. Not for him though, but for other random people. Just like on the first-day things seemed to go astray as he kept running into people that got mugged, assaulted or were brawling.

On one occasion two fathers were duking it out, punching each other left and right while their kids watched. Apparently one of the father's sons had asked for the other dad's daughter's hand in marriage. But that one strongly disagreed so they got into a fight, one claiming that his daughter was too good for the likes of them, while the other got offended. He found himself pacifying the situation and forcing the family to talk it out like civilized people while he watched.

In the end, he ended up handing over one Qi enrichment pill to the people as a gift. They were in one of the rings he got earlier so he didn't care much about it, but the people sure did. The people even wanted him to be part of the family after they got all buddy-buddy with each other. But he was afraid that they would try to milk him dry if he ever accepted to do that.

At one point he wondered if he should change his robe to a black color and put a bat symbol on his chest. The amounts of robbers he beat up and sexual harassers was quite high, he didn't know if it was just how things were around here or if someone had put some kind of curse on him. Well, it would be a lie if he said that he didn't enjoy beating up the baddies the man having a bit of a hero complex, but when you did it all the time, every day, it started to weight on him. When he got that Patriarch position he would be sure to form some kind of police force. He couldn't be busting up criminal rings while being the king of the city himself.

Though, he was doing the exact thing at the moment. It was less than a week till the Patriarch ceremony, so the clan members were busy with that. He was eating a shish kebab while walking, he wasn't sure where he was but by the banners outside the buildings, it was probably a similar place to the pleasure district in Moonlight city. While he was walking past one of the alleys he heard some muffled screams, his senses were quite up there so he stopped. Two people were in front of that alleyway, probably some goons to scare off others as they were giving him the stink eye.

He just went over there nonchalantly and took a peek behind them while the two were shouting things like 'Do you want to die' and 'F**k off bastard'. Sure enough, there was a woman getting held down by some goons. He gave out sigh and then looked at the two shouting men in front. He did something he saw in cartoons or movies, he grabbed the two by the heads, bumping their heads together and then tossing the two to the side. The people inside pulled out their weapons, one of them swinging his scimitar right at him but he just caught it between his index and middle finger. After disabling that attacker with a little jolt of electricity via the metallic weapon he moved forward. The other two were soon down on the ground with some missing teeth and broken noses.

This wasn't the end though, the woman in question started begging him to help rescue her sister that was abducted by the baddies in question. Guess he stepped in on a human trafficking situation, he just shrugged and told the girl to lead the way. He was a bit surprised by the fact that there were things like this taking place in this city. He thought the Zhang Clan wouldn't allow such things to happen, but later it was revealed that yes they were a lot better than the other clans. But still, some people could still be bought out they just kept things more secrete. So there weren't things like what the young bratty masters did back in Moonlight city.

This made Zhang Dong mad, he didn't want to have people forced into a life of prostitution. While some Zhang clan official turned a blind eye while getting paid some spirit stones. He wanted to go back to the clan abode to get some people to check this stuff out, but the girl was just yanking on his robe and crying. So, after giving out another sigh he told the woman to show him the way, what happened next was people flying out of windows like in an old western saloon scuffle. He was just too strong for them, without needing to use any of his Qi cultivation he just walked in the building, weapons shattering and denting the moment they touched his reinforced body.

In the end, he brought the big crime boss to one of the Zhang Clan's establishments, they were scattered around the city and told one of the people there to go get Zhang Kuo. He was still covering his face, plus he wasn't that known so the clan member inside didn't really want to listen. That was until he released some of his cultivation on him. After Kuo got here, he told him about the whole thing and wanted the man to get apprehended. Zhang Kuo didn't argue, he just looked at the beat-up man and some girls that were standing behind him, the girls were the ones that he saved from the baddies.

The man was quite good at organizing things, so he had the man brought in while having the women questioned about their situation. The Patriarch to be wanted him to get them back to their families or if they didn't have any to organize a place they could work at instead. He thought this was a bit too excessive for the Zhang Clan to get involved this much, but it was a noble endeavor and his boss gave the order so he couldn't really refuse.

After acting as a vigilante, he returned home to find Liu and Xue sitting by the entrance to his room. They were kowtowing there for close to two weeks, not moving an inch even when their mother came over to pick them up. He was slowly feeling bad for them, did those two even pee?

*God damn you brats, I have no idea how to teach you anything...*

He hid inside his room and bit his lower lip.

*Will those two just sit there till they are skeletons? Their mother was giving me strange looks lately...*

When he looked at the Disciple tab, there was not much he could do. He couldn't even remove the disciple candidates in the system or accept them, he figured he needed to tell them that he accepted it. He had that senior aura, but most it did was just make people agree with him more.

Impartation of Knowledge (Upgradable) | 30000 | Teaching was never this easy, all your disciples will absorb your teachings like sponges with just a touch of your finger. Skills and techniques thought this way will transfer a faint amount of the mentor's knowledge into the student.
Imposing Will | 35000 | This skill makes your disciples listen to you more, increasing their blind devotion towards you.
Mentor's Eyes | 20000 | Having trouble with picking up the flaws of your students? With this skill, you'll be able to see any shortcomings that your pupil is experiencing.

*I guess if I want some devoted minions that 'Imposing Will' would be good. But don't really want some crazy zealots. The other two will help me teach them faster while picking up on the flaws in their cultivation...Should I try it...*

He gathered a bit more points during these weeks, getting some clan resources and making weapons without having to spend points of them. But the earnings were so-so. He had enough to get those to skills, also he had a hunch that he might be needing those skills in the future to make the Zhang Clan stronger.

After buying them he looked at his mirror, checking if he wasn't looking funny.He then opened the door and said in a stern sounding voice.

"Liu... Xue..., stop sitting around there and get in here."

The two youths moved their heads up after they heard the words, they looked slightly emaciated but were in high spirits after they heard their uncle's voice. They closed the door behind them and looked at Zhang Dong that had his hands behind his back while standing up straight.

"So, do you two want to become my disciples?"

The two looked at him nodded and replied excitedly in unison.

"Yes, Uncle!"

"My cultivation techniques are very volatile. If you fail in your cultivation, it will mean certain death."

He said with a frown on his face as the lightning Qi that he used was quite chaotic and hard to use. If the cultivator made a mistake the backlash could kill them. This was probably why the rank of his cultivation was up there. While asking he moved his hand out, electricity crackling through his fingers as he demonstrated.

The two kids gulped while looking at that lightning Qi, they were quite gifted so they knew that what the man in front of them was doing, wasn't that easy. But they made their decision long ago, they would risk it.

"Also, you must give up on your revenge, extinguish your rage. Pursuing power for revenge leads to many demons in your Dao Heart, this will delay your progress significantly and at worst, will cost you, your life!"

He wasn't lying as this was the truth in this world, the knowledge that he was implanted with told him that. Inner demons were created from negative emotions and unless you were planning on cultivation some demonic technique you were better of without them.

"If you agree then you may call me master."

He said while opening up his hands, the bottom side of his palms pointing at each individual in front as if he was beckoning them forward.

The two thought about for a second before, kowtowing one last time. Then replied, determination in their voice.

"Yes, Master!"

Accepted Zhang Liu as your disciple!
Accepted Zhang Xue as your disciple!

Gained 10000 Spirit points for accepting your first disciple, congratulations!

He perked up at the prompts, he thought that he might be able to earn points by training disciples as otherwise, he would be spending resources and not getting much in return while others got stronger. Guess he could become the greatest disciple trainer in the world!

*I can even feed them pills to get stronger and choose their move set...*

Matt wasn't a person of this world, so he didn't really get the whole Master - Disciple dynamic that well. He wasn't against teaching kids some things here and there but wasn't really thinking about the cult-like behavior disciples mostly had towards their masters. The more he would teach them, the more devoted they would get. This could be a double-edged sword, but the kids didn't look like the type to get into trouble, he sure hoped that his trouble attracting aura wouldn't rub off on them.

Chapter 57

After seeing the prompts, Matt noticed that Xue and Liu's faces were now in his disciple window. When he clicked on them he could see all their statics, how far they were into their cultivation what skills they had learned, and how well they knew those skills. They all had the usual low, mid, high and perfect grading, so it was easy to figure out.

Zhang clan being a Clan based in a city full of springs made them mostly have water techniques, maybe this was the reason why the Tsai clan that was fire types hated their guts so much. Now he would have to make a decision, to either buy new water-based techniques for the kids or just teach them what he had already. He didn't think there was a reason to do the earlier, as his cultivation method was superior to the other ones. He also had many resources dumped into his lightning Dao way, that it wouldn't really make sense unless the kids didn't have the aptitude for it.

First, he needed to change their main cultivation method, only after that could he start teaching them his techniques. Then, he might need to get them a better body tempering skill, he didn't want to give them his as it was far to resource-heavy. Maybe it would give them an initial boost as the first levels would be easy, but later on, when the resources get scarce it would become a problem. They had no system to help them craft weapons that they could absorb, this type of technique was only good for people that were loaded.

"Take a seat you two."

He beckoned them over, letting them sit down while he stood up, brows furrowed slightly before he began speaking.

"Qi Condensation, you take in the spiritual energy of heaven and earth from the surroundings, to temper your body from the inside. You prepare your body for your foundation. You two have already started, but luckily it is not yet too late."

"The breathing techniques that you have learned allow you to extract Qi from the surroundings, filtering out the water elements and then storing them inside of your body. My cultivation method is a bit different."

Zhang Dong said as he stuck out his index finger and pointed it at his new disciples. After a moment the two could see a Qi bubble forming in front of it, but it was a bit odd. It was weaker than normal and didn't seem to have any elemental energy inside. But after a moment it started crackling, turning a deeper shade of blue as it appeared in the form of a small lightning bubble.

"You don't just gather the spiritual energy, you transform it, feel the heavens around you, bend them to your will!"

He kind of recited what the knowledge in his head was telling him, it sounded like hogwash but the two kids were eating it up. He also had to agree with it because he was actually pulling out heavenly lightning from thin air. But he didn't plan on making many speeches though, as he took that handy Impartation of Knowledge technique. He did have the books on him, but he didn't want to explain everything like a math teacher when he could just upload stuff directly into the brain. Also, the skill had a small bonus of already giving the one that was receiving it some proficiency in it. The first steps were always hard, so this was a big plus. He also could spend points to upgrade it later, so that the impartation would let the pupil learn more from the get-go.

"I'll impart my cultivation technique for the Qi condensation level to you, but also another technique. It's called the Tranquil Mind, I want you to study it first before you attempt cultivating my Lightning Qi Cultivation Art."

He thought that the bonus from the tranquil mind technique would aid the kids in keeping a calm mind, so they wouldn't make a blunder during the cultivation period. The two were giddy with anticipation as their Master walked over and placed his index finger on Liu's forehead. The two didn't know what Zhang Doong was doing as they have never seen a teaching technique like this.

"You might feel a tiny bit of pain... so endure."

Before Liu could nod he felt information rushing into his head, he could feel discomfort penetrating his mind and sweat going down his forehead. He never felt something like this before, the knowledge of the tranquil mind, the cultivation art and even the Dao of lightning was getting shoved into him. The whole thing didn't take long but the poor teenager almost passed out during it. The Dao of lightning was probably the hardest to comprehend, as it was the absolute principle of lightning.

*Uh, maybe it's too much information at once? I managed to survive that info dump... they should be okay, it's a lot less info than what I had to endure.*

He went over to the girl that was shivering slightly now but there still was determination in her eyes. She survived the headache but was rubbing her poor forehead while on the ground trying to process the information.

"I have imparted the basic teachings to you two, you can head back and start cultivating after you rest up. Also, take these and copy them down, don't show them to anyone else, then return them to me."

He handed them the cultivation manuals with the techniques as well, the impartation skill wasn't perfect they might need the techniques in written form for reference and the system didn't have a copy function. The two teenagers wobbled out of his chambers while grasping their heads, he might have overdone it but he smirked a bit as he wasn't the only one who had to endure migraines while learning new things.

*Haha, you two are young you can power through it.*

*I think that should take them a while to process before I have to teach them other things, but I sure would like to have a body refining technique for them... one that lets them get to the nascent soul at least...But those would be in the heavenly grade, those don't come cheap.*

He had spent most of his points now, he wondered if he could get Zhang Jin to fork up some spirit stones that he could absorb, or maybe he could get their mom to do it, but she was a widow now so he thought that would be inappropriate.

"Wait, there are those upgradable skills... maybe I can buy one that starts at the Qi Condensation stage but I can upgrade it all up to the Nascent soul stage... maybe even higher."

That was the good thing about those upgradeable skills, they might end up costing more in the end but you could use them at a lower level. A person at the Qi Condensation level couldn't use Core formation skills even though they were of a higher grade, they required just too much Qi to use. But not like someone with no body refining skill would be weak. Qi cultivators were more of a mage class, while body refiners were more akin to warriors. The strongest people cultivated both, but most of the time one path was the main one while the other was just a bonus.

Like Zhang Dong mostly used his Qi cultivation instead of his body, but that was mostly due to his body refining being behind his Qi cultivation but now it had finally caught up. So he would probably win against someone with a similar Qi cultivation if their body refining level was low, as he would take less damage and tire himself out less.

His Qi cultivation was of a high level, so the kids didn't need a super hard to learn body refining technique more or less something to add to their repertoire would suffice. But he still wanted it to be somewhat good. There were a lot of techniques that could be upgraded and had skill trees to them, but none of the attack ones he had. That kind of evolved as he upgraded his cultivation technique. He also had a skill tree for his body refining technique, but he couldn't up the grade but instead, he had attacks that he could unlock.

The copper body skill let him choose a grasping technique, his fingers would become metallic and his griping power would increase exponentially. He had already gotten that and tested it out, it also got a free buff when he rose his level of cultivation. The silver body let him deliver explosive strikes with his fists and legs, as they also changed to metal. He could also raise his defense past his cultivation realm for a brief moment. The golden body let him go into a special state he would perceive time slower while moving faster, so it was more or less a boost in speed and reaction time. All in all, it let him fight better at close range while using up his stamina instead of his spiritual energy.

*But wait, the upgraded skills work on me as I have the system, can I upgrade them if someone else learns it..."

He didn't take that into account, he was the person with the system. He could buy skills but he had to use them himself to get the required knowledge to pass on. So he checked out his cash shop and found another way. Some skills could be bought a tome at a time if needed. So he could buy the first tome of the skill and pass it on, then when they were done with it just get the second tome without having to pay the whole price for the skill or technique upfront.

So while his new disciples were bumbling with their cultivation efforts, Zhang Dong took his time in examining the body refining skills. He also was really close to becoming the Patriarch, he sure hoped that nothing wrong would happen during the ceremony.

Behemoth Body (Tome 1) | 2000 | Cultivator absorbs demon beast cores to enhance the body. Gains monstrous strength can transform body parts like nails into claws. Practitioners might experience violent tendencies.
Profound Physique (Tome 1) | 2900 | Through rigorous training, tempering and absorption of heaven and earth energies the cultivator can transform their body into the perfect weapon. Mostly focus on defense and power.
Devil's Frame (Tome 1) | 3500 | By performing specific rituals, the practitioner can gain the body of a devil, it boasts high regenerative abilities.
Sylph Physique (Tome 1) | 2850 | Suited for female cultivators, it focuses on speed and evasion instead of resistance. While still giving a moderate increase in defense and regeneration.

He didn't find anything out of the ordinary, the Behemoth Body seamed good as it only needed beast cores but the violent tendency part was a bit iffy. The Devil one was out of the question, he didn't want his disciples slaughtering infants. The profound one looked like your regular body refining skill, with no downsides besides being hard to learn. It looked like it would boost the cultivator's skills without the mental or moral downsides. The Sylph one would probably suit his female disciple, while the profound one would be better for the male one. He would give those later to his disciples, maybe he could even give it to some other clan members as those looked to be good high grade all around refining techniques. Plus it was just for the Qi condensation level, so they was rather cheap.

There was also one other thing he learned while he was examining the cultivation manuals that he got from the core formation cultivators he defeated. When he examined it with his system out, he noticed that he could actually refine the cultivation techniques. Also, the costs were lower. He would pay less for upgrading a low earth graded skill to a high earth graded skill than to buy a new high graded skill. So maybe if he got his hands on those water cultivation tomes that the clan had, he could upgrade them. It would be probably better to learn a better version of a technique you were already familiar with than to start practicing a new one.

For now, he didn't have many points left so he just resumed his daily activities the day of the 'coronation' was coming.

Chapter 58

His progress had slowed down with time, the Qi around the place was also thinning out as he was absorbing it at an increased rate. His cultivation was above 50% but it started stagnating. The good thing was that even without achieving a breakthrough he was getting stronger. Each percentage counted, he was a lot stronger at 50% than he was at 1% of the middle stage. Plus he had managed to get his body cultivation into the middle stage as well.

He wore a golden robe as the patriarch ceremony was uppon him, looking kind of regal as Zhang Ya was fixing him up. He was even wearing a strange ceremonial hat, which made him look like a pope or sect leader. The hat had some strange strings with small beads attached to them that just dangled around. The sleeves were very long and wide, this was certainly not a robe meant for fighting. He looked at himself in the mirror while his attendant was fixing up his clothes, he wanted to crawl into his bed and hide, due to his silly appearance.

"Patriarch, you look stunning. I bet all the prominent clans in the area will send marriage proposals as soon as they see your stunning appearance."

The woman said in an excited fashion.

This didn't help at all, as Matthew didn't really feel like getting married. He also knew how things worked around here, the marriages were mostly political and were meant to bind clans together while the parents were supposed to pop out babies like crazy. Well not like he had much against the baby-making procedure, but he would rather do it with someone who actually liked him. He still remembered that one woman just running away the moment she heard his clan name.

*Well, I'm the Patriarch so they can't force me to marry anyone. If someone tries, I'll force them to marry a goat! That will show them! I'll even bring some spirit grass for the goat as a wedding present.*

He was slightly nervous but quite less as his tranquil mind was in full effect. He just needed to do a couple of those breathing exercises and he was good to go. He had been living in this place for a month now, he had met some of the elders and core members for the clan. But he was quite bad at remembering names, it was even worse to attach those names to faces that kind of blurred together. So most of the time he ended up just nodding while greeting people.

Zhang Ya had explained everything to him, but he went through it once more in his head. First came the ceremony in the main building hall, everyone from the core members would be there. He would get the official title there, he would have to sit down on that big throne and get greeted by everyone which could take a while. After that, he was supposed to go to the mausoleum and pay his respects to his ancestors. A lot of this involved kowtowing and getting kowtowed back, these people sure had a thing for that, he liked handshakes more. Following that, he would have to get on a magical platform that worked like a flying sword. He would have to show himself to the citizens and either say something wise or just wave at them and nod. Then came the strange parade through the city ending it all with some kind of banquet where more people were invited to. The clan would receive gifts from other clans, which was more or less a friendly gesture to keep good relations. He wasn't expecting much as the clan was in decline, so there weren't many other powers trying to get on their good side just yet.

*This is going to be a long day...*

He gave out a sigh and headed out, it was time to get this over with as the day had only started. The whole thing was supposed to take quite a bit, the banquet was taking place at night so till then he would be greeting people while stoically looking at them. Zhang Jin gave a long-winded speech about the Clan's future, that the families should come together to form bonds or something like that. Matt wasn't really listening as he was trying not to fall asleep during it. Afterward, many people came over to pay their respects, some people he remembered some were new. He kind of waved his hand about while nodding, playing the role of a more silent lord but it was mostly due to not knowing what to say.

This took a good chunk of the day, there were many clan members as he kind of underestimated the massive size of his clan. Some looked happy, some looked dejected as the side families kind of forced their way into the whole ceremony proclaiming that if the Patriarch was from a side family as well, they had the right to be there. The raining grand elder had set this all up, these were troubling times so the clan needed unity more than tradition. Some people almost started fighting, but with one good snort they quieted down fast.

After that was done the mausoleum part was next, he was alone kneeling in front of some statues and graves. He just lit some incense sticks here and there while bowing at the 'ancestors'. He felt kind of weird doing this as he had no relation to these people whatsoever, besides the system bestowing him with the body of the so-called Zhang Dong. He had thought a bit about that, was this a game world? Or was this just some parallel world and he now inhabited the real Zhang Dong's body that existed in reality. Maybe the owner of this body died during the battle with the monster that slew his parents. He just got inserted into it, though that would be unlikely as he was the one that picked the name.

He was leaning into the direction of a godly being making this whole world, for some shits and giggles. Probably watching him dance like a puppet while laughing. This was kind of unsettling but he couldn't do much about it.

Next up, was the part he wanted to do the least, his public appearance. He was radiating his senior aura at max while looking down at the people, there was a huge about of them. It looked like a sea of people crammed into a small space, just looking up at him while he focused on his tranquil mind technique and recalled what he wrote down beforehand. Even though he remembered it mostly from movies and games... Thus he started speaking with a slow steady voice.

“This day does not belong to one man, but to all! Let us together rebuild this Clan, this city, that we may share in the days of peace."

"In order to succeed in this endeavor called life, we must come together with one heart, one mind, one love, and one determination"

"Unity is strength, division is weakness only together can we achieve greatness!"

"Individually we are but a drop of water, but together we are an ocean!"

He tried quoting some political propaganda that he remembered from some internet surfing back in the day, but he wasn't sure if it was working as you could hear a pin drop after he was done with his speech. But soon cheers could be heard around the whole city, probably because most of the people in this world had a big individualistic mindset, gaining power for themselves to raise up in society. The whole 'Work together' thing was a bit new. While the people on the bottom pole were eager to share and work together, the people on the top would probably still cling to their resources.

He just waved and flew along the road as the parade started, the platform he was on had a big throne on it. So he looked like some lofty magical king just floating while getting escorted by traditionally dressed clan members. The people looked quite happy to have him there, which made him glad but he just wanted to get out of these uncomfortable clothes also he was really bored.

While he was just sitting there he decided to see how his disciples were doing, he hadn't seen them much in the past week. The last time was just after they returned him his original manuals to the skills he gave them.

Name : | Zhang Liu
Cultivation Base Qi : | Qi Condensation 9th
Cultivation Base Body : | Qi Condensation 1st (Profound Physique)
Techniques : | Tranquil Mind, Rainwater Sutra, Empowered Lightning Qi Cultivation art, Flowing Water art...
Dao : | Dao of Heavenly Lightning(0,5%)

The kids had started learning his skills, the tranquil mind skill wasn't that hard to learn so afterward they concentrated on the Dao and lightning cultivation art.His Lightning Cultivation art already transformed into the empowered one, he hoped that when he upgraded it again he could teach the kids the improved version with no problems. The Dao bit looked hard to learn though, it wasn't even at 1% but that was the hardest thing to learn as it showed the cultivator the right way. The peculiar thing about his disciples, that after absorbing the lightning Qi, their hair started showing white strands. Guess that was the side effect of this art, silvery hair.

The girl wasn't much behind the boy, She had the Dao understanding a bit higher at 0,7% but had more trouble with the new body tempering technique. You could say she had more talent for Qi related techniques, while the youth for body-related skills. But it just might have been a different mindset.

The last thing on the agenda was the banquet, so they all returned to their main base. He was back at sitting at his throne while people were buzzing about, some other more friendly clans came to pay a visit. They were mostly the weaker ones, just trying to be polite but there were some others gathering some info about the new guy in town. Matt was trying hard not to yawn, which might have given the wrong signals as his face quite stern-looking.

The people were happily chatting between themselves, Zhang Jin was quite fond of the lady cultivators as he seemed to be working his adult charms on them. Zhang Dong sighed as he didn't want to get a new 'uncle'. But the pleasantries came to an end there, because everyone could feel an overbearing aura suddenly fill the whole place. It was an unannounced visit, no one knew how the person got here as the guards didn't notice their arrival. Matt was also surprised as he couldn't feel the person before they released their aura, the aura felt quite strong it was at the level of a core formation expert at the great circle. But it wasn't just one person, there were more.

Six people walked in, filling the room with their oppressive spiritual energy that pushed anyone below the core formation-level down to their knees. The five people behind the strongest person were all at the late stage, Matt had gotten stronger in the past month but he probably wouldn't be able to handle all those experts alone.

"Well, isn't the little Zhang clan going to pay their respects?"

One of the people in the back spoke up. All of them were wearing similar yellow robes, the person in front had the most expensive-looking one on him. The thing that stuck out was a symbol of a black hand embroidered to the back of the robe.

A note from Kuropon

Happy new year.

Chapter 59

The person in the front looked a lot younger than the people in the back, he was also the strongest, probably some kind of genius young master type. The people in the back were all older men, looking to be in their fifties. The lofty young master had long dark hair, a more tanned complexion and some kind of jewel sticking out of his forehead. Might have been some kind of treasure, or maybe part of a cultivation method. The six were of course members of the dark palm sect that ruled this region.

The first one to react was Zhang Jin, he was also the only one that could move beside Zhang Dong in this situation as the former was a bit baffled by the situation. This was actually the first time that Matt was in front of someone that he wasn't a senior too. Jin went in front and made a bow to the younger male offering his greetings in a pleasant voice.

"You honor our small clan with your presence oh honorable Seniors."

Zhang Dong was a bit slow to react, which caught the eye of the sect members. Who started eyeing them down, almost ready to pounce on him for not showing the due respect towards them and their young master. To them, he was just a country bumpkin that was a leader of a small insignificant group of cultivators.

"Ah, excuse my rudeness."

He quickly got off his throne and bowed his head in front of the sect cultivators, this being the first time he actually had to do it. Most of the time he was the strongest person in the area, so he kind of got used to acting nonchalantly around others.

The young master seemed to be a person of few words as he looked dejected to even be here in the first place. He just looked at Zhang Dong for a second and then turned his face to one of the elders behind him. His tone was quite condescending.

"Just give them the orders, don't want to be in this backwater place anymore than I have too."

The elder that was spoken too, took out a jade slip and threw it over to Matt that quickly scanned its contents. He started frowning more and more as he read on what was written in there.

"This..."

"Follow the orders in the jade slip, you know the repercussion if you decide otherwise. Know your place whelp, you might have won against some trash clans, but don't ever forget that the Dark Palm sect is the one that lets you have your petty squabbles in the first place.

The man spat on the ground, as he didn't like how Zhang Dong was slow in giving them face. After the elder gave them the warning, they withdrew their aura, jumped onto their swords and headed out. As their master had stated, none of them wanted to be here in the first place. The clan people started getting off the floor while panting, knowing well that there was probably nothing good in that jade slip. Zhang Jin walked over with a solemn look on his face, he was passed the jade slip his eyes going wide-eyed in the process.

"Does damn bastards! Did we somehow offend them?"

Matt let Zhang Jin keep the jade slip as some other elders started reading through it. Due to the previous expedition ending in failure, there would be another one. The secret ground opened up on set intervals and required a set amount of people to take part in it. Their clan was ordered to supply them with 1 core formation cultivator, 20 foundation establishment cultivators and 200 Qi Condensation cultivators. Also, they specifically ordered the new Patriarch of the clan to take part in it, if not the sect would replace them with another clan.

There was also an explanation about why this specific number of cultivators was required. After going to the secret grounds, the people there found ten large platforms. The whole thing was created by some immortal cultivator, if they completed a trial they would get some cultivation technique of his as a reward. There was also a giant door in that chamber, in the text it stated that if the trial is successfully finished the giant door would open and reveal the treasure inside.

The Dark Palm sect was very much interested in what was behind that giant door, they tried to brute force their way inside but even their nascent soul cultivators couldn't put a dent on that massive door. They decided to bring enough people for the trial, but they didn't want to use their own disciples. They brought in the clans for that, some of them went in for the spoils as the sect did offer rewards. But no one could actually refuse them.

So the first time around, the Zhang Clan went over with 3 of their core formation elders, 60 foundation establishment experts and 600 Qi foundation warriors. These were the best warriors of the clan, as the clan was going to get paid well if they succeeded. The rest was filled by other clans, in the end, no one returned. The secret grounds forcefully expelled everyone that came inside and the entrance to it got sealed off. But it was later revealed that the seal was weakening with the passage of time and that it would open again.

The ever greedy sect cultivators decided to throw more people at the trial, they didn't care about what the clans thought, they could be replaced later. The opening time would be in about three month's time, they were required to bring their forces there or suffer the consequences. If they succeded the sect would offer them some spirit stones and resources also they would let them have whatever was in the trial. Probably because they thought that there wouldn't be much worth in there.

The atmosphere was solemn in the room as everyone got the news, the banquet was ended prematurely while the people in charge went to the main hall to discuss things, Matt went with them of course.

"We have three months... we are done for...the previous Patriarch couldn't best that trial with our strongest forces, how are we supposed to do it now?"

One of the men in the room said while pulling his hair out.

"We could try running..."

"And what? Become bandits? Join another Clan? The moment they find out our roots they would execute us."

"They really want us dead..."

Matt listened to the old men bickering, the trial was strange as it had designated spots and a set amount of people. The composition was strange, the core formation experts seemed like generals of their forces, the formation establishment cultivators like officers and the Qi condensation warriors as soldiers.

*Maybe it's some military game where they compete against each other? But then one of the teams would have won and been alive to tell the tale...*

He tried thinking about novels and how most of those pocket dimension dungeons worked. Mostly there were a lot of traps involved people competing to get some strange herb or treasure in the end. But this one had a treasure outside it, while the people taking the test were inside.

*Sounds like a place to test your forces or something...Maybe people inside have to work together to win... If so ... that might be bad...*

He knew well how things worked around this world, sometimes a sibling would backstab their family to get that magical pill. Working together wasn't really something that was associated with cultivators. Being a murder hobo, popping pills was more the xianxia way.

*I guess if everyone was from one sect it would work out, but if you put in Clans that probably have some grudges with each other and tell them to work together for one goal... I think I need to get more points.*

After becoming the Patriarch he had unlocked the Clan window, he could see how many people were in it and what cultivation levels they were. It kind of looked like sim city, he could see the approval ratings in the city, what cities he had, the crime rate and so on. There was even an achievement tab, that showed him that he could get points for things like getting the approval rating up to a certain point. Building a hospital, building more martial art schools and bringing the strength and knowledge of the citizens up. More or less he got points the better the clan and the city did. Also, he gained passive points each day though at the moment he was gaining a whooping two points a day.

He decided to act a bit more like a leader, slowly filling the room with his aura as she said with a booming voice.

"Organise a city-wide tournament for our clan members, tell them about the new expedition. Qi Condensation juniors and Foundation Establishment cultivators from the clan can participate. We will select the right number from the strongest from them. Do it within a month's time."

"Zhang Kuo, find me a list of any strong beasts or demonic cultivators that have bounties on their heads, best if they are in the core formation stage. Do it as fast as you can."

He needed to train his forces up, which would require quite a bit of points. The fastest way would be slaying monsters or cultivators at the core formation level. He had to get enough points to upgrade the skills for the chosen elite warriors from the tournament. He could hide the fact that the winners would get conscripted, but he would rather have some weaker people that have the guts to fight, than having to force them to come along and then have them abandon others in the middle of battle. The strongest warrior wasn't always the best one for the job.

The people in the room, mostly knew what the Patriarch was going for with the tournament to choose the best warriors. But was a bit surprised that he wanted to hunt some bounties? But they guessed that he wanted the cash rewards to aid the clan, so there wasn't much resistance from them. They discussed some other things, with him there, mostly the logistics of getting the tournament ready.

Zhang Dong returned to his chambers and flopped like a dead fish on his large bed. His face was down in the pillow as he just wanted to go to sleep. But before he could do that he heard knocking on the door. He turned around and stared at the ceiling for a moment before standing up.

"Who is it?"

"We apologize for the intrusion, Master"

It was the two kids, they were looking at him with embers in their eyes. They had apparently heard about the whole dark palm sect expedition. Probably overheard it from their mother or one of the other clan members.

"Please Master, teach us fighting skills we want to participate in the expedition!"

He looked at the two youths, the two looking quite determined.

"There's going to be a tournament if you can get into the best 200 you can participate... But is your mother okay with this?"

"Mother will probably take part in it too... we overheard her talking to grandpa about it, we want to join her and our brothers and sisters of the clan!"

The to were taking it quite seriously, which made Matt a bit hesitant. He didn't want to get these two youths involved that much, they had a bright future ahead of them and quite the high talent. But if they failed the clan would probably be done for anyway.

"Fine... you two continue with your cultivation, but also use this..."

The two were getting the hang of it, but most of Zhang Dong's techniques required high amounts of lightning Qi. The most he could give them is the basic fighting techniques along with the lightning punching and kicking arts. If they could advance with those, they might stand a chance in the tournament. He also wanted to learn a sword art for himself, he didn't have one yet but he would need to get more points for that.

The two left his chambers with a splitting headache again and some manuals to copy from while Matt decided to cultivate for the rest of the night. He expected to get the info on potential targets in the morning, he would head out to gather points, his goal was to get into the late stage of the core formation stage, his progress was slowing down though. He started feeling responsible for these Zhang Clan people, the closer he got to them the harder it was to let go. He might have been an introvert but that didn't mean that he wanted to be alone.

A note from Kuropon

Speedy new year release \o/

Chapter 60

The next day the news was spreading through the city, making the citizens quite unruly. This was understandable because if this expedition ended badly like last time, there would probably be a new attempt on the city. No one thought that there would be anyone rescuing them again if that happened. Some people were thinking about abandoning the clan and city in general, but then they also heard that other clans in the area were in similar situations. No one was really safe from the sect overlords and it was hard to abandon an established life to start anew.

Matt was in his cultivation chamber, trying to raise his power level. But his gains had slowed down the further he progressed. The storm clouds were coming down less, the spiritual energy in the area was thining out. He was thinking about his plan, would it even work? He left and went over to Zhang Jin, he wanted to know if he knew anything about the last expedition.

After the two greeted each other then his grandpa explained everything in detail. The old Patriarch left with two other core formation elders, this happened about three months ago. They didn't have many details on what happened inside as the communication jades didn't work. The spirit tablets started breaking after about a month, so the people inside that dungeon didn't just get wiped out. They remained for quite some time, fighting for their lives. It took another month for everyone's tablets to break, maybe it was some kind of prolonged attack or some kind of maze?

The thing Zhang Dong was sure of was that he needed to get as many points as he could, but he wasn't about to go on a killing spree. That's why he told Kuo to get him that fugitive list. He wanted to hunt some monsters and get spirit stones as rewards to boot, he needed a lot of resources. Did everyone have the best available weapon for their disposition? Could he upgrade their cultivation method? This was a team event, so he needed to arm his men and women to the teeth and he knew that the previous expedition drained the clan's coffers dry.

"I have brought you what you asked for, Patriarch."

Matt nodded and took the jade slip, it had information about various baddies and monsters around the whole empire. He scanned it for core formation enemies, would be nice if he could grab a nascent soul beast, but a monster like that would probably one-shot him.

Ravager | Demonic cultivator, last seen near the five dread peaks by the city of Frostriver. Cultivation base in the later core formation stage. He has killed hundreds, maybe thousands of people in pursuit of power. Reward 10,000 low grade Spirit Stones.
Lesser Calamity Dragon | Evil Beast residing in the volcanic areas of the inferno mountain range, regularly seen raiding nearby cities and villages causing havoc on the populace. Cultivation base in the late core formation stage Reward 12,000 low grade Spirit Stones
Blood Demon Cult | An evil group of renegade cultivators, they act in the shadows and are hard to track. People have reported children getting abducted in the night. Reward 8,000 spirit stones, cultivation base unknown, possibly in core formation, not confirmed.

He mostly looked for opponents in the late stage of core formation, after fighting the fire lord and upgrading his skill he thought that he could take those on. He noted down the cult as well, as the city that they were doing their evil deeds was between the other two places he was going to go. He could head there after taking care of one of the assignments. After he finished up with those, he would decide if he could do more before returning to the clan.

He thought that maybe he could stay here and relax for longer, but now his life was at stake. There was always an option to leave and hide, but he was the Zhang Clan Patriarch. Everyone probably knew him by now, he would probably be a wanted one like that Ravager guy on the run. But there was also an option of a disguising skill, though if he did that the people from this clan would be dead meat. He didn't want to have that on his conscience.

*I really need some sword skills, I can't actually do any fancy attacks with this sword of mine besides swinging it around.*

Matt knew that there were many flashy sword styles, that if mastered let the user unleash powerful attacks. He would like to get a technique with a lot of potential best if he could use it from the get-go and be able to raise its prowess later. He had an eye on one particular sword art, that came under the umbrella of lightning elements so he got a discount. It wasn't an upgradable skill or anything, it was divided into tomes though if he bought the Earth grade one, he would get the previous ones for the lower ones.

The manuals were called Thunder God Sword Scripture and had various sword attacks and stances that went well with his empowered lightning Qi cultivation method. He wanted to grab the lower-level ones, but if he bought them one by one he would just lose points. For now, he decided to spend the rest of his points on Qi recovery pills and healing pills, as well as some detoxification pills against poison attacks. He knew well how those evil cultivators liked to poison everyone, though his golden body had quite the high resistance to poison attacks.

After checking out his map and marking down the first three waypoints, he could see that the closest area was the volcanic one. Also, this one actually pointed out the whereabouts of his target, the other ones were kind of vague. Maybe after he got the points from the dragon he could find some kind of tracking skill. He wasn't sure if he would be such a good detective and find that cult or that evil cultivator. Those guys seemed like the types that were good at hiding.

The plan was simple, go out, slay some baddies, get points, upgrade the cultivation methods of the clan members after they are done with their small tournament arc. Who knew, maybe some kind of protagonist type would appear during the tournament that he could focus his resources on. There probably had to be a reason why that secret ground required lower-level cultivators, so probably everyone was important and he couldn't just power through it with his own strength.

*Guess I'll be off to saving some damsels in distress, maybe that dragon will be hiding a cute princess somewhere.*

Matt thought to himself jokingly while making sure that he had everything he needed in his spatial ring. He took the excessive pills that he got from the previous battles with him, you never know, low grade pills could come in handy as well, he could always sell them later for more spirit stones.

While he was heading out, his grandpa Zhang Jin was waiting. He looked at him with concern in his gaze, fidgeting slightly before speaking out.

"Don... Patriarch, are you sure you want to leave the clan at this moment, what if something happens to you?"

He was informed about what Zhang Dong was doing, he wasn't sure what hunting some criminal and evil beasts would accomplish in the spawn of 3 months. The clan sure could use more spirit stones for weapons and gear, that was true. He was slightly concerned that the new Patriarch could die during his travels, they had no dao protectors to accompany him as he was the strongest member in the clan, they would only slow him down.

"Don't worry gramps, I'll be back. This is kind of how I get stronger... I might even have a breakthrough in these three months. I already said it to Ya and Kuo, but try to gather some crafting resources I might be able to forge some weapons for the winning clan members afterwards."

He replied in a calm voice, that tranquil mind technique working out quite nicely as previously he would have probably been stuttering all over the place.

Zhang Jin raised his hand as if he wanted to say something, but then instead nodded and gave his grandson a pat on the back and some words of reassurance before sending him off.

"Don't worry, I'll protect the clan while you are away."

Zhang Dong smiled slightly while just nodding back, then he jumped onto his flying sword that started glowing as he inserted his spiritual essence into it. With a thunderous sound, he vanished from the spot and you could hear a resounding sonic boom. Some other clan elders and members were also there. They had a myriad of feelings about the whole situation, some thought that this young cultivator would probably abandon them. Some were hopeful that their new Patriarch would deliver another miracle and get them out of this situation. Some were just confused, others were mad or fearful. Everyone dispersed after Zhang Jin told them to move their asses in motion and get to work while squinting.

The Patriarch had a communication jade slip with him this time around, the defensive formation was repaired so he would be able to come back if something went wrong. They had to follow orders, so they got busy with the tournament plans. Zhang Dong didn't mention how exactly the tournament was supposed to function, but he did say that he didn't want people to just get eliminated if they lost a fight. Everyone was supposed to have multiple chances to get their rank up, one fight wasn't enough to decide a good or bad fighter. Also, the fighter's stamina was important, so the combatants had to fight people in succession. Weapons were allowed, but they had to be of the same grade as the opponents.

The clan had a designated sparring area just for that, with build-in formations that kept people from getting killed or fatally injured. The people got to work while Zhang Dong flew through the air, the increase in cultivation making him fly twice as fast as before. If someone went into his patriarch chamber they would notice that the grand bed was missing, Matt sure as hell didn't want to sleep on that straw mattress that he got from that Tribe. The new bed barely fit into the upgraded crafting abode, he really needed to get something he could comfortable spend his time in...

Chapter 61

Two people were walking, one was an older woman holding onto a big basket filled with laundry. Next to her was a young child, it was the woman's daughter. The day was nice and sunny as they made their way to the river to wash their clothes. The previous day the people in the village spotted some beasts fighting in the mountains, but they just hid till the powerful aura's subsided before coming out. This wasn't such a rare occurrence, powerful experts and beasts fought among each other for various reasons. The residents were used to such things, but no one really cared about their little village so they were mostly left unscathed.

The mother and daughter duo arrived at their destination. This world wasn't that advanced, there were some spiritual artifacts that could be used as washing machines but only rich sects and clans could afford such things. Normal people usually did it the hard way, just washing them in the river. It was supposed to be just a day like any other but then suddenly the small child spotted something.

"Mommy, mommy! What's that!"

The child bounced around while pointing at a spot by the river. The mother smiled at her daughter and then looked at where she was pointing at, her eyes going wide at the sight.

"Quickly, go call your father!"

The woman shouted at her daughter while quickly dropping her basket and running to that spot. She jumped into the water, yanking and pulling at what appeared to be a person. She managed to drag the large man out of there but he looked to be in awful condition. She could see that his white robe was all torn up, there were scratches and cuts all over his body. The river water deluded the blood, so you couldn't see how injured the man was.

After the husband arrived they both dragged the man out of the river, ear to the chest wondering if he was even alive. These were simple people, so they didn't know about CPR but after further inspection, they could hear a faint heartbeat. The man was clearly Zhang Dong, his robe wasn't mending itself as it required the users spiritual energy to do that.

The wife and husband quickly discussed the situation, the man looked to be injured but alive, he was clearly a cultivator but they had no idea if he was friendly or not. But these were quite honest and good people, so they both decided to patch him up to their ability. The man was quite heavy and felt like he was made from metal, so with the help of horse and carriage, they managed to get him back to their farmhouse which was nearby.

You could see other farmhouses around, the village entrance was quite near as well. They placed him in one of the rooms and the wife tended to the man's wounds while the husband kept watching, a bit apprehensive about the whole affair. It looked like the cultivator suffered some kind of beast attack, this made them remember yesterday's fight between some strange magical beast. They theorized that he probably got involved in the fight of those monsters and barely escaped with his life.

"We should probably report this to the village elder, we have no idea what this cultivator will do when he wakes up..."

The husband said in a hushed tone while edging his wife to go along with the daughter as he didn't want to leave them alone with the unknown person. The two females headed out but soon spotted some strange people around the village, maybe it was just a group of adventurers passing by?

There were some by the mayor's house, giving them strange smiles as they were passing by.

"Excuse me, is the mayor around? I need to report something..."

The wife said to one of the mayor's attendants that were standing in front of the house, she didn't have to wait for long as the moment she said that the mayor and a strange man walked out of the hose. The mayor was wiping sweat from his brow while the man was grinning.

"Oh? Can I listen to that report too, young missy?"

The man smiled in a mocking way, while the mayor looked at the woman that he knew from the village. She informed them about the strange cultivator they fished out of the village and how they brought him to their house to tend to his wounds. This made the other strange people whisper among themselves before the leader barked out an order to her.

"Interesting, you won't mind if we tag along, right mayor? Think it might be one of my men."

The mayor wanted to refuse but he wasn't really in a position, these people had just barged into this village asking about yesterday's monster attack. He told them what he knew, where the spot was that the fight probably occurred he even lent them a guide as he was afraid that if he didn't he would end up with a dagger in his throat. These people were clearly some band of bandits or renegade cultivators, probably trying to find something in that beast attack.

Having no other way out, the wife and mayor headed to the farmhouse while the unwelcomed guests followed after them. As they arrived, the people that left with the guide returned, but without him. They whispered something into their leader's ear, the man just smiled and nodded while whispering something back.

The group arrived at the farmhouse to the husband's surprise, there were quite a bit of those cultivators around and the mayor was also there. This left the man with furrowed brows, but his wife explained that they were the friends of the cultivator they saved. The leader and two other men walked into the room where the silver-haired man was, he looked like a mummy with all those bandages wrapped around his torso. The strange thing was that the family was also forced into the house along with the mayor, the leader of the so-called cultivator friends started speaking.

"Okay boys, we hit the jackpot. Our brothers found a dead beast, it's worth a fortune this unlucky sap must have been fighting it, just leaves us to finish the deal."

He said while grinning. They were bandits, they were on the move as they came across the fight in the distance. Being the curious bunch they decided to see if the people that battled left something for them to take. They expected at most to get some scraps, maybe a half-chewed up cultivator carcass where they could find a working storage ring. But instead, they found a dead dragon and the cultivator was right here, they just needed to finish him and take all his bearings. There was only one problem, the villagers. They couldn't let them live now if this guy was some prominent figure and someone came looking for him they would be done for.

"Kill him, take all of his treasures... then kill all of the villagers, let no one survive... do it quietly so that they don't run..."

The family and mayor looked on in horror, backing away with the little girl in the back.

"No you can't do this, the Ruling Clan won't let this happen!"

The husband shouted out, while the bandits started pulling out their daggers.

"The Clan? Like that bunch of arrogant bastards would even lift a finger for some useless villagers."

One of the bandits replied while licking his dagger.

"Hey boss, can we have some fun with the girls?"

Another one from the bandits asked this one was quite wide, looking like a pig.

"Girls? Hehe, little bro you sure like them young don't you..."

Everyone looked on in horror as imminent death was approaching, the father tried protecting their family but instead found himself with a dagger stuck in his shoulder. The mayor was getting beaten while the wife and child looked on in horror.

"Hehe, just blame your bad luck."

One of the bandits said while his axe came down at the bandaged up cultivator's head, aiming to chop his neck right through. This didn't go as planned though as the weapon shattered into pieces the moment it collided with the man's neck. The struck spot shone with a golden metallic luster. Before the man could reassess the situation he felt his neck getting grabbed, as the seemingly passed out cultivator awoke.

"You know what, I was willing to let you live... but then you had to open your big mouths, there is a certain place in hell for bastards like you... "

The bandit was lifted up into the air as the white-haired man stood up. He looked at the man that just tried to chop his head off, then he looked at the injured village residents. The bandit in his grasp had a strange expression on his face as he thrashed about, but soon he could feel electricity run through his entire body. The man lit up like a Christmas Tree, death came fast and without much pain due to the overwhelming amount of electric energy. The man's charred remains hit the floor, he looked like a baked skeleton with some meat attached here and there.

"P-please s-senior, appease your anger..."

The bandits knew well that they couldn't handle this guy, he had killed that giant dragon that was still radiating with power. They were just simple Qi Condensation cultivators, with no backing to speak of. The man was slowly walking towards them without replying, so they just bolted for the exit. Running away was the only option, all of them scattered hoping that the mad expert couldn't get them all or wouldn't even bother.

Matt walked out of the farmhouse, he could feel the auras of all the bandits in the small village. The bandits were in close vicinity so he could sense all their unique murderous auras. He gathered Qi into his hand, forming a big spear of light. He threw it up into the air, the javelin went straight up, at the apex of its trajectory, it exploded splitting into many smaller spears. Guided by his senses they homed in on the escaping cultivators, piercing through their bodies as he left none of them alive. He knew that those men were killers and rapists, but it still left a bad taste in his mouth as he looked at the dead people scattered around the vicinity.

The previous day he had gone to the spot where the calamity dragon was supposed to have its lair. It was there like on the wanted list, but the problem was that it was a lot stronger than what he had anticipated. The moment the dragon noticed his presence it attacked. It was in the late stage, but the problem was its body. His attacks kept bouncing off the scales, his sword left flesh wounds while he himself took hits after getting too close. In the end, it ended up with a battle of attrition as he used his avatar form in a last-ditch effort, wrestling with the thing while it sunk its claws into his enlarged body. He managed to snap the dragon's neck in the end, the two fighting it out near a waterfall where he passed out. Afterward, he was carried downstream and ended up by the village where the villagers carried him home and tended to his wounds.

He realized that the Tsai clan patriarch wasn't a good reference point, he had just broken through and his cultivation technique was more or less trash. This dragon was at the pinnacle of that stage, plus it had a hard body that might have been its main cultivation method.

He wasn't as strong as he had thought, mistakes were made. He had also gotten some innocent people involved in this debacle. He went back into the house and handed the injured people inside some healing pills. The villagers were grateful but there was fear in their eyes, they just witnessed a man killing so many people with ease. Matt apologized to the residents, leaving behind some money as thanks before heading out. He flew back to where the dragon remains were, taking it into his storage ring as he could use the body for crafting materials.

*I guess one down and two to go... At least I got some points now.*

Name : | Zhang Dong
Affiliation : | Zhang Clan
Spirit Points : | 215432
Cultivation Base Qi : | Core Formation [Middle Stage 57 %] (Empowered Lightning Core)
Cultivation Base Body : | Core Formation [Middle Stage 3 %] (Golden Body)
Techniques : | Empowered Lightning Qi cultivation art, Golden Body Arts, Thunderlight Sword, Thunder Movement Art...
Dao : | Dao of Heavenly Lightning, Dao of Smithing and Crafting
Other : | Senior Aura, Impartation of Knowledge, Mentor's Eyes, Apprisal

Chapter 62

Matt was on his sword munching on some healing pills while his wounds were regenerating slowly. He didn't like how his first mission went down, he almost died fighting that dragon then some crazy bandits wanted to chop his head off. He even got some innocent people involved, then had to kill. He'd give himself an F+ for handling things, the + just for not being dead in the end. He kind of figured that he shouldn't rush into these kinds of things without gathering some intel first. Though not like there was anyone around that volcanic mountain range to ask questions about. He could also use a detection skill of some sorts, maybe if he pined the location of that dragon before it noticed him, he could have gotten a sneak attack in.

First, he used the new points to get the first three manuscripts of the Thunder God Sword Scripture, to increase his attacking power. Each manuscript taught him one special move, but they also contained the knowledge about sword stances, methods of attacking and defending. The first one was an attacking technique, the sword practitioner would release sword energy and deliver a slicking attack that would cut anything in its way. It also added some lightning laws, and besides slicing and dicing your opponent it would kick up a storm in its wake. It had the name of Thunder God Slash, it also increased in power with every higher-ranked manuscript. There was also a variation of the skill called Thunder God Thrust.

The second one was called Thunder God Domain, it was a defensive move you formed in illusory domain calling up lightning elements and storms. In this domain, you could perceive all incoming attacks and react accordingly. The last one was a charge up attack called Sever the Heavens. It was similar to the first one, but it would deliver an immensely powerful strike and couldn't really be spammed like the Thunder God Slash move.

He decided to try out his new repertoire before moving on, starting with the basic Thunder God Slash. It was more or less a sword light type attack, if he did a slashing attack it would send out an energy blast from his sword, that would cut anything in its path. He tried it out, managing to slice up quite the big boulder with no problem at all. He could also do thrusting attacks with it, this left a big gaping hole in another large boulder that he abused.

The domain technique gathered lightning energy and sword intent around an area of about 10 meters in all directions. He threw a rock up into the air and closed his eyes, waiting for it to fall down. The moment the object got into his domain he could sense it along with its trajectory, slicing it in half without needing to open his eyes. This was quite a handy skill to predict enemy movement.

The last one was a bit harder to pull off. He grasped his sword with both his hands and started pumping his energy into it. The sword blade started expanding upwards, getting longer and wider. He performed a diagonal swipe with the 'charged up' weapon, slicing a smaller mountain peak in the process. He was left drained, sweat running down his forehead as he panted.

*I can't use this one too often...*

After getting the gist of his new sword techniques, he thought about the next destination. The closer one was the city where the cultists were in, but he needed some things before that. He looked for a fitting detection technique, maybe something to mask his aura or looks as well. He recalled that many Xianxia protagonists always had a handy technique to hide how they looked so that they could escape into the crowds whenever getting into trouble. Also if the cultist noticed that they had someone sniffing around town, they would either try to kill that person or lay low if they were too strong.

He looked at the earth graded skills as always, he aimed for something that worked on core formation experts and below as he couldn't really afford heavenly ranked skills and didn't know if he could actually use them. There was one, just named 'Earthly Disguise Art' that was supposed to work on core formation experts and below, masking the user's appearance along with his or her aura. It also helped the users detect people that were using disguising arts of lower and similar grade. Then there was an enhanced version called the 'Heavenly Disguise Art' That was a direct upgrade of this one.

He also wanted to snatch a better aura detection skill, maybe an aura tracking skill. People tended to leek their spiritual energy into the surroundings, it did dissipate after a while. He could maybe home in on this dissipating energy to track the evil cultivators. He felt that these were some quality of life skills, so he decided to drop some points into them as well.

Matt closed his eyes and focused his mind on his surroundings, the enhanced aura detection skill let him home in on the beasts and animals in the surroundings quite a bit more. His range also was increased by multiple kilometers, he dropped down to the ground. He noticed that if he used his new tracking skill a sort of mist appeared. It was a trail that he could choose to home in if he fallowed after it the person or animal in question would be at the end.

He thought that this system was a bit too overpowered, it had way too many functions and was only limited to the number of points he could get. He wondered if after some time there would be some kind of drawback, would the prices suddenly increase? With this thing around, he could probably go into seclusion hunting weak beasts, evil cultivators or search for things he could absorb for points. Guess he couldn't absorb magical treasures for points. Also, he couldn't see anything above the immortal grade in there. He didn't want to abandon the people he was now feeling responsible for though.

With the new skills and techniques, his points dropped by about a hundred thousand. The dragon did give him a lot of points though, so he still had some left. He didn't want to waste them as he had no idea how many he needed to upgrade his clan members cultivation techniques, also there were some treasures with steep prices that he wanted to get to aid them as well.

*It always comes down to points... Well, I still have to go pick up the spirit stone reward think it was issued by the clan around here, what was it again the Huo, or Hou clan?*

Matt was still having trouble with all the oriental names, for now, he headed to the city to get his reward. He also shifted his clothes to a black color and used the new disguise technique to change his appearance. His facial muscles started shifting around, the color of his hair turned to black, he even grew a full beard as he looked like an old kung fu master. He wanted to see if he could pass for someone else in this town, no one needed to know that the Zhang Clan was out hunting monsters. Also, he wanted to get a higher reward for his troubles, would be easier to bicker with people if they didn't know who he was, but could also get him into trouble.

While Zhang Dong was on his way to get his reward, the people back in Spirit Spring City were getting ready with the tournament. Everyone from the clan knew about the second expedition and that they were testing everyone. Some people didn't want to participate, but most felt a deeper bond with the family clan and were going to give it their best because if not, their families would be done for.

The clan was quite large, it had many foundation establishment fighters and even more Qi condensation ones. There were about 20 thousand clan members scattered around, that wasn't really a big number considering that the city had 10 million people in it. From those 20 thousand members, only about 1 thousand were in the foundation establishment level. Most in the early and middle stages, the rest were just Qi condensation juniors.

People below at the 6th and lower levels of Qi condensation weren't even allowed to participate. Zhang Xue barely made the cut, but no one was expecting her to get far, her brother stood a chance as there were a lot of free spots to be taken. Though no one knew that the two people in question were experiencing a colossal change. It had been about two weeks since they picked up the new cultivation method. Their old cultivation art was more or less trash compared to this one. This could be seen by the amount of silvery hair that the two now possessed.

Xue managed to advance into the 8th stage while her brother was close to breaking through the bottleneck of the 9th stage. The two were frantically training with all their might, hoping to be of service to their new master and to their clan which they held dearly in their hearts.

The way the tournament would work was announced, it wasn't a bracket system as they didn't want to get one strongest fighter. The participants would fight multiple bouts in one day if they lost they got zero points if they won they would get two, if the time run out or if it was a draw they would get one point. The ones with the most points would move on to the next day where more fighting would take place. The first couple of days would be the worst, as there were just so many participants.

This wasn't really an event for the masses so everything was closed off, the sound of fighting resounded in the Zhang clan compound. After the first day, the two disciples managed to get some wins while loosing to some more experienced fighters. People were somewhat surprised as the two youths were able to defeat cultivators that were of a higher realm. They seemed to use some new techniques, Xue was adept at kicking while Liu at punching techniques. When their kicks and hands collided with their opponents, sparks flew about while the adversary became momentarily stunned leaving themselves open for attacks. The two kids looked promising as the tournament continued, but it would take some time till it ended.

Chapter 63

A youth could be seen slowly breathing while sitting in a lotus position. His eyes were closed, his body was exuding a strange glow while several glowing wisps hovered close to his body. Those looked like tiny soap bubbles, one of them started slowly approaching his dantian. The youth's face showed a frown as the tiny bubble entered his body and the energy from it started circulating throughout his meridians. The force that entered began crackling and sizzling slowly shifting into a tiny stream of electricity. The new form of the bubble was quite rowdy as the young man tried to keep it in check, slowly managing to make it part of his body.

The young man was Zhang Liu, he was practicing his new cultivation method it was a lot harder than his previous one but it was also a lot more powerful. Even though he wasn't able to condense and transform much of the spiritual energy into the lightning type, he could feel his energy reserves increase exponentially.

He stood up and took on a fighting stance, his fists moving forward at a rapid pace as they gleamed with a faint electric aura. His long ebony hair had started turning pure white, he was getting close to having a salt and pepper type of look now. He was still in the 9th stage of Qi condensation, but due to this technique, he felt that his bottleneck was about to be broken.

"Master's cultivation method is so powerful, I can easily contend with others at the same stage as me... I can even beat the ones on the 10th level."

He took a look at his body, it looked somewhat more profound. It wasn't his muscles, but his skin the first part of the profound physique refining art enhanced the skin of the cultivator. It made it a lot more resistant and elastic, he could take a lot more punishment thanks to that but the way you trained it was quite painful. He had to perform strange poses and chants, holding them for hours while concentrating on his fleshy body. This was extremely painful, his body ached all over as his refining technique destroyed and then rebuild his cells to be tougher. But he powered through this all, his defensive capabilities increased and if he mastered this technique he would be rewarded with an impenetrable shell.

The skill had four stages if he passed it the resistance would increase exponentially the first one was the bronze skin stage, then came the iron skin stage followed by the silver skin stage then the golden skin. He had passed the first and second one., this put his body on the level of a 6th Qi condensation fighter, the third would put him at the 9th and the last would be the 12th. There was one skill that came with this refining technique, the cultivator could temporarily raise their defensive and offensive capabilities. Their skin would start shining slightly taking on bronze, iron, silver or golden color depending on the stage the cultivator was in. It was kind of similar to Zhang Dong's technique, but Matt's also worked on his internal organs so this one was weaker.

People were surprised at how much the young master and mistress had progressed in these past three weeks. The fighting tournament was in full swing and both of them were still in it. The brother was doing better as he was older and had more experience as well as a higher cultivation method. But the younger sister wasn't doing bad either, the combination of her speed and fast kicking attacks had brought her into the middle stage of the tournament.

The older brother preferred overpowering his opponents, while the sister took her time in analyzing the fighting patterns and methodically taking people apart. She managed to get many draws due to her evasive tactics, her bother took some loses due to his bravado instead. Their Master would probably have to take a different approach to each student after they advanced further in. Giving the girl a more speed focus technique at the start, was a good first step for the noobie senior.

The two were doing so well that their mother was worried, if they continued like this they would surely be chosen to come along to the expedition. Being a doting parent she would rather have them remain back here if the expedition failed again her kids still had a chance of survival. She also knew that she would probably be one of the foundation establishment elders selected as she was in the upper late stage and there were only ten or so elders in the great circle stages. At least she could protect her children if they went there together and she knew that they wouldn't forgive her if she did something to make them lose.

The new Patriarch seemed to have some kind of plan so she had high hopes for him. They also had a bit of a scare with his magical life telling plaque, it rumbled for a second but didn't break. They contacted him afterward, the patriarch just replied that he got in a bit of trouble but he handled it already.

Back in Zhang Xue's room, she was also cultivating diligently. She edged out her brother when it came to cultivating in spiritual arts, but did worse with her body refining skills. She had already reached the 8th stage and was going for the 9th one, on the other hand, her Sylph Physique was still in the first stage. It was different than what her brother used, it mostly focused on her libs instead of her skin in the first tome. It was aimed at increasing the cultivator's speed and dexterity. In short, each stage gave a boost to the girl's quickness the special skill let the practitioner send wind blades with their kicks. The wind energy synergized well with the lightning one, so her kicks were even more ferocious. The 'side effect' of this was that her long legs started putting on some meat, this made the male youths in the surroundings quite ecstatic.

During the tournament, they were giving her strange looks, as they discovered a new world after getting stepped on by their junior sister. The clan people were more or less loosely related, so this wasn't as strange as some people might think. Though most people scoffed at inter-clan relations, as you mostly wanted to bring in new blood from the outside or marry your daughters off to strong clans to foster better relations with them. But it did happen, where some cousins tied the knot here and there.

So while Zhang Xue was looking at the weirdos in disgust days went by, the tournament continued while more and more people got eliminated. Zhang Dong was now in a city called Spirit Tree City and would you know it, it had a giant tree right in the middle of it. He was just walking out of the ruling clan house with his spirit stones. He had arrived and scared the people a bit after dropping the massive dead dragon out in the open so he could get his cash reward. He tried to sneak in some snorts and grunts to look menacing but the people in there didn't want to give him even one more spirit stone. They did want to buy the dragon though, but he refused as he didn't trust them on getting a good deal for it. He'd rather people back in his base do it instead, they wouldn't lie to him.

*Ah, why do you have to be so stingy...*

*Well, surprisingly I didn't run into any cartoon-like villains stealing candy from a baby this time around, should I just bolt for the next town or get something to eat first... this place looks like it has some interesting grub.*

Matt didn't really have many things to do besides cultivating and getting more points, so this left him quite bored most of the time. He was used to watching movies, playing games in his free time but none of these existed here. The music was also bad, the played those zither things most of the time, it wasn't bad but just made him want to sleep.

*I don't think I'll find anyone rocking out with a guitar around here anytime soon...*

He went to go eat and not much happened afterward so he just left for the next city. But due to his now enhanced aura skills, he noticed that after he left, some cultivators were trailing him. He could feel three people, all in the core formation stage one in the middle stage and two in the early. He wasn't worried that much, so he led them away from the city so that no one could see them before confronting the group.

Of course, it was people from the clan that was stationed there, they came to the conclusion that Zhang Dong probably stole the dragon body from somewhere and just came for the reward. He was, of course, hiding his power level to be at the lower end of the early core stage but he didn't think people would be so dumb to attack him.

"Leave your belongings behind and scram!"

One of the uncles shouted out at him while they all pulled out their weapons, looking like hungry wolves that just saw a succulent piggy.

"Well, aren't you people from the Ho Ho Clan quite fierce?"

Zhang Dong replied in a mocking tone as he wasn't really fearful of the bunch. He actually thought this would be a great time to test out his sword-fighting skills. So he pulled out his glowy sword while beckoning them over like you would in martial movies with your palm.

The three elders just scoffed at him and flew right at him, thinking that this guy was courting death. The moment they got into the cultivator's range, they felt a strange aura surrounding them. They started attacking him from all sides, thrusting and slashing with their weapons. To their surprise, the cultivator was able to parry all of their moves with just his sword hand. He held one hand behind his back while playing around with the attackers, honing his use of his domain skill.

The three flew back, deciding on a group ranged attack. They fired off various colorful magical skills at him, the fluctuations of core formation experts fighting could be felt in the surrounding area which made everyone close scatter. He took those skills head-on, using the first sword move releasing powerful sword slashes that disintegrated the incoming magical attacks. The three men were just realizing that the man in front of them might have actually been the person that killed that dragon himself now. But before they could apologize the man closed in on them, he started pummeling them to submission till they were a twitching mess down on the ground.

After 'clearing' up the misunderstanding, he was richer but quite a lot of spirit stones though those people didn't have much on them. He just gave them a good old thrashing and left them naked in a forest. He made sure to put them down in a triangle, each enemy cultivator was resting his head on another man's posterior. He nodded to himself after looking at his marvelous work, the only thing missing was a camera to snap a picture for later.

*I guess this also is a valid way to get more resources, and they attacked me not the other way around. I can use their flying swords to upgrade my body refining level.*

He thought to himself while rubbing his chin as he thought that robbing from the rich and giving to the 'poor' wasn't such a bad idea.

Chapter 64

He arrived at the city that the so-called cult was supposed to be in. His new disguise was of a rugged looking old man, a big scar over his face and short brown hair. He figured out that he could change the length and volume of his hair at will. He could also shift his muscles around on his whole body, but couldn't really change his bone structure. Matt decided to play it safe, not knowing if the cultivators that he robbed would put up any wanted posters of him.

The town looked kind of gloomy, the sun was covered by a thick layer of clouds. Matt noticed that the weather tended to change rapidly depending on the location he was in. Sometimes he would arrive at a tropical area with lots of natural beaches, only to fly for an hour in another direction to arrive in a snowy area. This might have something to do with the nature of spiritual energy around this world. Places tended to be warmer where fire elements gathered.

The city was called Fogmire, which was a peculiar name given that most towns had those xianxia sounding names. This one was just dim, murky and the moment he stepped inside it started to rain. The notice came from this town, so he wanted to go get the details. Fogmire as any other in the area was governed by a clan. The city had about five million people living in it. On earth, this would be a capital city, but here it was just a regular mid-sized town.

His robe was pitch black as he flew close to the city, he descended in the nearby forest while hiding his aura. He didn't want to alert people to his high cultivation, his flying sword being a dead giveaway. It took him about half an hour to walk to the main gate, he paid the toll normally and then asked one of the pedestrians about the clan that governed the place and about the cult.

Fogmire was governed by a side family of the Kin Clan, their leader wasn't all that strong but he still was in the core formation. When he asked about the cultists, the person looked at him with wide eyes then bowed deeply before running away. Guess the people were more scared of that cult than of his new menacing appearance.

*Well, I guess I'll go check out the main clan building, they should have all the info there.*

Your Disciple Zhang Xue has reached another level in the Sylph Physique, 500 spirit points gained.

Those prompts starter popping up here and there, whenever his two disciples gained insight in his skills or advanced he would get rewarded. Guess it was a good decision as he already had earned back the points that he spent on the two rascals. He wondered if he could just make a martial arts school and have everyone swear him in as their master. But then he looked into his disciple tab, he could see a 2/5 counter in the upper right corner. Guess the system wouldn't let him use it like that. Maybe if he cleared some hidden quests, the limit would increase?

Matt had picked up a habit lately, every new place he visited he was drawn to their restaurants. The food in this world was quite tasty, probably due to the added spiritual essence in the plants and animals.

*Work can wait, first it's time to check out the local cuisine!*

He rubbed his palms together as he strolled through the city, trying to find a nice restaurant for himself. It was getting late, the gloomy town was becoming even bleaker as it lit up with the faint light of the street lights. The lights didn't run on electricity, they were simple magical treasures that used up spiritual energy from the surroundings. Matt finally found a place to eat, it looked like a tavern that you would see in those fantasy games. It even had a sign with a beer mug outside, but it seemed kind of quiet.

He pushed open the double doors as he walked in, the people inside slowly turned their faces towards him giving him cold stares. He was hiding his cultivation base, so they wouldn't know of his level. Matt thought that people would be having fun inside as it looked like a saloon, but it was rather quiet inside. The floorboards creaked with each step as he made his way towards the counter where he saw a lone bartender person standing.

He wondered if he walked in at a bad time as the place felt gloomy, even more than on the outside. He wondered if he changes genres as the inside looked like your run of the mill western fantasy establishment, still, the people were wearing robes even though they were on the shorter side. Before he could ask for some food, the man behind the counter spoke up in a hoarse voice.

"Greetings stranger, you shouldn't be out here, all alone... He he he ..."

The man was strange-looking, his eyes vacant and a pale unhealthy complexion. When he was laughing Matt could see the rotten teeth and the accompanying bad smell that came with them. The motion of ordering any kind of food from this place went out of the window after getting a load of those chompers.

These people were kind of strange, he felt multiple gazes of people from behind and the barkeep was acting loony. Zhang Dong had gotten that new skill where he could see people's auras in a more visual form. He decided to turn it on, wondering if this would shed some light on the situation.

*W-what is this...*

He took a step back after seeing a black smoke like aura enveloping the man in front of him. This wasn't any old chimney smoke, this was evil miasma mostly seen on demons. He turned to the side, the people in the establishment were all covered in the thick, eerie aura. The whole place was covered in it, did he just walk in on the main evil base or something. Where those people evil cultivators, or some kind of monsters, the demonic aura was really thick on them.

Matt decided to do a test, he flicked his finger at the man that was still laughing. A little bit of his electric Qi flew out and bonked the man in front on the forehead. The good thing about his Dao of heavenly lightning was the heavenly part. Apparently anything that involved the heavens was the bane of anything that involved demons and demonic energies. The lightning jolt was really weak, it wouldn't really do much to a normal person but when it came in contact with the man he started shaking furiously.

Strange growls escaped from the man as he twitched around, his head was twisting in impossible ways. Soon his head shot up into the ceiling while the body collapsed onto the floor. The head had spider-like legs and had multiple eyes protruding out of its body. It gave out a high pitched scream that seemed to rouse the other monsters in the room. Everyone inside started transforming into nightmare creatures, lots of teeth, claws and even tentacles.

They all pounced at him in unison, biting, clawing and gnashing all their various appendages. The creatures were stopped by a barrier, the moment those creepies touched it they were sent flying backward due to an electrical shock. Matt was inside, really glad that he had bought this skill before the monsters wouldn't be able to get to him now.

*Without my tranquil mind skill, I'd be s*itting bricks right now...*

Besides their gruesome horror appearance, the things were more or less just trash with Qi condensation level strength. They were all quite brainless as all of them continued attacking him while bouncing off the electric shield over and over again. Matt just wanted to obliterate the whole building with the monsters inside, not really keen on touching those ugly looking things. But if he did that, he could harm people outside also there could be some innocents in here as well.

Instead, he formed a couple of smaller lightning dragons, sending them outside his barrier to do the fighting for him. They were the size of larger snakes but packed a punch. They started chomping, pouncing and just charging through the monsters quickly clearing the place up. The small lightning snakes coiled their bodies around some of the humanoid monsters, causing them to sizzle and evaporate as they discharged heavenly lightning into them.

None of the monsters was spared, Matt only came out of his bubble after he didn't feel any demonic auras in the building. He looked at the dead bodies that were quickly turning into black sludge, frowning. He toured the tavern, hoping to find normal people inside but it was barren the most he could find is some gnawed on remains, probably a midnight snack to these monsters.

*Well, this whole thing became rather unsettling... think next time I'll go fishing..."

He went back to the bottom floor and dipped his finger into some of that black sludge. Even though the thing was dead, it still had a faint demonic aura to it. He tried focusing on this type of evil energy, closing his eyes as he let his senses guide him. Then he noticed a certain spot that was radiating this kind of energy. He opened his eyes and hopped behind the bar counter, going into the pantry.

The food looked rotten and there were flies buzzing about. The demonic energy was coming from behind the wall, there might have been a secret passage behind it. He started patting down the walls in the hopes of finding a switch or lever, but to no avail. Guess it wasn't as easy as they made it look in those adventure movies.

He did the only logical thing afterward, punching the wall and uncovering a secret narrow passage behind it. He cleared the rubble and took a step in, the demonic aura was leading inside. The passage quickly turned to narrow circular stairs that were going downwards. This was a textbook example of a horror setting, he expected to find even more of those monsters below. This was probably the moment in which he had to decide if he should continue downward or just report this to the people in the city and have them risk their lives.

Maybe it was just bravado, but the man felt that he should be able to handle himself. Also, if the monsters got alerted to his presence, they might start killing those people that they abducted, that is if they were still alive. He started going down, the stairs went on and on as he walked for a good half an hour before finally arriving at the bottom. There were torches lining up the walls, illuminating the interior faintly.

After descending the stairs he started hearing strange chants in a language that he had never heard of before. The walls were made from old bricks, the corridor started getting wider and wider the further he went in, the strange chanting louder and louder.

"Ph'..lui mglw'na... .ul..hu ...yeh wgah'na... fht...n "

He was almost there, he could see green light outside of the tunnel. He slowly moved forward, trying to not let his aura seep out into the surroundings as he peeked out of the tunnel. He saw some cultists kneeling down in front of an altar, some babies in front of them crying their little hearts out. Those were probably the sacrificial offerings, to the thing that was on the altar when Matt saw it his jaw dropped.

*...What is that thing doing here again...*

A note from Kuropon

Woo, 7 place in trending o(^▽^)o

Chapter 65

The tunnel Zhang Dong was peeking out was not the only one, there were many and they all led into this massive cavern. The other tunnels were also probably connected to other places that those demonic beings had taken over. Matt didn't know where they were, but they were probably deep under the city. The cavern was circular with a high ceiling. In the middle was an altar, pedestals with torches around it and a familiar-looking mass of tentacles in the middle.

*I thought that thing back in the forest died... are there more of them around...*

Ltl'thulhu The Corrupted One ( Core Formation Late Stage )

*Ltl?... little? Is that even bigger than mini...*

This monster was certainly stronger than the last one of its type. Zhang Dong looked on as the monster was just a head peeking out of a mass of tentacles, similar to the way the other one looked when it powered up. He took a quick glance at the people that were standing around the altar. They were holding curved daggers in front of some infants that were placed on smaller sacrificial altars in front of the monster. What they were doing was quite clear, he had to save the children and he couldn't let the monster evolve further.

There were eight infants, two on each side of the rectangular altar. The people seemed to be finished with their chanting as they started pointing those daggers at the babies. First Matt bolted out of his hiding place, making enough sound so that everyone would notice his arrival. He wasn't really worried about the cultists, they weren't strong but he had to get those kids to safety first.

The cultists quickly started going through their demonic transformation as they reacted to the threat. While the baddies were focusing their attention on him, he surrounded the children with his spiritual energies forming small barriers around their frames. This was a bit taxing on his mind, but he managed to pull through before the monsters could shishkebab the poor babies.

The monsters were uppon him at that point, trying to devour him whole while their big boss was flailing around in the tentacle mass, mad that it couldn't get its meal. The lackeys weren't really a problem as they got bisected in an instant by his blade. He started cleaving them apart left and right while gathering up the infants from the altars.

Ltl'thulhu wasn't having any of this, the tentacle mass started coming together to form his body. He looked exactly like the monster that he fought back in the forest, but it was a lot bigger. The good thing about its size was that it was taking some time for that body to form, this was time he needed to get the kids out.

The children floated around him in those tiny barrier bubbles while he hopped onto his sword. He couldn't really battle this thing while thinking of the babies, so he decided to fly straight upwards. He shot through the air like an arrow, while holding out his sword that was glowing deep blue. The ceiling had some strange rune-like patterns drawn into the rocks, probably some kind of formation that prevented the demonic aura from seeping out. It only worked one way though, as Matt could feel that the rock wasn't all that thick. He used his Thunder Sword Thrust to lunch a flash of powerful lightning sword energy at the ceiling in front of him.

The people in the city could suddenly hear a rumbling sound, followed by thunder as Zhang Dong busted from beneath the clan estate. Yes, the monster lair was right under the governing clan's main building. But the clan in question didn't seem to be working with the demonic cultists as they were baffled by the situation as well.

The Kin Clan members just witnessed a cultivator bust through their backyard, surrounded by thick spiritual energy. After the man flew out, many winged monsters started clawing their way out of the hole, screeching and roaring in the surroundings. This certainly woke everyone up, the cultivators started fighting with the monsters that they previously came across but could never pint point their location. No one in their right mind would have thought that the demons were hiding right under their estate.

The monsters gnashed their teeth at the human cultivators that attacked them with spears and swords. While the creepy crawlies were distracted with the other cultivators Zhang Dong descended to the side. He looked around, spotting some female cultivators that were running somewhere. He dropped down right next to the group of females, the sight of a big burly cultivator with balls of light hovering around him made the people stop and stare.

"Hey, those demons were trying to eat these babies, bring them out of here, I’ll take care of their boss.”

The women blinked in surprise while Zhang Dong opened up the barriers surrounding the infants, doing it one by one while handing the crying children to the women. One of the women quickly run-up to a specific baby, grasping it close to her chest.

“It’s Bao’er, he disappeared two days ago!”

Guess this one was one of theirs, so the women quickly took the babies away. The surroundings rumbled once more and a strong demonic aura could be felt by everyone. The people started screaming, blood coming out of their ears and eyes. This was clearly an aura attack performed by the huge ugly boss monster that started emerging from the hole in the ground. It was a lot bigger than the one he met in the forest, about three times as tall.

All of the monsters roared as their master was emerging, not affected by the aura. The human cultivators were close to losing their minds, but then they felt a powerful aura enveloping them. This aura pushed the demonic one away, forcing the smaller monsters back as well. The people saw a fearsome cultivator emerging on his sword, his body was covered in lightning, his eyes glowing with a deep blue hue.

"Hey, sh*t head. Your opponent is me."

Matt sent another sword thrust at the ugly looking beast, aiming for the head. The monster covered itself up with its huge palm which blew up sending flesh and black goo flying. The hand regenerated quite fast afterward though, the black blood sizzled against the pavement as it had corrosive properties, it even dissolved one of the smaller demons in the process.

Zhang Dong flew upwards on his sword, throwing his ranged skills at the monsters just poking it while the thing finally burst out fully through the rocky ground. It didn't look like he was doing much damage as the thing had high regenerative properties. This wasn't really his plan though, he just wanted to make it mad so that it would chase him instead of remaining in the city. His plan seemed to work as the monster spread it webbed wings taking off into the air.

The huge size making it blow away its own demon minions along with the weaker human cultivators. Matt flew away while throwing his javelins at the demon, slowly making the demon follow him to a more secluded location. He thought that the Kin Clan members should be able to take care of the weaker demons, they also had a core formation elder among them.

People in the city could see the giant being flying above them, its loud booming roars waking everyone up in the city. They could see that the behemoth was chasing a man on a sword, that was attacking it with some ranged attacks. It looked like the man was fleeing while the beast was chasing him down, it looked bleak for the cultivator.

The two vanished in the distance after a couple of minutes, the sounds of fighting could be heard in the Kin Clan compound as well as in the distance where the flying horror and the cultivator headed to.

*Okay, this should be far enough...*

Matt looked at the Cthulhu looking fiend, it looked quite similar to the mini version. Red glowing eyes, squid face, huge burly arms and frame. He thought to the last time he was battling this thing, that time he just overpowered it after finally mustering up some courage to fight. This time around it wouldn't be that easy, the thing was a lot stronger and a lot bigger. But he had also gotten a lot stronger and he actually knew how to use his techniques.

"I wonder how long you can keep regenerating, didn't last that long the first time we fought"

He grasped the air, forming another spear of light. He charged it up for a longer period before chucking it at the incoming baddie. The spear split into smaller parts and pierced into the tough green skin of the monster, damaging it in the process. Ltl'thulhu roared annoyed at the wounds it was receiving, the holes where the small spears pierced into healed in the spawn of seconds.

"Well, at least your slow and stupid."

Matt thought that he would just tire the thing out with some guerrilla tactics first. Poking till its regenerative abilities run dry, then he would either slice and dice it or match its size with his avatar ability. But as he was charging up another one of his ranged attacks, the beast roared and released a deep red energy blast from within its hideous mouth. The blast of energy headed right for him, in the nick of time he managed to dodge it to the left side, the blast only grazing his arm slightly. This was enough to disintegrate his clothes on his right side, his arm getting a bit charred in the process as he felt a massive amount of pain.

The energy attack flew by, crashing into a forest below creating a giant explosion. Dirt and dust flew up into the air as the only thing remaining afterward was a giant crater. It looked like a meteor had crashed in the middle of the forest. Matt's whole arm twitched, he felt a sharp pain but luckily nothing was broken and the pain quickly subsided thanks to his body refining skill.

*I guess it has more tricks up its sleeve...*

Chapter 66

The creature started blasting him with various ranged attacks, besides the breath attack it also could shoot out its huge pointy claws at him. He managed to parry them thanks to his new gained swordsmanship while counterattacking with some timely placed Thunder God slashes and thrusts. Matt didn't think he would have so much trouble with this thing, but his inexperience in battle showed. He couldn't just rely on his stats anymore, these enemies were close to his level and he had to start taking things seriously which he was trying.

He wasn't keeping his distance anymore, he was like an annoying fly buzzing around the creature's head as he used his small size to his advantage. The demon couldn't really use that huge ranged attack on him if he constantly moved, so he did. He sliced and diced the large body, managing to chop one of those webbed wings clean off. He evaded the large claws that were swung at him, the creature then promptly fell to the ground with a resounding boom.

He examined the detached wing that just turned to black liquid the moment it got removed from the main body. Another wing started growing right back, but the regeneration was getting slower and slower. The angry monster fired of another mouth blast in Matt's direction but missed by a mile, it looked quite pissed of as its face tentacles thrashed about menacingly.

He had been fighting it for an hour now, the thing was quite sturdy but after he learned its move set it was just a matter of dodging the telegraphed attacks while getting one or two of his own hits in. He could test his fighting prowess on this raging monster that was at around his level. He was able to test out his skills on a moving target, upping his fighting experience.

"I guess I could test this new move out on this thing..."

He was mostly focused on his swordsmanship in this battle, it was a lot easier to use his weapon than to rely on his fists. While the monster was down on the ground he also descended and started charging at it. The angry behemoth brought down its giant fist at the annoying cultivator but instead of hitting him, it felt a jolt of electricity running through its whole arm as it hit a lightning afterimage. While the monster was feeling a tingling sensation in its huge arm, Zhang Dong appeared behind it with his sword in hand.

He breathed in while concentrating, his body giving off a golden color. Everything seemed to slow down in the surrounding area as he activated the skill he achieved after upgrading his golden body. This skill let him perceive everything in slow motion while increasing his speed. He used this in tandem with his thunder god slash, slashing out with his sword energy. He didn't just slash once, nor twice he delivered hundreds of these less powerful slashes in a matter of seconds that quickly turned the monster's body into sashimi.

He breathed out, feeling his stamina getting drained due to the multiple usages of skills that was taxing his body. Delivering so many light sword slashes in unison was quite strenuous. He looked on as the giant's body started breaking up into cut-up cubes that turned into black goop. The monster was quite in a bind as it tried reassembling itself back to its original form. Matt was a bit surprised that the creature was still alive as he hoped that this special move would bring the thing down.

"Do I have to disintegrate this thing to molecules or something?"

He performed some hand seals, pointing his hands on the cut-up monster that was slowly reforming its head. He pumped his cultivation into his next attack as a giant dragon head started forming. This dragon construct was huge, its head easily able to gulp up the monster remains as it was ordered to. Matt guided the dragon upwards, while the wiggling mass of tentacles and thick black liquid tried to escape outside. The over-sized lightning dragon could be seen from afar flying towards the heavens only to explode, disintegrating any remains from the Cthulhu lookalike, as the heavenly lightning that it was made off was quite effective.

Ltl'thulhu The Corrupted One Slain( Core Formation Late Stage ), gained 192000 Spirit Points

The clouds parted revealing the stary sky to the denizens of the gloomy city, the multiple moons shone down upon the people as the battle was over. Zhang Dong fell down onto his butt, his forearms propped up on his own knees as he panted. He had slain the monster, he didn't take much damage as the thing was all power and no speed. Still, he was gassed out the Qi regeneration pills weren't tasty at all as he swallowed them whole.

He was slowly getting the hang of this fighting stuff, he grabbed the leftover core that the monster dropped and hopped onto his sword. He didn't know if the people back in the city were able to handle the monsters so he sped back. He didn't need to worry though, as the warriors from the Kin clan managed to clear them up. He also noticed that some monster stragglers were just dissolving. The beasts might have been part of the big boss monsters, it probably was just using them to gather in resources. Though this one had an acquired taste for infants, Matt didn't know how many of them fell to the beast but at least there wouldn't be any more casualties after this. He also wondered if this was really the last time he would see this type of demonic being.

He landed back in the Kin Clan estate, people were a bit apprehensive about his arrival as they saw him leaving with the huge overpowered monster. The clan came out to have a talk with Zhang Dong, that gave them a quick rundown of the things that happened to him after he arrived in town. He also told them that he was here to collect the bounty for the monster he defeated as it was put up by this here clan.

The clan members didn't have a reason to doubt his story as they started examining the hole beneath their estate, finding the ritual cavern and the tunnels heading into various establishments around the city. They all gulped hard after realizing that the whole city would have probably been devoured by those devils if this cultivator didn't show up. They were so grateful that they even doubled his salary which Matt was grateful for. They invited him to stay over for the night, though it was close to dawn at this point.

He took the denizens of the city up on their offer, he was quite hungry as the demons interrupted him when he was trying to get some grub. He was led to a nice looking room where he was offered various spirit foods, some cute ladies were even playing harps and slow dancing on the side to add to the atmosphere. The only awkward thing about this was that he was still in his disguised state and had to come up with some fake name. Being the big-brained individual that he was he gave himself the genius name of...

"Just call me... Lei Yinglo..."

He almost choked on his drink after coming up with that name, trying not to laugh while the people around him tried to please him. After some nightly pleasantries, he was guided to a nice room in which he just for a couple of hours. He left early in the morning, checking if he hadn't forgotten anything. The people were nice enough to see him off, or maybe just being courteous.

He looked at his status and counted the spirit stones that he had gathered until this point, two weeks had passed since he had left. He should be able to get to that last wanted person. He would have about a week to take care of him before returning. He had a hefty amount of points now, but having more wouldn't hurt. He left this disguise on this time around as he swished towards his next destination, it was a couple of days away from this spot. He really wished that he could get a smartphone with music or movies that he could look at during his boring flight. It was fun in the beginning, but now it was boring as hell just looking at the blurry ground below him as he zoomed by.

The Ravager sure sounded like an edgy character, he imagined someone dressed all in black with a strange haircut. Or maybe he would have a long coat and a mask covering his face. Though his body count seemed to be no joke as the notice said that he might have killed thousands of people. The town he was heading was called Frostriver, he wanted to check it out before going to those five dread peeks. Maybe if he was lucky he could get this done in just a couple of days, this tracking skill he had now was quite nifty.

For now, he just churned his cultivation power, the crystal flying sword glowing brighter as he dashed through the clouds. The milky sky marshmallows parted as his sword surfing board pierced through them, leaving a triangle-shaped path behind him. The wildlife below him scattered after taking in his overbearing aura, people craning their necks as they heard the sonic booms.

"Watch out Ravager, Lei Yinglo is coming for you!"

Chapter 67

Back in Spirit Spring City.

It had been about three weeks since Zhang Dong left on his adventure and the tournament was coming to an end. All the foundation establishment elders were set in stone at this point, the Qi condensation participants would be ending their bouts in a couple of days as well.

Zhang Liu had managed to break through his bottleneck of the 9th level and reached the 10th. The combination of his hard to crack skin and lightning combat arts had propelled him to the top in his age range. Xue was able to reach the 9th level due to the overwhelmingly better cultivation art that she possessed now. She wasn't doing as well as her older brother, still getting a lot of drawn-out that ended in draws. She was still holding her ground somewhere at the end of the brackets.

The two were increasing their battle prowess with each day, getting some practical sparring experience during the tournament while concentrating on their insights into the Dao that their master had left them with. The two missed their masters a bit, as they had many questions concerning their Dao path as the scriptures that they received had many hard to understand passages.

"Hey Xue, do you know what this one about the prime meridian means..."

Liu asked while squinting at the copied over manuscript.

"I'm not sure brother... it's challenging to understand..."

The sister replied while looking over the shoulder of her big brother, the two trying to trade pointers with each other during these 3 weeks they were cultivating.

"Maybe it's too soon for us to understand? We'll have to wait till Master returns to ask him about it."

The two wanted their uncle to return from his journey, they wanted to receive some input on their advancements. But also didn't want to bother him too much so they were trying to progress by themselves as much as it was possible.

"Mother has been chosen as one of the seniors to participate in the expedition..."

Liu gave out a sigh as he handed his sister the manuscript with the dao of lightning written down.

"Well, at least there will be someone to knock some sense into you there~"

His sister chuckled into her long sleeve while her brother scoffed at her reply. They both were nervous about the future of their family, their father was already dead. The whole predicament was due to that sect, the two felt a burning rage towards it.Their master told them to abandon that anger otherwise, they would form some inner demons. But even with the new Tranquil mind skill, the male from the group was finding it hard to drop his vengeful feelings.

"Remember what Master said, 'Anger leads to hate, hate leads to suffering. Though I'm not sure what he meant with 'dark side' when he was talking about it."

The girl contemplated on the cryptic meaning of her Master's wise words. The month was coming to the end and their master would be returning, so they focused on their training.

A couple of days earlier.

Zhang Dong was arriving by the city of Frostriver, as he had thought it was covered in snow. It looked like a blanket of white was covering the entire surrounding area, he even saw an abominable snowman as he was flying by some mountain peaks. He used his travel time to slay a couple of demonic beasts, gathering up more points in the process. This didn't slow him down all that much, considering he could kill the weaker beasts with one thrust of his sword.

Time was running out though, he didn't have much of it left so he wanted to catch this demonic cultivator and return back home. First, he needed to gather some intel, so he directly landed in front of the city gates and just asked the guards if they knew something about that Ravager fellow. The men looked at the strong-looking cultivator and told them that he should talk to one of the merchants in the city, as the man would probably know where to find the man.

*Oh? Well, maybe I won't need to search for him that much then.*

He was pleasantly surprised that he had a lead right from the start. Matt was a bit surprised by the authenticity of all the wanted reports he had, all of the leads were panning out. These people sure had a good information network going around, even without any internet. Guess those communication jades came in handy.

*Wonder if I can get something better than a communication jade, they said that they couldn't talk with anyone that went to that secret grounds after they entered it.*

He recalled a couple of pocket dimension dungeon tropes that went around in novels. Some of them had random teleportation traps that send people all over the place if something like that occurred a communication device would come in handy. He would check that out later, but for now, he headed to a large merchant building the emblem on it looked somewhat familiar but he couldn't remember from where.

*Probably seen it in some restaurant in another city.*

Matt was still in his disguise, having the more menacing scarred up face look. He kind of liked playing the role of the grumpy looking cultivator, he found it funny how women quickly grabbed their kids to the side whenever he was walking down the street. It was certainly a good look if you were going with an intimidation approach.

The merchant business building was huge, there were carriages coming in and out of it. He could see some muscular-looking bros unloading and loading merchandise. There were various types of weapons and items scattered around, he could even see someone selling fresh fish in the corner this kind of made his tummy grumble.

*If I don't stop eating so much I'll get fat...*

He shook his head while going in and looking for a clerk that he could ask for directions. As he entered a little bell rung and he was greeted by a nice looking lady, though the woman twitched a bit as she noticed that a fearsome-looking uncle just come in. But she quickly gathered herself, showing a bright smile.

"Welcome to the Red Lotus merchant group, how may I be of service, good sir?"

Matt pulled out a jade slip on which he stored only the part with the Ravager fellow, on it was the description of his last location as well as his appearance. The woman looked through the jade slip, her eyes moving between the storage device and the man in front of her. She was staying silent for some reason so Matt decided to get the conversation on track.

"I'm looking for that man, the guards by the city told me that you people from the merchant group should have some information..."

The woman certainly knew something as she was fidgeting around not sure what to do. After a moment she excused herself saying that she would bring over a manager. Matt waited for a bit while tapping his finger on the bar counter, other people started whispering amongst each other while glancing at him but evading his gaze when he looked back at him.

*They are certainly bad at keeping secrets.*

After five minutes or so the lady worker came back with an older looking gentleman. He was wearing glasses and looked like a strict teacher type. He examined Matt from top to bottom before speaking out in a serious tone.

"Could I know why sir is looking for that man on the wanted list?"

Matt crossed his arms together, trying to look slightly more menacingly before he replied.

"To get the rewards of course, what else?"

He shrugged nonchalantly while grinning, kind of making it look like it wouldn't be a big deal. The two were a bit taken aback by the man's claims and confident act.

"Sir, are you sure, that man is a powerful demonic cultivator... he had killed many men..."

The man replied with concern in his voice.

Zhang Dong raised his eyebrow, he still didn't know if they were protecting the man or just trying to not get strangers into trouble. Guess they didn't trust him, so he decided on a demonstration of his power. He slammed the counter with his hand, making it break apart in the process, his core formation aura filling the whole merchant building. Everyone felt the strong aura around them, but they weren't getting pushed to the ground or bleeding from their orifices as Matt just wanted to show his level of cultivation and not cause the people harm.

"Stop stalling, you dare hide information from this Lei Yinglo!"

He shouted out so everyone could hear him, almost breaking his act after he told the people his name. He stopped releasing his aura letting the people gather their senses as they were still panting. Before the scared manager and the lady could reply, a chubby man waddled out from the side. The man was quite rotund, his cheeks jiggled around as he ran towards the group of people. The man came to a stop in front of him and quickly started bowing.

"Boohoo! Please senior save my daughter, that bastard took my little girl Whaaaaa."

The man dropped down to his knees and started hugging Matt's thigh, crying and sobbing like a little child. He started shaking his leg but the ball of a man was clinging to him like a spider monkey just bawling his hear out. The man was the owner of the merchant group here, he had apparently lost his daughter to the demonic cultivator in question. Lei Yinglo delivered a bonk to the chubby man's head to calm him down, hoping that he could get an explanation.

Chapter 68

Matt felt a bit perplexed as he looked at the rotund man that was rubbing his forehead. The manager and the lady tried to help their boss up to his feet, but he was just too heavy for the two of them. They fell on their butts after the woman slipped and lost her grip on her boss' arm. After the people were done with their comedic routine they finally started to talk, recounting the previous day.

"He came at sundown, he somehow managed to remove the cities protective formation. The experts in the city cowered in fright and didn't even dare to come out to face him... damn cowards..."

The man blew his nose and continued speaking in a solemn tone.

"The demonic aura soon filled the whole area, it was truly overbearing. He said that he demanded ten beautiful women as his brides and that he would pick them out himself. He then used some kind of strange purple glowing treasure that looked like a medallion."

The chubby merchant wiped some sweat from his brow, he looked like he was about to cry again.

"He started pointing that thing at the poor girls, t-they got sucked into it, he got my little girl too..."

Matt rubbed his chin while listening to what the man was saying, it looked like the demonic cultivator probably captured the women to perform some kind of ritual. Could also be part of his cultivation method, he knew that some cultivation methods required people to sleep with each other. He didn't like where this was going, would he sacrifice those girls to some demon, or suck their life energy? None of those choices was any good.

"Hmmm..., tell me where he went. There is probably not much time left for those girls."

He didn't want to sugarcoat it as he replied in a serious tone, he would try to save those girls but he didn't want to give these people high expectations. The manager stepped in this time around, telling Matt in what direction the man left.

"Also when that man come here? Did he touch anything? Or do you perhaps have something that belonged to your kidnapped daughter?"

He had his tracking skill by now, maybe he could get a whiff of the man's aura that would point him in the right direction. He might also be able to home in on the aura trail of the girls. He received some kind of hair accessory that was giving off a faint spiritual signal, he could see a purplish energy trail going all around the merchant house which didn't help him out that much. In the mess of trails he could point out an ominous looking one.

It looked like a strand of vape smoke just drifting about and out of the front door. He stepped outside to follow the trail that was mixing with some other random aura trails. If he didn't home in on it in the merchant building he would probably not be able to single it out in this piled up mess.

"Okay, I got his trail, I'll be leaving then."

He jumped up into the air, skillfully removing his flying sword from his spatial ring and wooshing into the distance before the people around him could say anything back to him. Truthfully the merchant and his workers didn't expect much from this man, they thought that he would either flee or die, still the father prayed that his lovely daughter would be rescued.

*The more I stay in this world, the bleaker it gets... demons, monsters that kidnap infants in the night. People that care more about power than the well-being of others, rapists and murderers everywhere... not sure why people like these kind of worlds in those novels, prefer them less chaotic, wonder if I can change the peoples mindset...

He rubbed his glabella with the eyes closed before opening them up and following the smoke trail. He was set on rescuing those women, hoping that he would make it in time before it was too late. He tried to be positive but the surroundings were throwing him curveballs every time. The trail brought him towards a mountain range that looked even more gloomy than the town he was previously in. The wind was whistling and storm clouds were gathering, lightning and thunder filling the surroundings. It looked like these were the so-called dread peaks.

The moment he got close he noticed that the trail was getting thicker and thicker, leading him towards one of the mountain peaks. He arrived at the spot, his sword drawn as he could feel quite a bit of demonic Qi around. But besides some trashy looking demonic beasts there was no one in sight. He focused on the trail, but it turned from one smoke stream to multiple ones and soon just filled the whole surrounding area so much that he had no way of telling where the demonic cultivator went. His sytem map didn't show much either, just pointed out some dots here and there but it could't pierce through the mountain not showing any life signals.

*His demonic qi is filling the whole mountain top, I can't tell where he went from here... is there some kind of secret passage?*

The cultivator was at a high level and he managed to survive for so long even with people on his trail. It was wise to assume that he had some kind of hidden lair or some kind of treasure that hid his presence. Maybe if Matt could find the entrance he could figure something out, but his tracking skill wasn't pointing him to it.

He thought about the hair accessory that he received from the merchant, he pulled it out in the hopes that maybe he could home in on the woman's aura instead. The tracking ability was quite easy to use, he just needed to concentrate on one energy signature and it would show him the trail if that type of aura was in the surroundings. He concentrated, the dark smoke vanished as he focused on the accessory that gave out its own light purple smoke signal.

*Okay, I've locked on to it... let's see if I can find something here...*

He looked around while hovering on his sword, trying to pick up the purple aura. It only took him a couple of flights to finally spot the trail in question. He followed it to an unsuspecting wall, it didn't seem like there was anything there just a part of the mountain, not even a cave. The purple smoke was clearly going into the rocks, telling him that there should be an entrance somewhere.

*Should I just bust through? But won't that alert that guy to my presence...*

He changed his trail vision back to the evil cultivators, dark smoke filling his vision as he looked around. He spotted a certain spot that was a lot darker than the rest, it was a tree stump with a hole in it. After fiddling for a second he actually found a lever in there, after pulling on it he could hear some kind of mechanism getting turned on. The wall started rumbling and suddenly vanished into thin air revealing a corridor behind it.

*Great, more corridors...*

He placed his flying sword back into his storage ring while pulling out his Spirit Infusion Longsword, he also thought that the name for his weapon was a bit too long. He would have to give his weapon a better name like 'Lightbringer' or 'Thunder-fall'. For now, he hid his aura as much as he could and went into the tunnel, inside he was rewarded with some stairs, though they were going upwards into the mountain peak and not down this time around. The peak in question stretched into the mountains for quite some time, so this might have been a long walk.

*What's with all these damn stairs... *

He focused back on the purple trail that continued on, the daughter of that merchant had to be here somewhere he had to hurry up and rescue her along with the rest. Luckily it didn't take him half an hour like last time as he came to a clearing and could even hear some voices in the distance.

He started sneaking towards the noises, there was light coming from that area and the door seemed to be open the demonic cultivator probably wasn't expecting any visitors. Matt tippy-toed his way and slowly peeked out of the door entrance while remaining vigilant. It wouldn't be funny if he got attacked the moment he looked in, so he kept his guard up.

What he saw inside was a strange-looking room. He was on the upper floor and there were handrails in front. When he looked down he could see a circular room, the ten women were there. The females were bound and strung up on what looked like one of those bondage contraptions. It was in the shape of an 'X' with spaces to bind the hands by the wrists and legs by the ankles. There was a large bed right in the middle and there was a woman on it. She had a collar around her neck with a chain attached to the bed, she was trying to yank herself free while a man was disrobing himself.

*I didn't think they called him Ravager due to his pervy tendencies...*

Zhang Dong looked around, the women looked to be fine for now just naked and bare. They all were kind of shapely, guess the demonic cultivator liked the voluptuous types. He was about to pounce on the sexual deviant but then he looked at the woman on the bed, she was really familiar looking...

*Wait... what is she doing here... Was she that fatties daughter? *

Chapter 69

The previous day.

Lan Fei was going through her inventory checking if everything was in place as she was getting ready to head out once more. She arrived in Frostriver a week ago. She was the daughter of the chubby merchant boss but she didn't want to tell him about the fiasco back at Moonlight city as she knew that her dad was very overprotective. If it was up to him, she would probably not be allowed to leave her old home. Fei had to force him to let her travel as one of the caravan leaders in the first place, he didn't need to know what happened.

She sighed to herself as she thought about the incident that happened back in that city, but more about the way she run away from that cultivator. After coming back home and unloading the things that they got, she went to get some info on that Zhang Clan. To her surprise, the man that she had a passionate night with turned out to be quite the warrior. He managed to defeat the invading forces single-handedly driving them back and even slew a late stage core formation cultivator.

The man also became the new clan Patriarch within a month's time. What was a clan Patriarch? He was the leader of at least one city , but Fei knew that after he got settled in the clan would probably regain back their former land. That was a lot of assets and resources, ones she could have a bid for if she just didn't run.

*Darn Fei you blew it. I could be getting my feet massaged while relaxing in one of those springs in that Spiring Spring City.*

She slumped her shoulders while thinking that she let a golden goose escape her clutches, plus the man was quite the looker so there were no downsides. She, of course, didn't know that the Zhang Clan was getting forcefully recruited to go back to that secret ground. She might have been singing a different tune then.

*Well, at least I got away with my head intact, maybe dad wasn't wrong when he told me that it was too dangerous to go out to other cities... but it's so damn boring here... If I stay here he'll just pawn me out to some ugly senior*

She looked around the snowy surroundings and the chimneys that were spewing dark smoke. Due to the cold weather people mostly remained in their homes, there wasn't that much to do around here and Fei being still in her prime wanted to tour the world. She was also planning to nab herself a good hubby, he, of course, had to be loaded.

*Maybe if I visit that man he'll take me in... he was quite fond of me, though he did look quite silly when I was making my moves on him. Kind of cute...*

While thinking about some schemes to get back on good terms with the Zhang Clan Patriarch she heard a rumble. This was the sound of the cities protective barrier breaking, soon an ominous aura filled the whole city. The loud voice of a man could be heard everywhere.

"It's me th' mighty Ravager, ah deman' ten of yer most right purdy wimmen as tribute, they will become mah brides!"

The man flew around an eerie looking flying sword, somehow he could tell where the so-called purdy wimmen where. He pulled out a silver medallion, it had some kind of runes on it and glowed a purple hue. He pointed it at a woman, the female started getting surrounded by a purple light and then got sucked into the metallic trinket.

Soon he found his way up to the merchant building. His demonic aura was making everyone kneel and unable to move, he looked at the trembling Lan Fei with a grin on his face. The man was surprisingly good looking, he had long golden hair and strong facial features that made him look like prince charming.

"Ah yer a fine specimen, yer fit t'be th' prime vessel, ah reckon."

He didn't give the female much time as she got sucked right into his magical treasure like the rest.

Fei landed on her butt in an open field and she could see more women around her. This treasure apparently transported people into a sealed-off space that looked like a grassy field. There was even a large building in there, right in the middle. How did the people in there know that it was a sealed-off space? Well, the women could see that they were standing on a small rocky island that seemed to be floating in the void. They could see the end of the small landmass that was about five kilometers in diameter with the building in the middle and grass filling the rest. After the tenth lady dropped in from thin air, they could hear the kidnapper's voice seemingly coming from the void.

"Don't wo'ry mah buttercups, soon we will be one."

This was the only thing the man said while he flew back to his lair, some of the women just collapsed crying while others checked the building out hoping to find something in there to aid them. The house was quite unkempt, dirty on the inside spiders and roaches everywhere. It was clearly not getting managed by the crazy cultivator, there was nothing in there besides bugs and some skeletons that gave the females a scare. It was quite large with many rooms, if Matt was here he would think that it looked like some kind of student dorm.

After some time passed the man finally appeared amongst the ten scared women. He didn't say much before grabbing one of them and just vanishing into thin air. He returned after half an out or so just to grab another to bring her out. He was undressing the scared females while hoisting them up in his ritual chamber, taking his time as he was having fun.

Fei was left alone after the ninth female got removed from the small pocket dimension. She collapsed on the ground not knowing what to do, why was she so unlucky did someone curse her or something. She wanted to defend herself but the difference in cultivation was just too huge. She was dropped off on that large bed with a collar and chain around her neck, her eyes glaring daggers at the man in front.

"Don't look at me like thet mah li'l vessel, ah reckon. Eff'n thet stoopid Sect didn't git rid of all th' cultivato's aroun' hyar Even ah w'dn't dast t'do this~"

She had a hard time understanding his dialect, but more or less the cultivator said that due to the drop in powerful clan cultivators in the area the evil cultivator could come out of his hiding and do what he pleased.

"Yo' might be wonnerin' why fo' ah brought yo' all hyar mah ladies, Well..."

He started disrobing himself, the only thing remaining on the man was his underwear and a glove on the right hand.

"Ah's in need of yer essence, ah's runnin' outta time yo' see..."

He pulled off his glove letting the women see a darkish looking hand, it had many warts, blisters and boils with puss on it looking quite hideous.

"Yo' will gimme yer life essence so ah may recovah."

Lan Fei was backing off on the bed but was held back by the collar and chain, she yanked on it but to no avail. Ravager started pulling down his underwear, presenting himself bare to the women that went wide eyed at his 'little brother'. The thing he had between his legs looked like a serpent, but the head was a mix of an alien and a predator. It wiggled around while bearing its teeth at the naked woman in front.

"Don't wo'ry mah dear, its quite th' nice feelin'... fo' me."

All the bondage crosses started to glow with a bizarre light. The women on them started squirming as they felt their spiritual essence getting pulled out of them. The essence was getting guided to the bed in the middle, the vessel would receive it all and then transfer it to the demonic cultivator as she got devoured by him.

While the evil cultivator was focusing on the voluptuous woman in front, she was looking behind him. Fei could see another cultivator slowly approaching from the back, sword in hand. As the cultivator made contact with her eyes he moved his index finger to his lips. The demonic cultivator was not aware of the man behind him as his lower snake was thrashing about slowly pointing towards the bewildered woman.

"Noo... S..stop my father is a rich man, we can give you thousands of spirit stones if you let me go... you don't need to do it..."

She shouted out in a loud while trying to keep Ravager occupied with her, hoping that the man behind him was someone friendly. Her wording was quite natural, she was quite eloquent with words when it counted.

"Hah, whut kin yo' offer me thet ah can not simply take? 'Nuff talkin', time t'feast!"

As the man was ready to pounce on the defenseless woman, he suddenly felt that something was off. He got a bad premonition but was just a bit too slow because as he was about to turn around he felt something hit his neck. Wind pressure could be felt around the room as the cultivator dressed in black swung his sword, making sure to swing with all his might as he decapitated the evil cultivator. The man's head flopped down onto the bed while his body fell down like a puppet with its strings cut, the essence drawing ritual instantly stopped after the man lost his head.

"Well... that was easier than I expected..."

The man said while looking at the dead demonic cultivator on the bed, black blood shooting out of his neck stump while the women in the room looked on at the spectacle. They didn't know how to react, was this man here to save them?, or was he just another bud guy, he certainly had the bad guy looks. Fei was about to say something but then the man backed away while muttering something.

"Wait... there was no..."

Before he could say the sentence the snake-like thing that was between Ravager's legs shoot out straight for his face. His sword got knocked to the side but somehow the cultivator evaded while grabbing the serpent-like appendage with both his hands. The women could see how the cultivator in black started pushing and pulling on the elongated thing that spat yellowy-white goop at him. He managed to dodge to the side, but the goo was quite acidic as it burned a big hole in the floor behind the two.

*Aww hell naw...*

Matt thought while Ravager's body contorted in unfeasible ways and stood up without the head attached. The body's knees and elbows were bent in the wrong direction and his hands and feet turned into claws. The whole body started turning to the way the evil cultivator's hand looked like as it attacked the man in black.

Zhang Dong was a bit afraid to let go of this snake thing that was spiting suspicious looking liquids at him. Instead, he used one of his skills that increased his grip strength. His fingers glowed with a metallic luster the creepy looking thing started swelling due to the pressure. The creature tried to back away but was held in place by Matt's vice-like grip. But this wasn't over as the demon suddenly felt electricity running through its body, lighting up like a Christmas tree, its strange high pitched screams filled the surroundings.

While this was happening the woman on the bed felt something moist graze her thigh. She looked down in horror as it was the demonic cultivator's head. It had vacant eyes but its tongue was out and licking her leg. She screamed while kicking the thing away, the head just rolled a bit before going down from the bed and to the ground going in the direction that the fight was happening.

"Look out, behind you!"

Fei shouted out as the head was somehow making its way towards him as he was electrocuting the body. It somehow jumped up, its mouth opening showing off a huge amount of sharp teeth. Matt turned around to see the horrible looking face coming towards him, he used his movement technique to dodge, grabbing his sword that was by the side going back to his fighting stance.

"weLL NoW, wE hAf aN uNweLcOmE gUeSt."

The demonic cultivator's head spoke while some tendrils burst out from the neck stump and reattached themselves with the main body. Zhang Dong grimaced as they were back to square one again, guess this wouldn't be that easy.

*Why do these people have so many regeneration abilities... damn hax*

A note from Kuropon

Chapter 69 ( ͡~ ͜ʖ ͡°)

Chapter 70

Matt thought that he had taken enough precautions in sneaking behind the unsuspecting demonic cultivator, he did manage to chop his head off but didn't foresee that he would be able to regenerate from that. He glanced around a bit, he didn't want to give the enemy time to recover but he also couldn't really lunch a devastating attack while there were so many innocent people around.

He needed to take the fight somewhere else, best would be outside. The enemy was on guard but momentarily out of commission while regenerating as he wasn't attacking. Matt thought to himself that it was a bit of a drag to have to think about collateral damage, he then placed his force field around Ravager and then started yanking him into the corridor that he came through. The two soon vanished from the main room, the demonic man was thrashing around in his barrier bubble.

The females found themselves alone in the main chamber, naked and bare. Most of them were a crying mess by now as they wiggled around shackled to the crosses. Lan Fei tried removing her chain but it was just too sturdy, she saw that Ravager had dropped his robe on the edge of the bed. She managed to reach it with her foot, yanking it towards herself rummaging through it in the hopes of finding a key. She couldn't find anything in there as the man probably kept all his belongings in a storage ring, it wasn't in here.

Luckily there was a huge boom outside in the mountain range, this made the entire room shake with so much force that the bed in the middle broke apart. The chain was still around her neck but it wasn't attached to the bed as it broke into several pieces. Fei run-up to one of the girls and tried to pry one of the shackles open, she still was a cultivator at the pinnacle of qi condensation so she wasn't weak by any means necessary.

The shackles started rattling a bit as she tried prying them open, but to no avail, this type of metal would be able to hold foundation establishment cultivators in place. She wanted to help the woman out but couldn't, she looked around hoping to find something else otherwise she would need to abandon these people. She spotted something on the side, it was round and metallic. It was the medallion the cultivator used to bring them here, maybe she could use it on the girls the same way he did.

She fiddled with the thing but couldn't make it work, sweat was running down her forehead as she noticed that the booming sounds stopped outside which might have indicated that the two cultivators stopped fighting. She clearly couldn't activate the pocket dimension with her spiritual power level, you at lest needed a core formation cultivation to do that.

She bolted to the side running around the room as she tried to find another exit beside the one that the two men had gone in. Then she heard it, there were footsteps. They echoed through the hallway that the two cultivators disappeared too. The sounds started getting closer and closer, the person took his sweet time as he was just walking towards the place where the women were still struggling in. Fei couldn't really do much besides pulling the chain to her body in the hopes of using it as a weapon, maybe if it was an enemy he would be injured enough for her to make a break for it.

Slowly a silhouette appeared, the steps were a bit heavy with indicated that the person coming had quite the weight to him. Fei peeked out seeing that it wasn't the demonic cultivator but the man that sliced his head off. The man looked kind of annoyed as he was rubbing his cheek that looked kind of red.

Matt had managed to defeat the pervy strange talking cultivator, he found him to be a lot weaker than the Dragon or Cthulhu look-alike, just annoying to fight. He wasn't as sturdy as the two and his regenerative capabilities were a lot more limited than of the squid monster. He was rubbing his cheek furiously only due to the fact that the man's trouser snake had managed to graze him there. It didn't do any damage, but he felt dejected by the fact that he got attacked by a demon donger.

He had promptly turned the evil man into minced meat before blowing him up with half of the mountain. He still had his spatial ring with him, there were quite a bit of spirit stones and demonic cultivation manuscripts in here. He jumped down into the circular room with a thud, the scared women looked at him with fright in their eyes which made Matt drop his head in shame as he had scared them even more.

"No need to fear that man is dead, don't worry I'll get you out in a second."

The man walked over to one of the women and grasped one of the shackles just tearing it apart while making sure to not hurt the ankle that it was around. After a couple of cracking sounds, the first girl was free and down on her knees looking at the scary-looking cultivator in front. Matt thought that maybe this wasn't the best face to use when rescuing fair maidens as he looked like a bandit himself.

"Hey, you stop hiding behind that column and come help me..."

Matt coughed into his hand while he beckoned the hiding Lan Fei over. He was a little mad about the last time they met, but all things considered, he couldn't stay that mad as the woman was really down on her luck. He waved his hand as he took out all the female clothes that the man had in his ring hoping that the females could use those.

Time passed and the females started dressing back up while the cultivator that introduced himself as Lei Yinglo went around the lair. The females gathered together, crying and hugging but also discussing if they could trust this new man. Zhang Dong toured the surroundings, opening some closed doors while looking at his system map that actually helped him find some hidden parts. He started looting the place, grabbing everything he could find he could just identify it later.

The girls looked on curiously as the man started forcing his way into some closed-off rooms that were behind some sturdy walls, giving them a scare, they found it a bit funny that afterward he came back and apologized while rubbing his neck. They were all beautiful women, so they noticed how he was acting quite bashful around them, even blushing slightly while mumbling something about tranquility.

"Senior Yinglo, everyone is dressed h-how will we be going back."

Fei asked with a concerned voice, she didn't know if the cultivator could carry them all on a flying sword. Matt was also finished with his looting spree, this was quite a big haul as the evil cultivator had amassed quite the treasure hoard, there were many spirit stones and crafting materials, though they were mostly of the demon beast kind.

"Hm... I don't think I can carry you all on my flying sword... leaving some of you behind would be a bit..."

The man was pondering while the girls fidgeted as he mentioned leaving some of them behind, they surely didn't want to remain in this godforsaken place anymore. Lan Fei, on the other hand, brought out the medallion and placed it in Lei Yinglo's hand.

"Sir, the demonic cultivator used this to transport us here maybe you could also use it."

Matt looked at the medallion and used his apprisal skill to examine it.

Name | Dimensional Regalia
Grade : | Immortal Medium
Attribute : | None
Durability : | High
Condition : | Damaged
Advanced Grade : | A+
Special traits : | This Spatial treasure houses a world of its own, due to its damaged state the area within is limited, can be repaired to increase the size.

His eyes bulged as he saw the grade of the item in front of him. It was the highest-graded item he ever came across. He quickly sent his spiritual sense into the item due to its previous owner's death it didn't offer any resistance whatsoever. He could see the small island floating in the void and the building in the middle. He did a little test and the girls saw the man get sucked into the medallion that promptly dropped onto the ground.

They all looked at each other wondering if the man would be stuck in it but soon he returned, appearing right out of the medallion.

"Okay, think I figured it out. Oh and I left you something to eat, it's on a blanket on the grassy field you can't miss it."

Soon the females found themselves back in the small pocket dimension munching on some strange looking things. It looked like two bread slices stuck together with some filling, it were, of course, some system bought hamburgers and cheeseburgers. Lan Fei was the last one that was in the room, the cultivator gave her a more meaningful look as he contemplated something.

"Is something wrong, Senior?"

The woman became a bit uncomfortable, not knowing what this man was thinking about but he probably wouldn't try doing anything weird at this point. She didn't know that the man in question was wondering if he should reveal his true face, but did he really want to continue this relationship. The woman showed a lot of character, as he overheard the women speaking. He heard that she didn't just try to flee on her own, but actually tried to help the other girls while he and Ravager were duking it out.

She did drop him like a sack of potatoes back in moonlight city the second she heard of his situation, this was kind of understandable all things considered. He wasn't that mad but his pride was still a bit hurt. But would she just do the same thing if she heard that he had to go to that secret ground, where death was very likely? There was probably no future left for the two of them, but at least he wanted to end the whole thing.

He shrugged and leaned over towards the woman, he held out his finger in front of her forehead flicking it.

"Owie..."

Fei backed away rubbing her forehead from the finger poke, not really knowing what it was for but then she saw the man's robes changing white, his hair growing out and his facial features switching around.

"Take that, that was for running away back in Moonlight city."

Chapter 71

"It's you!"

Fei exclaimed in a surprised voice.

"It's me, long time no see?"

Matt replied in a somewhat more relaxed tone.

"We should probably stop meeting like this..."

He scratched his cheek a bit while looking at the smaller female in front of him, he could see the woman's facial expressions cycle through a couple of times. She didn't know how to react in this situation as she did not expect to see this man again. Matt wasn't quite sure what he should say either, his experience with women had gone up lately but not by much. He decided to speak up first, trying to use a neutral tone.

"Well, why don't we leave first, we can talk on the way..."

He pointed to the exit and beckoned the voluptuous female over, he could bring one person onto his flying sword without having any drawbacks.

"Senior Dong... or is it Yinglo?"

Matt turned his head to the side trying not to laugh as his great naming sense came into the limelight.

"Dong is fine you can drop the honorifics..., the other one is just a pseudonym, it wouldn't look too good if the Zhang Clan Patriarch was bumbling about the place. We have enough trouble as it is with that dark palm sect business..."

Matt started talking, kind of blurring the dark palm sect thing out in the open but not like it was that much of a secret. This made the woman perk up as she started asking questions.

"Dark palm sect? Trouble?"

Fei asked a bit curious about the clan situation, from her point of view the clan was on the rise with the new strong Patriarch at its help.

"Ah yes...about that..."

He scratched the back of his neck while pulling up his sword. Pointing to the large thing as he invited the female cultivator onto it. He took the rear position, he was a head taller than the woman so he could see quite well.

"You don't need to be afraid, you won't fall down."

He brought his aura around the female's frame, he kind of naturally moved his hands behind his back as he stood on the sword. Lan Fei intuitively backed up into the man, grasping the hem of his robe even though the flying technique didn't allow any gravity or wind pressure to affect her. His new mind technique really kept his pervy tendencies at bay, as he didn't stare all that much but he still got quite excited due to the woman's close proximity. So he resumed where the two left off so that he could focus on something else.

"Yes, I'm sure you know of that expedition the Dark Palm sect ordered some time ago."

Lan Fei replied with a yes, due to the flying technique the two could hold a conversation even though they were flying above the speed of sound. The woman looked down at the passing by landscape a bit jealous of the core formation experts that could do this so easily.

"Well, those guys came right back and ordered the clans to do it again, ours included... I also have to participate"

Matt said while his voice became quieter in the end.

"Is that so Brother Dong..."

Lan Fei contemplated while Matt sweatdropped at the fact that the female was calling him brother now, guess he told her to drop the honorifics but he didn't realize that it would just switch senior to brother in her mind. This time Fei started talking speaking out in a shyer sounding voice.

"I have to apologize for the way I behaved back in Moonlight city..."

It was kind of a strange situation, the woman slept with him but then run away, the whole lead up to the act was mind-boggling.

"Ah, it's fine... it was a strange night, guess I lost myself to your charms, ha ha..."

The two started awkwardly laughing, the woman might have been a lot more experienced but people in this world conducted themselves differently. Relationships like on earth didn't really happen as people were more materialistic, families traded each other's children just to have better relations.

"Well, I guess this will be a good learning experience for both of us."

The two started chatting during the flight, the woman blushed after thinking things through at the way she acted just going for broke at seducing the man the moment she got the chance. Matt did the same, thinking back to the way he acted like a teenager and allowed himself to get seduced even though he should have been the more mature one. It took him a mind skill to be able to relax and not be stressed out around women, this was kind of cheating but it let him see things more clearly.

"Brother Dong, you have to understand, times are tough ..."

After a while, Lan Fei started unloading onto Matt telling about her troubled times and her thought process. He just started nodding and replying with 'Is that so?', 'Aha' and 'Your right' kind of getting lost while the lady chattered on. He also checked out the girl's stats while he was at it.

Name : | Lan Fei
Age : | 24
Cultivation : | Qi Condensation 12th level
Potential : | B-
Trust : | 40%
Alignment : | Chaotic Good

*40% I'm not sure if that's high or not...guess she trusts me more than the average person?*

While he was thinking the trust level shifted to 41% on the fly, guess the more they spend time together the more it increases. Her potential was quite high as well, probably if she had some sort of good cultivation technique she could be in foundation establishment at this point. Or, it was due to her traveling too much and not focusing on cultivating.

He could see her cultivation techniques, they revolved around the wind element but she didn't have many fighting techniques to speak of. He could actually get into more detail with his upgraded analyzing skill, he had dropped in more points just for this.

Name : | Lan Fei
Potential : | B-
Elemental Affinities : | Wind B+, Fire C, Earth E,
Weapon Affinities : | Whip A-, Sword C-, Spear D+, daggers D-

He raised a brow at the weapon affinity, the one with the A- made him imagine Fei in a black latex suit, whipping people around while laughing.

*Oh, boy... I think I made a 'perfect common grade' whip while doing tests...*

The woman continued talking while Zhang Dong thought about some things he could give here before he left.

"And that's when I smacked him in the face and run away from home. Do you believe the audacity of my dad, trying to wed me to that ugly toad of a man, well he had the money... but that face... nothing like you Brother Dong."

She looked up smiling, as she went back to those alluring gestures the man just gave a forced smile, he didn't know one person would be able to talk non stop for this amount of time. From what he gathered, the female was very foolhardy, running away from home and forcefully starting her own caravan business. Her father wasn't all that rich so he couldn't really provide great security, it was a miracle that this woman didn't get sold off to some slave traders a long time ago. Guess her luck ran out recently, or perhaps it was his trouble attracting aura that caused all of this.

"W-well...uh... I think I better change we will be arriving in your town soon..."

He started shifting his appearance back to his pseudonym, his hair getting shorter and face getting more scars. The woman looked at the change in appearance, astonished by the whole process yet again.

"I know what you might be thinking... but yes the previous appearance is the way I really look, I'm just thirty years old..."

The woman just smiled while nodding, this answered one of her questions as she was afraid that this big bro might be a big gramps on the inside just changing his appearance to suit his needs.

The two arrived in the snow city, everyone at the merchant building was surprised to see the rough-looking cultivator back so soon and their young miss was with him. Just as Lan Fei stepped down from the flying sword you could hear something in the distance coming at her. Matt could see a round blur just on a collision course with his female companion. This was, of course, the big round daddy, eyes all red and snot coming out of his nose. He was quickly kicked in the face by his daughter and fell to the side right into a stand with some fish.

"Waaa... how can you do this to your father little Fei, I was so worried... Sob sob..."

Matt looked at the comedic routine as the dotting father tried hugging his child with fish all over him, the girl in question just kicking and punching him away with disgust on her face.

"Stop it dad, you're all stinky..."

The man ended up hugging one of his daughter's ankles while she tried pushing him back with her other leg. While the two were busy he started pulling out all the other girl, they soon appeared outside hugging each other as they realized that they were back in their town. More townspeople gathered, slowly rejoicing as they got reunited with their mothers and daughters.

Everyone cheered as they thanked the scared up cultivator that proclaimed that he slew the evil Ravager and all was well. It had been about three weeks since he left the Zhang Clan, it was time to return. He just needed to drop the dead body of the evil cultivator and pick up the spirit stones he was owed. His alter ego's name was slowly getting known around these areas as he had slain that cultist monster and now defeated a powerful demonic cultivator.

Before heading out though, he handed Fei a spiky whip weapon along with a tome he got cheap from the store telling her that she should probably practice with this as she had potential in it.

"You should probably get your cultivation up and grow stronger, these are troubling times."

The woman nodded looking at the whip, she had never trained with a weapon like this. She didn't know how the senior measured her potential for this, but he was a powerful cultivator she should probably give it a try. She also received a wind cultivation method for the foundation establishment level, he had gotten it from one of the rings the cultivators had. It didn't take many points to upgrade it to a suitable level that she could use it. He still felt kind of bad for the girl for getting in so many weird situations, he would feel more at ease knowing that she got stronger.

The woman looked at the gifts with astonishment, as she read through the manuscript she could tell that this was quite the refined technique.

"Br... Senior Yinglo, this is a bit much... I don't deserve this."

Her hands shook a bit as she tried giving the items back, as she fought against her materialistic nature, these were some costly things and to be honest she wanted to take them.

"Ah, no need, think of it as a present from a friend to another... hope you will do well in the future, no more getting captured."

The man laughed a bit as he hopped onto his sword ready to leave.

"W-wait, will we ever meet again?"

The woman asked while hugging the items she received to her body.

"Well, it wouldn't be safe around me but I guess you know where to find me..."

He flew away, he thought that this was probably not the best time for a relationship he had other things to focus on. He also didn't know if he could trust this woman, though she wasn't a bad person she just had a tendency for chatting and shiny things. He noticed her eyes glistering the moment he brought out the gifts, the way she was trying to resist the temptation was kind of cute though. Maybe if destiny allowed it they could meet in the future but first, he had to survive what the Dark Palm sect had in store for him.

A note from Kuropon

I will probably be taking a longer break, have been releasing a lot for the past two months without stopping. But due to this, the quality suffers plus I don't have time for other things. The bad scores didn't help either, but anyway thanks for sticking around for so long.  (･д･)

Chapter 72

After bidding the lady goodbye he headed to where he could pick up his reward, strangely enough, it was the same place that he got the spirit stones for the dragon. It would take some time till he got there though, he had to backtrack all the way there. It was close to the place he faced off against the dragon at the start of his journey. He wondered if the people would try to rob him again when he left the city, as he was 'wearing' a new face again. Though his new pseudonym was gaining recognition due to defeating two evil creatures.

*Took me over three weeks to get this done, guess I'm on track. *

He looked at some other wanted notices, this made him feel like a bounty hunter. He wanted to see if he could grab a fast one alone the way but couldn't really see anything worthwhile. Core formation beings were rare, it was even harder to find ones that you could hunt for money as most people wouldn't even bother putting up a wanted poster. Maybe if someone offended some big shot, or was a demonic cultivator like that Ravager fellow.

*Well, guess my detection range increased a bit, maybe I can find some demonic beasts around here.*

He was becoming quite the monster hunter lately, he also had the white hair to go with it, just needed to get a wolf medallion to place around his neck. He had that one he looted from Ravager, but he was afraid to leave it out in the open. The sects were quite bloodthirsty and everyone was rushing for that immortal ascension thing, they would probably kill his entire bloodline to get something in the immortal grade.

He also took a peek at his cultivation skill, mainly his next upgrade path. He had three choices and after getting his first evolution into the empowered lightning tree he could finally see what those colors did.

Golden Lightning Path | The cultivator's lightning imbued with more heavenly powers with an added holy element, creatures of the demonic nature are highly susceptible to this type of energy. This path doesn't favor offense nor defense boasting an all-around increase in combat prowess.
Violet Lightning Path | The cultivator's lightning takes a more chaotic nature, harder to control but a lot more destructive than the other two types. This path favors offense increasing the cultivators Qi reserves the most, allowing for prolonged use of techniques.
Azure Lightning Path | The cultivator's lightning becomes in tune with the heavens, this is the most stable form and easiest to progress in. Favor's defense over offense increasing the resistance of all construct and defensive type techniques.

He read through the information once more wondering which path he should go for. The first option was quite interesting, it would aid him if he ever faced off against demonic beings like the Cthulhu lookalike. He felt that there would probably more of that kind of monster around in the future, so this could be useful. Matt didn't really have a defined fighting style just yet, though he mostly finished his enemies at close range.

The second one had 'Mage Class' written all over it. He would gain the biggest Qi pool from the three and would be able to spam his skills more. Guess bombarding enemies with overwhelming ranged skills could work, he also had his body refining skill for close-range fighting. The last one looked the least interesting as it favored defense but the increase to his construct type techniques like his avatar form and the lightsword was tempting. Though would this push his constructs to another level, or would they lose out against crafted weapons and other items in the end anyway?

He looked at the golden path, it looked like the most interesting one with the added elemental affinity. Maybe he should get some healing skills to go with it, or some auras like Paladins tend to have in games. He could imagine him and the Zhang Clan fighting in the secret ground together, him using some aura skills to boost everyone's stats, maybe using something to boost stamina and Qi recovery.

*Well... it's always more fun in a group? Guess I'll have to check if aura skills like that even exist around here.*

He checked out the shop to see if there were any paladin or cleric like skills. There were some but there was a small problem, he couldn't use them unless he was cultivating a holy element based cultivation method. This meant that he needed that upgrade before he could even use the cheapest healing skill.

*Well that sucks, can't even test things out ... this upgrade costs quite a bit...*

He looked at the 1 million spirit points next for the upgrade, the previous one only cost 100 thousand points. By this logic, if he wanted to get that golden nascent soul upgrade afterward he would need to spend 10 million points on it, maybe more as this was a full large cultivation level.

*Yikes, think I'd need to kill over 50 core formation enemies in the late stage to get that many points, which wouldn't be that hard if I was some kind of murder hobo... Also not sure if I could find that many around unless I raided some sect.*

Matt thought that this system would be really overpowered if he lost his morals and just started extinguishing lives left and right. This was the perfect system for someone that liked to kill.

*Well, I guess you could also rob some kind of spirit stone mine instead...*

The spirit stones mostly came from mines that were scattered around the continent. The only problem with that was that they always belonged to powerful sects or clans with nascent soul cultivators that were there to protect the assets. This was understandable as spirit stones equaled wealth, it was the most common currency around the continent.

*I might be able to sneak in ... but when they notice the drop in spiritual energy after I absorb the stones, I'd get murdered.*

Matt shook his head as he gave up on trying to rob a spirit stone mine, he could rob some convoys but that would probably involve hurting other people. Someone might get killed or maimed, he also could get chased by some angry sect uncles and he wasn't that desperate quite yet.

*I need to up my cultivation as well, need to at least reach the late stage in both body and mind.*

Matt had tested out spending points on increasing his cultivation with not very good results. He could dump points into it for an easy increase but the more the percentage went up the more he had to spend. It kept stacking doubling each time which made him stop. Due to this, he didn't want to spend his points, only if it was urgent and he needed a quick power-up. He also didn't know how many points he would need to upgrade his clan's cultivation manuscripts to a respectable level.

*It would really be nice if I could go into my crafting abode while flying on my sword, it said that this medallion is damaged, wonder if I can repair it. Well I guess I have some time, I'll just do it at night.*

He parked his sword by a big tree in a clearing then hopped into his crafting space to see if he could do something with this dimensional regalia that looked like a medallion, guesses it belonged to some king once?

He did upgrade some of his equipment before, so he placed the medallion on the big anvil and looked into his crafting screen if something would show up. He saw the item getting scanned by the system before he saw the medallion's status screen.

Damaged Immortal Grade item detected, can't process please upgrade the crafting abode by at least one level.

*Meh... think I need close to 3 million to upgrade the crafting abode... guess I'll pass.*

He grumbled while removing the item from the large anvil.

*Well, it's still usable people can still go in there and bring stuff over... guess I'll get some of the clan members to clean up the building in the middle.*

Matt wasn't quite sure what he could use this closed-off space for yet, he hoped he could use the crafting abode to expand the size or maybe add some upgrades. He hoped for things that would aid in training, like slowing the passage of time in the pocket dimension. Many such artifacts existed in the novels he read.

*Guess that's a bummer, but it still can be used for training...*

He went inside that space with his sword, he could leave the little floating island but there was nothing around besides empty space. The air thinned out the further you flew away from the center as well. The peculiar thing about this place was, that if the ground was damaged it would recover after a short while. So you could train and destroy everything around you, the next day everything would be recovered. That is everything besides that unkept building in the middle, maybe it was brought in by someone and placed there and it wasn't part of the treasure.

He wondered if that secret ground would allow him to bring in more people if he placed them in this medallion. It would be unfortunate if it didn't, and they would somehow die due to this, that place was also made by an immortal so he wouldn't risk lives.

*Well, time to rest for a couple of hours then I'll go get my spirit stones. They should be done with the tournament by the time I'm back. Guess I could use this medallion as a secret training ground for my clan bros, there is enough space to run around and train. The amount of Qi in there is quite high as well. It also replenishes itself naturally for some reason. This Qi is a bit strange, it lacks any kind of elemental affinity, but its quality is slightly higher.*

Matt thought about the future while time was running out, the people back home were close to ending the event, the people selected for the expedition were the most skilled and willing warriors that the Zhang Clan could offer but they still needed some training.

A note from Kuropon

Small chapter update, had to change the cover art too. Probably going to be doing slower updates.

Chapter 73

Not much happened while he was picking up his reward, he left the chopped up remains of the demonic cultivator behind, he didn't feel like keeping that pervs body stashed in his storage ring. He also saw the idiot trio that he disrobed the last time he was around, they were acting a lot nicer though. They probably won't be bothering random cultivators for a while.

*Well time to go home..., home huh?*

He wasn't yet sure if he should call that Clan's city his home yet. He had only been in this world for a couple of months, so the feeling of longing wasn't quite there yet. After having some food he flew back to his clan, he hoped that his clan members would procure those crafting materials so that he could start crafting. He could make quite the amount of items as long as he had the materials as the rhythm game took between ten to five minutes. If the blacksmiths of this world saw him making weapons in five minutes they would probably get a heart attack.

*Zhang Kuo should at least be able to get the crafting materials for foundation establishment items, even though I can't earn that much with them they are a lot easier to make. Though also depends on how fast they can sell them*

If he made perfect grade weapons in the hundreds he could make quite a bit of spirit stones, the problem were the logistics. Unless you had a flying sword traveling between the big cities took quite some time. Maybe he could get ol' gramps do act as a courier, but he also wanted to upgrade the old man's cultivation method so he could get stronger.

*Guess I'll do it in the beginning so that our clan people can go between the cities and trade, would probably take them a couple of weeks to a month to do it.*

Thunder could be heard as Zhang Dong churned his cultivation to the max shooting off like a rocket towards Spirit Spring City. He needed to check those skills first, maybe he had enough points for everything and he was just overthinking it. While he was on his way he spotted an immensely huge mountain, on top of it a giant storm was brewing. Lightning bolts could be seen hitting the peak, while the hurricane-like winds were breaking nearby trees and scaring the beasts living in them.

He stopped as he was passing by, thinking that he could use that huge storm to increase his cultivation, he still had time too, so he dived right into that thing. He got bombardier by lightning bolts left and right, even he had a hard time absorbing all of this energy, coughing up blood as the rainwater drenched his whole robe.

While Zhang Dong was getting electrocuted at a snowy mountain peak, the tournament back in Spirit Spring city was coming to an end. Liu and Xue were still fighting it out as this wasn't an elimination event. The younger sister was barely keeping up at the 194 spot hoping to survive among the 10th to 12th Qi condensation clan members. Liu ended up around the 90th spot, his fighting strength being around the 11th level even though he was at the 10th level.

The two hadn't adapted to the lightning arts just yet but if they had more experience, they would probably jump a couple of levels above their peers.

Xue delivered a wind infused kick to one of her senior brothers that barely defended himself with the help of a saber that rattled after the impact. Zhang Dong's two disciples didn't have any weapons with them, they wanted to focus on what their new master was teaching them. They hadn't received any weapon training and their previous water-based techniques didn't really work all that well with the new lightning Qi ones, or they just didn't know how to synergize the two.

"You've gotten quite strong little Xue, but not strong enough!"

She was fighting an 18-year-old at the 11th Qi condensation level, she was barely holding her own. The youth swung his battle saber at her, she was barely able to evade the attack thanks to her nimble movements. The sylph physique added to her evasive repertoire quite a bit. Just after this happened you could hear people cheering from the sides.

"Junior Sister Xue is the best! You can do it!"

"Hey, if you hurt Junior Sister in any way you'll be answering to me! I'll pummel you to death!"

"What a stinky Senior Brother, you should be ashamed of yourself!"

Xue was quite popular among her own generation, probably it had something to do with her being one of those jade-like beauties. You could hear cheering and threatening shouts that were aimed at the opponent that she was fighting. The opponent gulped as he had heard that one of the opponents of this clan sister, was found beaten up and left naked in the streets.

The siblings were cultivating body refining physiques that were transforming their bodies. Liu was getting more manly, his muscles were showing in all the right spots that made him quite popular with the junior and some senior members. Xue, on the other hand, was getting her female attributes enhanced thanks to her Slyph physique, it probably helped that she was wearing more form-fitting robes so that she wouldn't get slowed down by them. She was focusing on her speed and nimble movements.

"Hey, you guys stop this is a serious event!"

Xue shouted at the peanut gallery, with her brows furrowing but that only made the people cheer more.

"Hah, she looked at me, look at that passionate gaze!"

One of the younger males said while another slapped his head from behind and the two got into a fight. In the end, the fight ended in a draw as the senior brother didn't want to get beaten up also he didn't need to get any more points. The top brackets mostly consisted of people at the 12th and 11th level. There were a couple of level 10's at the end, with Xue in tow. She was the only person that made it in while being at the 9th level.

Both of the Patriarch's new disciples generated a lot of buzz, some were envious also wishing that they could get taught by the strongest member of their clan. The two have been rapidly growing at an unprecedented pace, showing everyone that Zhang Dong was quite the teacher with superior cultivation knowledge.

Most of them didn't delude themselves into thinking that their Patriarch would pick them up as disciples. They realized that these two had a lot more talent, being the strongest at their age range even before Zhang Dong came along. But they were hoping that if they got into the best 200 they could get some pointers and rewards from their leader as they knew where all of them were going afterward.

The Clan members were mostly segregated by skill and cultivation levels. Matt was surprised when he previously toured the compound as the younger generation members went to something akin to a high school. They had normal classes that consisted of reading, mathematics, and the sort, combat aimed lessons were also taught. There were even classes on pill forging and crafting.

The people of the clan even wanted him to take a teaching position for the more experienced students but he quickly refused that proposal. There were four classes starting from common followed by mortal, then earth and at the end was heaven class. The last class was reserved for people at the strength level of 10-12th Qi condensation. So depending on talent and resources people of various ages attended.

The fourth week was coming to an end, all the placements were set at this point. The place got busier as every placeholder was ordered to list out their cultivation methods and battle techniques. The Patriarch apparently wanted everyone to get segregated by their cultivation method firstly, then by similar working combat techniques. Most people weren't sure what he was up to, did he want to check out the skills before giving them pointers. That would be extremely hard to do without seeing them preform first, how could he even know what they were good or bad at.

No one really knew what good it would do to look at some random clan skills, but they trusted in their Patriarch's strength at least. The way his disciples were progressing was also a boost to his validity as a teacher.

"How's everything progressing?"

Zhang Jin asked one of the Patriarch's new retainers, Zhang Kuo, he was mostly responsible for the calculating side of business while Zhang Ya was more in human resources, doing odd jobs.

"We are in the process of gathering the manuals that the Patriarch requested, there shouldn't be any problems in procuring them as the Clan members techniques don't vary that much. Also, we have gotten reports that all the missions that the Patriarch selected were carried out."

Zhang Kuo gave a jade slip to Zhang Jin as everything was written down there, the older man looking at the report with a mixed expression.

"Make sure none of this leaves this room, If my grandson wants to stay anonymous he has to have a reason for it."

The old man was a bit surprised by his grandson's battle prowess. That Lesser Calamity Dragon he took out would probably maul the old Patriarch that was in the core formation late stage, that thing had a really tough hide and anyone below the great circle would get trashed. Also, he fought another monster and a strong demonic cultivator that was nothing to scoff at, and the boy just bested them without a setback.

This grandpa would probably be less astonished if he knew that his grandson barely escaped with his life when he was fighting the first monster on that list. Still, the achievements were speaking for themselves, this Patriarch was already stronger than the old one, the problem wasn't him but the rest. The other clan members weren't ready, they didn't make it into the last selection for a reason.

Back at the mountain range Matt was in a hole, pulverized rock all around him while he was twitching while laying on this back. The lightning storm had done him in a bit, but he managed to absorb most of its energies before they dispersed. He felt like an overcharged light bulb as the chaotic energies circulated all over his body making him shoot of tiny sparks.

*Damn, didn't think this blasted storm would shred my clothes down to my boxers.*

His robes had begun regenerating already, but the chaotic energies in his body were making things difficult.

*Guess I should be careful in absorbing so much energy, but that was a nice boost of 10%!*

He dusted himself off the gravel and hopped up onto his sword, guess if he flew high enough people wouldn't see that he was bare-chested. He set off towards the clan, he wasn't planning on stopping to cultivate anymore the month was coming to an end and they only had two left, he had to start training his soldiers.

He had gained over half a million points from killing the three mini-bosses alone, but he also gained another 200k through killing smaller demonic beasts along the way. He got close to 45k spirit stones that would translate to a bit less than ten times of that in points. So he stood at about over a million points now, having spent some to buy the sword arts, the disguise skill and the tracking skill which paid of in the end as he would never be able to find that pervy cultivator otherwise.

Some other people could have probably gained more points by killing more, like those three that he left naked and bruised. That wasn't his style though, it would be nice if he could get a fraction of the points for just beating up people instead. He also didn't run into any spirit stone convoys that he could try to rob, though he would probably be apprehensive about that as well.

While in thought he started noticing some familiar scenery as more water springs appeared on the horizon. The water elements started being abundant and the familiar smell filled his nose.

*Home sweet home, huh?*

Chapter 74

Matt canceled the disguising art during his cultivation period in the mountains, so he was back in his white robe looking like the Patriarch that everyone knew and loved. Well, at least that was what he hoped for. People on the ground spotted him flying in, he cruised by by the gate and just gave the guards a nod, this making the men freak out and do sort of a salute.

"At ease?"

He flew back to the main clan building, trying to slip in without making too much of a commotion but the moment he landed he could hear footsteps coming, people were apparently waiting for his return, he could hear some youthful voices.

"Master! Welcome back!"

The shout made his ears ring as his male disciple greeted him with a wave followed by a small quick bow with clasped hands. Matt looked at the sixteen-year-old, his hair was a lot whiter than before but you could still see the black strands in there. His sister appeared right behind her brother, a pout visible on her face.

"Aww, I wanted to greet Master back first... not fair..."

The girl puffed up her cheeks while glaring at her brother that was looking kind of smug. Matt didn't know how to react, was it some kind of grand achievement to greet your master first? The kid sure looked like he had won some kind of prize, while the young lady pouted like a little child. Though their master started chuckling to himself, finding the siblings to be quite the comedic duo.

"Well, Liu my student for greeting your Master first, you have earned the right to a reward!"

The brother perked up at his masters' words, you could see his eyes shining with anticipation.

"R-really Master?"

"Hah, you wish!"

Matt replied with a smile on his face then ruffled up the youth's hair with his larger hand. The sister started at her squirming brother that was getting his hair rearranged by their master. This was a peculiar sight, most master - disciple relationships were more no-nonsense but Zhang Dong liked to keep a more relaxed atmosphere where people weren't that tense around him. After he was finished teasing the youth he asked about the tournament.

"Well, I didn't see the report yet, how did you fare in your fights?"

Zhang Liu was grasping his messed up mop of a head, trying to calm down his long locks, due to that Xue answered instead.

"We both got into the top 200 participants! They had no chance against Masters' superior cultivation and combat techniques!"

"She meant to say that she barely made it into the 195th spot."

Liu snickered under his breath while his sister snow-white complexion started turning pink, her eyes in the form of daggers were pointing in the direction of her brother that was having a good time.

Matt crossed his arms over one another and looked at the two, the two would be going with him, their life probably depended on his decisions. He sighed inwardly hoping for the best, the two made the decision to come along on their own but they were far too young in his opinion.

"Is that so..."

"Well, I'll check your progress later you two. First I have to speak to your grandpa, we need to start preparing for that expedition..."

The two quieted down, the atmosphere got a bit more serious as their Master started talking about the impending quest into the unknown. The two bid their master adieu as he went to his chambers, his two retainers and Zhang Jin were already waiting for him.

"I see that you are back Dong'er, were you successful in your travels?"

Zhang Jin asked while the two people on the sides gave small bows of respect to their acting Patriarch.

"More or less, got some loot. I went through it all and there are some things that we can sell, but I'm not sure about some of these items, here take a look."

While saying that he handed one storage ring with some less useful treasures over to Zhang Kuo so that he could pawn them off. He handed a second storage ring over to his grandpa, this one contained a lot of occult looking items and demonic cultivation manuscripts. Matt didn't really know what to do with those, could they be sold of, or were things like these banned? Matt did look through all of them on his way here, he disposed of the more gruesome techniques, like the one that used women as batteries. He mostly left techniques and items that used the cultivators' life for bursts of power, if someone wanted to use things like those for a short term power increase they could go right ahead. He just didn't want more demonic cultivators popping up that used strange skills to bother the populace.

Zhang Jin just scanned the storage device with his spiritual sense, his eyebrow quivering oh so slightly.

"I see... we can't sell these with the usual channels, but there is a way, don't worry I'll have someone handle it."

Gaining more spirit stones was always a good thing, he could absorb them for more points or buy more crafting materials to equip his soldiers.

"So, did you do what I asked for?"

Matt looked at his retainers that nodded, they handed him a storage ring with a lot of old parchments and manuscripts. Some of them looked like they would crumble at the slightest touch. He also received a jade slip with the statics that showed him which cultivation techniques were the most used by the Zhang Clan members. Luckily the costlier ones that the foundation establishment seniors used weren't that varied, they all more or less cultivated similar water skills.

Mostly depending on the family ties and bloodline, a Zhang clan member could choose a cultivation method from a limited pile. The higher the grading the less of a choice there was, so most of the people tried their luck at cultivating the highest-ranked technique or skill they would find. Due to this, there wasn't as much verity, which would mean that there were fewer manuals to upgrade.

"Okay, I'll start with the foundation establishment ones first... Oh right, Gramps give me your cultivation manual as well."

The Zhang Clan members still weren't sure what their Patriarch was trying to do, what could he do with those old techniques, could he learn them all and train the people in just two months of time? This was a hard pill to swallow, there were over a hundred manuals in there even if you were a genius, you needed a couple of days to grasp even the easiest of skills. They didn't think that there would be enough time to do that.

"Ah sure, here you go..."

Zhang Jin handed his grandson the cultivation technique. The group discussed some other things, asking Zhang Dong about his travels. They gave him a general report about the tournament and what happened in the past month, but there wasn't much to report. The three left soon after, Matt could now concentrate on his next task. He removed the big bed from his storage ring and started placing all the foundation establishment manuals on the ground, segregating them by general cultivation manuscripts, then combat techniques which were further segregated into ones that required and didn't require weapons.

"There we go..."

He picked up one manuscript, it was called Rainwater Sutra. It was a general cultivation manual and this was the second part of it. This was the method the main family line practiced, along with his new disciples that switched over to his now. There were three parts to it, that went from Qi condensation up to core formation, but the third part was incomplete. Due to this, it was impossible to cultivate it to the great circle and you could barely get into the late stage if you bumbled around.

Rainwater Sutra part 1 (Common high grade): | The first part of a cultivation manual, suited for cultivators with water affinity. Gives a more than moderate insight into qi condensation.
Rainwater Sutra part 2 (Mortal high grade ): | The second part of a cultivation manual, suited for cultivators with water affinity. The foundation pillars forged through this method are more or less stable, but flawed ones can arise.
Rainwater Sutra part 3 (Earth low grade ) [Incomplete ]: | The third part of a cultivation manual, suited for cultivators with water affinity. It's missing a lot of information, cultivators won't be able to cultivate past the late stage if they follow the incomplete instructions and it will stifle their progress.

Matt raised a brow at the explanations, the best cultivation method of the clan wasn't all that great. The ones the core formation elders were supposed to use even got them stuck in the late stage. This was the one his grandfather was using and the same one the previous Patriarch used as well.

He brought out a different cultivation manual, it belonged to the first man he killed it was called called 'Inferno art'. It had quite the cool sounding name, but the grading was just as bad as the one that the Zhang clan was using. Matt had checked every core formation manual that he got from his travels and they all were of lower grades, sometimes incomplete with glaring flaws. This was probably why no one was able to reach the nascent soul, the methods these people used were just abysmal.

*The manuals for foundation establishment and Qi condensation are better, but still they aren't perfect, no wonder the sects treat the clans as lower-class citizens. I bet they hog all the good methods to themselves and just laugh at the clans that bumble their way through the process.*

Matt could see that past the foundation establishment the clan was reaching a bottleneck in their techniques. The lower the grade of the method the more damage one suffered to their body. Like with the Rainwater Sutra, it outright stopped the cultivation process after the late stage.

*Also the advanced grade is quite low and that rainwater part isn't good either...*

Cultivation methods mostly fell into a certain Dao. The Rainwater Sutra was derived from a greater Dao of water and was a lesser Dao. The closer to the 'Source' of a Dao you got, the better it was. Zhang Dong's lightning cultivation was from a greater Dao, the inferno art was also something created from the greater Dao of fire, or yang as the people in this world liked to refer to it.

What was the difference between a lesser Dao and a greater one? A person that followed a lower path would always be weaker than a person that followed a greater one. Also, you could not progress into the immortal stage if you didn't have any insights into a greater Dao. Most cultivation techniques in this world were just crude imitations of greater Daos, but they were a lot easier to produce.

*Guess I lucked out with my greater Dao of lightning, I wonder how many spirit stones I could get for my cultivation arts...*

This was a tempting motion, to start selling improved versions of cultivation methods. But then some scary sect uncles could come knocking, wondering where he got them from.

*Think I better wait till I'm in the nascent soul for that...*

He picked up the manuals that the foundation establishment members used and started upgrading them.

Rainwater Sutra part 2 (Mortal high grade ) Do you wish to upgrade this cultivation manual. Yes/No?
Springwater manual (Mortal middle grade ) Do you wish to upgrade this cultivation manual. Yes/No?
Dragontide manuscript (Mortal middle grade) Do you wish to upgrade this cultivation manual. Yes/No?

His points started going down and down, he got them all up into the mortal perfect grade. This wasn't the limit of the upgrading though, you could improve them further. He also used an immortal grade cultivation manual that was for core formation practitioners. The only rule was that a manual couldn't be of a lower grading than what the cultivation level was. So, if you were in the foundation establishment realm your cultivation manual couldn't be off common grade, that just wouldn't work.

*Should I upgrade them into the earth grade, or is this enough...*

Matt thought that upgrading a technique of a lower level into a higher one would probably be very beneficial to the cultivators that practiced it, even if it was only in the lowest of them. He was glad that there weren't that many of those scripts for his foundation establishment members, so it didn't cost that much but still he lost eight thousand points a pop.

*This better be worth it, could buy myself an earth grade skill for this... Though it's not that much at this point*

There would be more spirit stones coming in so he could spend some points on these things. He needed to go through the other parchments before deciding if he could upgrade anything past the lower earth grade.

*Though there is one problem...*

The upgrading process didn't do anything to the manuals he was holding, the refined techniques were added to his system's library which he now had an icon for. He could click on it and read through everything, he also got the knowledge inserted into his brain as always.

*Damn, do I need to write these down myself now?*

The Impartation skill was good and all, but it wasn't perfect so he needed to complement it with the written down texts. As always, the system came to the rescue as it had various calligraphy and copying skills that he could buy, and they didn't cost much as they weren't used for battle.

He bought two skills, one called hyper calligraphy the other beautiful penmanship as his writing style was quite trashy. Thanks to the first skill that let him smoothly scribble everything down within seconds, he managed to write everything down within fifteen minutes. Which was quite fast for so many complicated manuals.

*Think I should hand these over so that those guys can go to work, still so many things to go through...*

Chapter 75

A person was standing with both of his hands on his forehead. The man's name was Zhang Zhi, he had just turned forty this year but due to his cultivation, he looked like a man in his late twenties. He was the one that took the first spot for the foundation establishment elders at the clan tournament. Due to his fairly young age and high cultivation level, he was highly regarded amongst the clan.

Half an hour earlier he and the other tournament participants were brought into a room. There he saw some copied over manuscripts, even while they were walking in some women clan members were diligently working on copying them down from some nearby notes. He straightened out as he saw that their current Patriarch was standing there, handing down some papers to people that were copying them over.

"Ah, I see that you all are here, could you all just line up. There is much work to do, best if you line up in order of your tournament placement."

The patriarch ordered while waving his hand around, moving it in a certain direction. The Zhang clan elders looked at each other and just followed the instructions, lining up by the wall. Zhi was the first one getting approached by their new leader, he was slightly shorter than Zhang Dong and had a more ectomorph like physique. He looked at the silver-haired man in front of him as he placed his hand on his shoulder, he could feel some strange energy wash over him the moment that happened.

"Zhang Zhi, Great Circle, 40 years old... you should probably switch to sword arts from those spear arts...you practice the Dragontide method, I see..."

Zhi was a bit astonished that the man that he never interacted with started naming things that he shouldn't know. The man started claiming that he was better at the sword than the spear, he had followed in his father's footsteps that was quite renowned for his spearmanship. The white-haired Patriarch mumbled to himself for a moment before placing his index finger on Zhi's forehead.

"This might feeeeel a bit funny, just bare with it..."

The moment Zhi heard those words he could feel information getting forced into his brain. This knowledge was something that he knew by heart, it was about his cultivation method the Dragontide Manuscript. It was different though, the wisdom contained was far superior to the understanding of the technique he previously had. He backed away, holding onto his head in shock as most of the knowledge remained intact. He instinctively wanted to seclude himself and try out the improved cultivation method.

"T-this..."

Before he could say something the Patriarch looked to one of the people that was copying down his scribbles. Talking to them in a pleasantly sounding bassy voice.

"One Improved Dragontide manual, please~"

He said while one of the girls brought over the goods, Zhang Zhi got the item shoved into his palms his eyes going wide as it was the same cultivation method that was imparted into him, just written down the ink didn't even look dry.

"If you have any questions, they should be answered in there, now go reinforce the foundation, you have a week."

Zhang Dong had improved his Impartation of Knowledge skill, but it still wasn't perfect so he needed those copied over manuscripts with all the required data. Zhang Zhi being the typical cultivator nut started shaking furiously as he looked at the manuscript in front of him. He knew that improving cultivation methods that you didn't make yourself was extremely hard. But there it was, his family art improved even he could tell that it was far beyond anything the clan had in their library.

He was baffled, he wanted to hug the man in front of him and beg him to take him on as a disciple. But he managed to stop himself, for one this man was the clan's Patriarch and he already had disciples, two he was ten years younger than him. The others next to Zhi glanced in his direction, they saw his eyes redden and his lower lip quivering not really sure what was happening.

"Thank you, Patriarch, this Zhang Zhi will never forget this act of kindness!"

What followed was a furious display of ass-kissing in the form of kowtowing, which made the Patriarch's eyebrows twitch momentarily. He coughed into his hand and moved over to the second person. He placed his hand on the older looking man and within a couple of minutes, the man was down on his knees, thanking the young clan leader for being so benevolent.

Zhang Dong started moving past the quivering clan members, trying not to look at their over the top behavior. Everyone was receiving the improved versions of their cultivation methods. The ones that had yet to receive their manual had stars in their eyes and sweaty palms, they looked like a bunch of puppies before you fed them. Most of the people were old men past their forties, so the looks on their faces were priceless, Matt had to force himself to not laugh in front of them.

"Oh, you're Liu's and Xue's..."

About at the end of the line, was the mother of his graying disciples. She and Xue looked very similar, having that unhealthy white complexion that people in this world liked so much. She looked a bit more refined than her daughter that still had some baby fat stuck on her face, also she was quite flat. She made up for that deficiency with her back end, which was quite large in comparison.

"Zhang Jie greets the Patriarch."

She gave him the usual bow of respect before Zhang Dong went through the motions and imparted the improved Rainwater Sutra art to her. The woman was wondering what was the deal with this man, her children just couldn't shut up about how great he was. She finally knew how those two brats started progressing so fast, this man teaching methods were quite unusual. Her head was throbbing but her knowledge of the cultivation arts increased by leaps and bounds.

"You should tell gramps to not cultivate before I look through his cultivation art, it has way too many flaws in it."

She figured that this 'Gramps' that the new Patriarch was talking about was her grandfather Zhang Jin, she didn't know if she should laugh or cry about the way this man refereed to her adored grandfather.

"Ah yes... I'll be sure to pass it on, Patriarch."

The dazed Zhang Clan foundation establishment elders waddled out of the gathering room, their heads hurting a bit but this was a small price to pay. They all felt invigorated as with the imparted knowledge, they were sure that they could reinforce their flawed foundation pillars.

What was the Foundation Establishment cultivation realm? It was the first real step on the way to cultivation, everyone could condense Qi in this world, but not everyone was able to advance past that. If you wanted to further advance you needed to create your dao pillars, people that advanced to the early stage only had one pillar while advancing further they formed more. Depending on the cultivation technique the amount of those pillars varied. The thing that also varied was the state those pillars were in.

The lowest kind were the cracked pillars, a myriad of cracks like spiderwebs would run through them, indicating a flimsy foundation that could be shattered at any moment. After that came the flawed pillars, they had fewer imperfections ruining through them. These types of pillars were very common among the Zhang Clan practitioners. After that came the superior pillars, flaws in those were difficult to spot. The last ones were the perfect pillars, the rarest and the most difficult ones that a cultivator could produce.

A cultivator could have mixed pillars, flawed ones together with superior and cracked ones. Most people around the world that used average cultivation methods had flawed pillars with some cracked ones in the mix.

Zhang Dong having an immortal grade technique was the owner of perfect pillars. Also, they were special lightning dao pillars which increased their rarity even further. With the improved versions of the cultivation arts, Matt hoped that everyone could transform their flawed and cracked pillars to the superior version of them, maybe even add a couple of new ones in the process. The better your pillars were and the more you had of them, the smoother your cultivation path would be in the future. This was also the reason Matt was cultivating at such breakneck speeds, he faced no bottlenecks whatsoever. The only thing holding him back was the amount of spiritual energy he could absorb to expand his lightning core.

Back in his chambers, Zhang Dong looked at his system screen, the shoulder touching wasn't only for figuring out people's names and what they were good at. He could actually save everyone's stats into his database, in it he could see the personal data of the people he examined.

*I'm sure glad that I took that analyzing skill.*

He couldn't see the progress of the people he analyzed as he saw it in his Disciple section. He could pull up the database at any moment, update it and see how everyone was progressing. He could also plan ahead, like with Zhang Zhi, his talent wasn't that great only at a C+, but his affinity with the sword was at an A+. But for some reason, Matt saw that the only weapon techniques the man had were spear ones. Zhi's spear affinity was much lower at a C, it was a travesty that this man was training in an art he had no talent in.

*Should I get him to try out some sword arts, or is two months not enough...*

Matt didn't know if retraining yourself before going to battle in two months would be wise. But the A+ indicated that the man had superior talent in swordsmanship, also he was a lot older so some things should translate over. There were other people that were already using the sword as it was a common weapon type along with the spear and saber, so it would come in handy.

*I can't give him my sword art, it's for lightning Qi...*

Due to being the Patriarch, he had access to all of the best techniques that the clan could offer, though they were worse than even his lowest graded technique. He looked through the more advanced sword techniques the clan could offer, they were mostly in the lower or middle grade, but there was a high grade one that could be used.

Rainstorm Blade (Mortal high grade ) Do you wish to upgrade this cultivation manual. Yes/No?

He upgraded it to the low earth grade, the thing about this whole process was that he was learning all of these skills almost instantaneously while not even cultivating them. Matt didn't know if knowing so many skills would even be good for something, he looked through his technique library but he didn't see any options for combining skills which he could use.

*Damn, I can't even sell these as that would undermine my clan in the long run...*

He threw the motion of selling off cultivation arts out the window, as he didn't want a paper trail leading to his doorstep. Also, you couldn't earn much back for anything below the core formation as most sects and clans had their own stuff below that level. Training in some random techniques could impede your progress.

*Well time to go through the youngster techniques...*

He gave out a sigh as there were two hundred of those Qi condensation juniors he had to go through, at least upgrading techniques from Qi condensation didn't cost that much. Also, they weren't that bad as the foundation establishment ones, being a lot easier to produce for the lower level clans and sects like them. Matt flexed his cultivation aura which alerted a nearby clan member that was in his service. This was quite a nifty way of getting people to come over, he didn't even need to use his voice.

"Give this to the Zhang Zhi fellow, tell him that he should try it out. Also, tell the junior members to come to my chambers in order of the tournament results."

Matt didn't want two hundred people looking at him silently while he analyzed others one by one. It would be less stressful if he just takes care of them one at a time, they were young so they could wait in line all day. Which they would have to as he had to look at their cultivation method, write it down for them, then have others copy it over. This would be a lengthy process, they didn't have time and he also wanted to teach people some actual battle skills later on.

"Okay, let's get this over with..."

A note from Kuropon

Was wondering, would people be interested in a Discord channel for this story?

Chapter 76

Zhang Dong needed about ten to twenty minutes to process one person, but due to there being two hundred people that he had to go through it took him two days to finish everything. You could see a big line of nervous youths just outside his chambers. Matt made a mental note to have the clan members build him an office for things like this. There were a lot of people from the side families here so they weren't familiar with the place, their eyes moving left and right as they examined every nook and cranny. They looked at the inner members with envy in their eyes, but now with the new Patriarch also being from a side family, they felt like things would change.

After the two days without sleep, Matt flopped onto his bed. He had 198 more people in his database as he didn't need to add his two disciples that were already training in other things that he got for them. After checking out their affinities he noticed that due to his Dao of Heavenly Lightning their grades towards the lightning element were increasing. He sure wished he could afford to buy Dao knowledge for the water element with so many water cultivators around, but he only had a small fraction required. The Dao of water was a greater Dao, so it required a lot of points.

He laid on his huge bed looking up at the ceiling, but he was actually looking at his system window that was showing him the Qi cultivator profiles. Luckily the techniques didn't vary as much as he thought. This was probably due to this being a clan and not a sect, so most people specialized in similar fields. You didn't really have divisions for pill forging, crafting or beast taming as clans tended to stick to one profession. The Zhang clan specialized in restorative pill forging that went with their water arts that were suited for healing.

*Glad that their techniques don't vary as much as I thought. Got the basics down, now I need to prepare the regular weapon training techniques, the evasion techniques, they don't really use any body refining techniques...So still a lot of work left.*

The Qi condensation techniques were really cheap so he got a 'Water Nymph Physique' for the female cultivators, it was similar to the Sylph Physique that Xue was using. For the male cultivators, he found the 'Leviathan Constitution', this also belonged to the water element bracket. These two worked similar to the techniques that he got for his disciples, the girls got more agile while the men got more resistant. They were a bit worse than what he got for his disciples, but they were fashioned for water type cultivators so they would complement their strengths.

He decided on those two for one reason, they would let water cultivators use their Qi skills even in harsh environments devoid of any water elements. The more they progressed in his refining techniques, the more Qi they could store in their body for later usage and the less they needed to use for their other techniques.

Zhang Dong meditated for an hour, not sleeping just yet as he headed over to his dimensional regalia. Inside he saw many clan members shuffling about, they were crying various tools and resources. Some of them were sweeping, some of them were scraping the bricks from the moss. The more Matt gazed at the building the more it looked like a university dorm that he was familiar with. It was long and made from bricks with many rooms that were connected to a hallway. It was several stories high if you squeezed two beds into each room, you could fit about 250 people in. Maybe more, as cultivators liked to sit down and meditate instead of sleeping which took up less space.

After the walls got cleaned up you could see the reddish color of the bricks, it had that steep Mansard roof that Victorian-era buildings back on earth had. It had some sash and bay windows plastered in, making Matt wonder where this thing came from, as most buildings in this world were more or less Oriental, but there was that one western looking tavern back in the gloomy town.

The moment the people saw him they bowed and started working faster and harder, fearing that their new boss would start whacking them if they didn't speed things up. The place was getting renovated, beds and furniture were getting carried in as Matt was preparing this place for the training that he was going to give his warriors. He thought that making the people live around each other and spar would increase their coordination.

He was still of the mind that that whole place would be some kind of group activity, so he wanted to increase his peoples' teamwork. He wanted to implement some group exercises to elevate the synergy between his clan members. It would be good if they figured out each other strong and weak points, then complemented each other's flaws.

He wasn't going to do it alone, as he had some more experienced members help him out with the formations they could put the people in. They wanted to segregate people into groups, each Foundation Establishment elder would get a team of ten Qi condensation juniors to lead. He wanted to assign everyone at the start so that they could get to know each other better, this wasn't anything out of the ordinary as it was quite common to put soldiers into smaller teams.

"I guess eleven people isn't much of a platoon but it will do..."

He would be the company captain while the twenty elders below him would be his officers, the Qi condensation members would be the grunts. He would need to either make specialized squads or more all-around platoons.

*Well, if I use specialized groups it would be easier to train them. But if everyone gets split up and my medics are lost without any combatants to cover their butts, they will be screwed.*

Naturally, everyone was good at something, most people knew how to fight but the first ranker and the last ranker were miles apart. Matt thought back to his gaming days, mostly the MMORPGs he played. Most parties had a tank to keep the monsters busy while the damage dealers either used ranged attacks or flanked them from the side. The healers could then keep their party refreshed and ready for the next fight. There were also the buffers and debuffers and various other specialized classes, but he would be keeping it simple for now. The Zhang clan being a water elemental clan, had some good healing arts which Matt would be upgrading for future use as skills like those were a necessity.

*Guess I'll go for the more all-around team setup, better be safe than sorry later.*

*Got eleven people in one platoon, would be good to have at least one medic/healer, then some frontliners to keep the enemies busy while the backliners either bombard them from afar.*

He looked at his database, focusing on the Qi condensation members. There would be enough people with healing abilities to cover each team, but all platoons wouldn't have perfectly balanced setups as the people were picked mostly through combat. Teamwork was fine, but he also had to take into consideration that everyone would be separated and would have to fend for themselves.

The cool thing about this world was that the cultivators had specialized techniques for team combat. They were called formation techniques, Matt also fought against one of those formation techniques. The people from the Tsai clan had combined into a giant volcano golem and gave him a good whacking before he turned the tide. He was holding two books in his hands, they were the formation techniques that he had chosen for upgrading.

Floodarmor Formation (Mortal Low Grade) | This formation allows cultivators to produce a large shield in a wide area around them from water Qi. It can be used by Qi condensation practitioners in tandem with a foundation establishment cultivator that acts as the core of the formation. People within the formation can still attack from the inside while being shielded. Minimum 8 cultivators required.
Spirit Serpent Formation (Mortal Low Grade) | This formation allows cultivators to transform into a large serpent composed of water Qi. It can be used by Qi condensation practitioners in tandem with a foundation establishment cultivator that acts as the core of the formation. Minimum 9 cultivators required.

One was for attacking while the other was for defense. Matt hoped that with the increased grade the formation would shine even more, maybe allowing the people inside to reach close to the core formation level. The formation techniques didn't have any cap on how many people could use them, so in theory, if all 220 of them used that Water serpent transformation, going into the core formation area wasn't that far fetched.

*Would be good to get these up as high as possible, formation techniques are indispensable in large scale combat.*

He thought back to the rock golem, he still had that technique manual with him. It was of low grade of course, but he reckoned if it was of a high grade than he would have probably lost during the power struggle at that time.

Matt sat down on a chair that was brought in by his fellow clan members as he was still in the medallion realm. He scanned through the most used techniques, thanks to his library he could organize them like in a spreadsheet. Everything was nicely presented, from the most commonly used skills, the highest-graded ones, he could compare everything and take out the most essential ones for further improvement.

While he was busy with clicking the air, the Zhang clan members on the sides started staring at him while they cleaned the building. They looked with wide eyes at their silver-haired Patriarch while seeing him poking at the air in front of him. Was this some kind of ritual for a new technique or something? It would be far too rude for them to ask but the sight of their leader swishing his finger up, down, left and right was making these people have sweaty palms from the way their boss was frowning.

"Ugh, why are there so many of these skills... just learn one and stick with it..."

Matt rubbed his forehead while staring at his decreasing points that were declining with each second, soon he would run out. Luckily he got most of the skills that he wanted and more spirit stones would be arriving as well. The next thing on the agenda was the equipment, thanks to his golden touch he knew exactly what each person had an affinity for so he could design the right weapon and gear for them.

*Guess I'll have to use that dancing platform as well... the clan robes don't really have much to go for them...*

He vanished from the pocket dimension and appeared in a certain heavily guarded room, there were many intricate inscriptions on the walls that were pulsating with spirit energy. This was a secret chamber that the dimensional regalia was resting in. The moment he showed it of, his grandpa looked like he had laid an egg. He knew the implications of having this sort of item around, if any sect figured out that they had it with them, there would be nothing that could save them from extinction. Unless they just gave it away, but luckily this thing didn't give off any immortal artifact aura. You needed to get really close and actually touch it to feel the wondrous immortal radiation that it was giving off. So, they decided to hide it for now.

The people that were working inside had sworn an oath of secrecy, it was something to keep people's mouths shut. Other clans used different methods, in Zhang clan's case if a person tried blabbering out the secret they would find themselves bursting from inside. Guess there was a lot of water in a person's body, so a water clan would know how to come up with a technique that would use that and explode a body from the inside.

Matt was a bit apprehensive about the methods, but kind of knew that this was the only way to be sure that no one spilled the beans. The people that were working inside the pocket dimension weren't against it at all, everyone knew that this safeguard had to be made. Also, the people inside the medallion didn't actually know of the treasure's grading most of them reasoned that it was a heavenly graded artifact at most, as the dimension inside wasn't all that large. No one actually touched the item as it was used by the Patriarch.

Matt went out of the room and headed to his chambers, it was time to get some crafting done after that he would start cultivating, he really needed to get into that late stage as soon as possible.

Chapter 78

A large group of youths approached a certain room, there were many people close to the walls acting as guards. Before they were let in everyone was searched thoroughly. The atmosphere was tense as everyone was searched, no one knew what the fuss was all about they were just ordered to come here by the top brass.

These people were the two hundred Qi condensation expedition participants that were chosen through the tournament. The oldest one from them was twenty, while the youngest was Zhang Xue that was fifteen. Everyone here was devoted to the clan, no one with a shifty character would actually come this far. All of the people that valued their life more than they valued their clan, were already thinking about what they would do when the expedition probably failed again. It wouldn't be hard to leave the city on the pretense of a journey or business and just wait it out, some people like that were already packing up.

After everyone went through the check they were guided further into another room, there were a lot of stairs going down. They went further into the inner sanctum and into places not many people had been before. They were led into the dimensional regalia room, Zhang Jin was already waiting for everyone. Zhang Dong could give partial ownership to his magical treasure, he was kind of the administrator who could give moderator spots to other cultivators.

The medallion was hidden in the middle of the room, without giving off any immortal treasure fluctuations no one would be able to tell that the dimensional treasure was there. Most would just assume that the whole room was the portal to the separate small dimension. Everyone had already been given the finger poke of pain to the forehead by Zhang Dong while he was passing down the cultivation knowledge a few days ago. He would give an update about that a month later, but for now, he wanted to focus on his cultivation progress while everyone else did the same.

"Everyone gather up, anything that will happen in these next two months can not leave this room, is that understood?"

"YES, GRAND ELDER!"

Everyone responded while shouting out loud, but thanks to the silencing formations nothing could be heard outside. Zhang Jin looked at the promising youths in front of him, his heart started hurting as he knew that he was sending these poor children to a place they would probably never return from. He was hoping that somehow his grandson could pull off a miracle as he did before, but he was a special case, these youths were far, far weaker.

"I won't bore you with a long speech, but know this. A crisis can be an opportunity in disguise! Now go train well and train hard, the Zhang Clan is depending on your success."

Zhang Jin waved his hand, the youths in the room could detect a vortex forming in the middle of the room. They were all prompted toward it by the grand elder and started vanishing into the pocket dimension one after another. After everyone was in, the old man gave out a sigh and returned upstairs. He had other things to tend to, there were many things to prepare like what he would do to protect the city while his grandson was outside. Even if he returned victoriously, some enemies might try to pull a fast one while the strongest cultivator from the city is away.

"It's always the old farts like me that are left in the end..."

The grand elder wouldn't be taking part in the training, he was just there to let people in and out. The twenty formation establishments officers were already in the pocket dimension getting ready to introduce themselves to their squad of ten. They would be responsible for their formation training along with some helpers to do the dirty work. There was only one problem with the teams, Zhang Jie demanded to have her kids in the same squad. She whined her motion to her grandpa, he had the freedom in choosing as their Patriarch left it to him.

There was a conflict of interest if you had a close family member in places like the military. Others might see their comrades in arms getting preferential treatment which might lower the morale or cause fights. It was slightly different here though, as this was a clan where everyone was kind of related. There were cousins and siblings everywhere though most of the ties run quite thin. After some deliberation, Zhang Jin agreed.

A crowd soon appeared, the cultivators looked around in astonishment none of them had ever been to a pocket dimension before. Their eyes scanned the surroundings, there wasn't that much in here besides the big building but they could also see other training areas getting set up. They could see some training dummies for close combat and long combat practice. Some spots were devoid of grass and they had symbols written down on the ground, these were to aid people in their formation training, helping them remember the spots they were supposed to stand in.

There were some impromptu tents set up, with things like 'Armory' or 'Cafeteria' written on it. There wasn't much time to construct a proper building and the large 'dorm' in the middle only had space for the living quarters and nothing besides that. The twenty officers greeted their soldiers as they entered, the juniors quickly straightening up as they saw their elders.

"Listen up everyone, when you hear your name you will go to your assigned team. You will be given further instructions by your team's lieutenant."

The youths looked at each other, one of them raised a hand after the elder was done talking. The elder in question gave a nod, letting the junior speak out.

"Um, excuse me elder Zhi... what's a lieutenant?"

The people here didn't really have any military ranks, what did you need an army for if one guy could just bulldoze through a city. The clans mostly took the form of the soldiers and they had their inner family ties and rankings, the sects had all the outer and inner disciple designations. There was no organized military structure around here, most cities were self-sufficient city-states with the clans acting as the lords or kings.

"Lieutenants are leaders of a platoon."

Zhang Zhi replied while his eyebrow twitched a bit, but he just saw more confusion in the youth's eyes.

"A platoon is a team of cultivators acting as a unit..."

He tried to recall what the Patriarch said while he was giving them the orders, he just gave them some unique names and divided them into smaller teams. Also for some reason he wanted to be called 'General Dong' instead of the Patriarch, he couldn't really argue with the man though. They also received new robes, these were some state of the art garments as he could feel the flow of spiritual energy, these were clearly earth grade treasures.

"Your lieutenant will explain everything to you in detail later, just follow the instructions. I'll begin calling out names for my platoon first then."

People started getting called out, if Matt was here he would probably get dizzy from all the similar-sounding names. Soon enough Zhang Jie stepped out and started gathering her own group. Zhang Xue and Liu were a part of it, besides that there were twin 18-year old girls named Zhang Mii and Zhang Yuu. There was a chubby fellow by the name Zhang Hong, a tall burly looking male with a beard that looked older than he actually was, called Zhang Peng.

Besides those six there were four more youths, the first one Zhang Tai he was a bit special as he was the person that scored the highest in the tournament. He looked like your average young master with a resting bitch face, he was already scoffing at his team members. The second one was Zhang Teng, his face was a bit elongated making him look like a snake, he was also grinning constantly. The third person was called Zhang Ai, she had a more mature vibe than the other girls in the group with a body to match. The last person was a small looking youth by the name Zhang Bao he looked very meek, with his neck long hair covering up his eyes.

This would be the 9th Platoon, they ranged from the youngest Zhang Xue to the oldest Zhang Peng that was already twenty. Zhang Jie looked at the group of kids, she was ordered to help them train with the help of some other clan members. She was still apprehensive about her kids coming along, but at least she would be there with them if something happened.

"Well then young ones, first its time to gather your equipment."

Zhang Jie followed the instructions and went with the kids to the armory tent. In there they could get their 'battle robes' and weapons, as they arrived they were already the 9th team there. They could see people leaving the tent carrying some things, there weren't enough spatial rings for everyone so they had to carry their gear manually.

"Oh, that's some good stuff..."

Zhang Teng mentioned while grinning as he checked out some of the things the other juniors were carrying out, no one was actually wearing the robes just yet. After going inside they started receiving their gear, everyone got excited as they felt the mortal grade energy radiation coming off the robes. Though they were a bit skeptical about the designs, they looked at the ominous-looking masks, not sure if they were safe to use.

"You'll find these magical robes to be quite high quality, they are very resistant and don't get in the way at all."

The quartermaster chimed in, while everyone was looking at the presented items. The kids could also pick out a perfect grade common weapon for themselves if they needed one, but most of them already had theirs. On from the twins chuckled while putting on the mask, quite curious about the features it had.

"Hey, hey Mii? how do I look!"

The helmet looked like a front mask at first, but when you placed it closer to your face it would envelop the entire head from all sides. The girl shrieked out a bit as the helmet shut itself around her head, but noticed that it didn't impend her vision at all. The eyes shined a bit with an azure light as she looked around. She could already tell that it enhanced her optical senses in various ways.

"Yuu... you look funny..."

Zhang Mii snickered to herself while her twin looked around while wearing the new item. She also wanted to try it out, but before she could do so she heard a loud snort.

"Knock it off you two, just take the magical items and be quiet."

It was Zhang Tai, annoyed by how the way these clan members of his were acting, this wasn't a place for kids to be playing. He just grabbed the robe and helmet and left the tent, bumping into Zhang Bao on his way out and making him fall onto his butt.

"Watch were you are going, hmph!"

He held his nose up high and headed to the large building in the middle of the closed of space, they were told to do that after they were done with picking up the gear. Zhang Liu helped the shorter clan member up to his feet, a bit dejected how that other senior brother was acting.

"Don't mind him, Senior brother Tai is like that... but you can count on his skills."

Zhang Liu didn't want to admit it, but he was weaker than that senior brother of his. Even with his new master's skills he still needed to catch up. But with the Patriarch upgrading everyone's skills as well, he might have a harder time doing that now. The others stopped playing around after that, everyone grabbed their items while Zhang Jie hurried them on as well. She needed to show them their rooms and then brief them in on the training schedule.

The twins were staying in one room, while Xue and Ai were together in another one. The muscular youth ended up with the stuck up Zhang Tai, Liu shared his room with the chubby brother. That left Teng and Bao in the last room, the smaller youth was a bit scared of the snake-like youth that kept staring at him with a giant grin on his face all the time. Training would be starting soon, so everyone was ordered to change into their new robes and meet outside. They would mostly be training in the new body refining art and the formations, besides their regular cultivation techniques. The boot camp was finally on its way!

Chapter 79

The pocket dimension had its own light source in the distance, no one knew if it was real or an illusion because if you left the small rock formation you would quickly run out of air. Every platoon was gathered outside the dorm building, each officer was standing in front of their squad while another member of the Zhang Clan was in the middle.

"By the order of the Patriarch, I will be your 'Drill Sergeant'. From now on you will speak only when spoken to, and the first and last words out of your filthy sewers will be 'Sir.' Do you maggots understand that? If you do, reply with "Sir, yes Sir!"

The Drill Sergeant was a middle-aged man, with a military-like haircut and scars all over his face. The man was trying to keep a straight face as this was ordered by the Patriarch himself. He had written down some mean sounding quotes to him and told him to use them while training the juniors. The foundation establishment elders wouldn't be part of the training drills, so they were free to train on their own accord for now. The formation training would be practiced later, first came the physical drills and some sparring among the youths.

"...Sir yes, Sir!"

The kids shouted out, some of them feeling a bit dejected at the treatment.

"If you juniors leave this island, if you survive the training, you will be a weapon. You will be a minister of death, praying for war. But until that day, you are nothing but unorganized pieces of amphibian excrement."

Question marks could be seen above the youth's heads when the 'amphibian' was mentioned, from the context they somehow knew that it wasn't anything good. While the foundation establishment elder was belittling the new soldiers, he was exuding an aura that was making the Qi condensation juniors buckle under the strain. Everyone in the surroundings was starting to feel pressured, this clearly wasn't going to be easy. After some shouting they finally left for a run, the robes they were carrying had a function to decrease and increase the weight just for this. The juniors quickly found themselves sweating profusely under the increased weight of their enchanted clothing.

The first one to fall behind was Zhang Hong, due to his increased bodyweight he wasn't really fit for cardio all that much and collapsed. The drill sergeant instantly was on him, shouting and even kicking his rear end to get a move on, some of his fellow platoon members helped him up and they all started moving once more. The Sergeant looked at the fatty wobble away, now remembering a certain instruction that he got. The clan leader had told him, that if there was someone that started falling behind the others, he should let up on him just a bit, even more, if he was overweight. He wasn't sure why, but he would follow orders to not be so hard on Zhang Hong.

The drill Sergeant pulled out a jade slip, on it he had all the lines that the Patriarch gave him. He looked at it, his eyebrows twitching slightly while he sighed inwardly. Orders were orders and he would follow them to a t, he moistened up his lips and started talking while the youths were jogging around the compound. The Patriarch kind of told him to try to sing this part, he wasn't sure about that though. He also didn't know what the 'Totally original Patriarch lyrics, plz don't steal :)' at the end meant.

"Let's get down to business, to defeat our foes. Did they send me servants, when I asked for cultivators?"

"You're the saddest bunch I ever met, but you can bet before we're through. Junior, I'll make a cultivator out of you!"

The training switched to hand to hand combat, the platoons competed against each other as they were learning some basic teamwork. Most of the time they were bumping into each other though, the 9th platoon wasn't doing all that well as Zhang Peng liked to solo everyone, letting his muscles do the talking. Zhang Ai liked to hang in the back while spamming ranged attacks, just using her teammates as meat shields. This resulted in her hitting Peng in the back of the head with a water serpent technique while he broke of defensive formation to attack an enemy. Some semblance of teamwork could be seen between the two pairs of siblings, the twins along with Xue and Liu were somehow not getting into each other's way.

"Tranquil as a forest but on fire within. Once you find your center, you are sure to win. You're a spineless, pale, pathetic lot
And you haven't got a clue. Somehow I'll make a cultivator out of you."

A week had passed now, the members were still not doing that well as they were slowly learning the ropes with the formation arts. You could see the formation's blue lights all over the place as everyone tried to make the shield appear. Some of the platoons were succeeding while some were nowhere near finished, their shields breaking and the people suffering cultivation backlash from the rampant spiritual energies in the area.

"I'm never gonna catch my breath, say goodbye to those who knew me..."

Zhang Hong said while collapsing, his robe all sweaty from the constant running and physical training that he was being forced to do by the drill sergeant.

"Boy, was I a fool for not preparing more, Now I really wish that I didn't come here."

Said Zhang Teng as he suffered a hit to the face from a clan member during a mock battle against the 7th platoon, his team members just looking at him as he ate dirt.

"Be a Zhang! We must be swift as the coursing river. Be a Zhang! With all the force of a great typhoon
Be a Zhang! With all the strength of a raging fire, Mysterious as the dark side of the moon!"

Which of the moons did the drill Sergeant even mean, thought the youths while their physiques were getting better and better. Their understanding of the two formations was increasing as they didn't blunder so much anymore. There were even close to moving on to the next step of every clan member forming a giant formation together.

"Time is racing toward us till the Patriarch arrives, Heed my every order and you might survive Even if you're unsuited for the rage of war, Don't pack up and be through because I'll make a cultivator out of you!"

Three weeks in the juniors were showing promise, they were all working together with each other. You could see a large muscular man together with a wide chubby youth standing side by side while shielding their teammate from attacks while she charged up a finishing move. The team mentality was slowly clicking together as even the unlikable Zhang Tai was seen working together with a smaller junior, pummeling away at some other platoon people. Everyone was slowly singing the catchy tune that the drill instructor repeated each day, it started getting integrated into their minds.

"Be a Zhang! We must be swift as the coursing river. Be a Zhang! With all the force of a great typhoon
Be a Zhang! With all the strength of a raging fire, Mysterious as the dark side of the moon!"

After the 'training montage' was over, they all returned to the dorms to talk. They had all increased their mastery in their techniques, but they still needed to do more. There was still about a month left before the time was up, they could still level up their masteries and get better. Due to spending so much time with people with the same mindset everyone started slowly thinking as a unit, the petty squabbles between the purebloods and the side families were shoved to the side while everyone concentrated on the future of the Zhang family.

At this time Zhang Dong was not in the vicinity of the Zhang Clan, he was on a tall mountain experiencing an increase in power. The lightning energies in him were a lot more chaotic this time which caused a huge explosion. Any creature in the vicinity would get electrocuted as the cultivator in white hovered in the air slightly. Yes, he was hovering this was an early sign of a cultivator getting close to the nascent soul level as experts of that caliber didn't require flying swords anymore.

He couldn't fly just yet though, as you required a lot more juice to do that without a flying sword to hold you up. Matt was only at the late stage now, but he could give anyone at the pinnacle of the core formation a run for their money due to his immortal grade cultivation method. He was frowning though, looking at his opened palm on which the blue lightning energy was forming.

"Damn, it took me a whole damn month to finally get through to the late stage..."

He noticed a serious decline in his advancement speed, it still was swifter than any other cultivators, but it would take him at least a year to get to the great circle at this rate.

"Guess cultivating more won't make that much of a difference, but every bit counts... maybe I should try getting some new skills, the guys should be back with the spirit stones by now."

He had a minor amount of points left, not enough to do anything with them. He wanted to get enough to upgrade to that golden lightning art, but he needed a million for that, and he didn't think he would be able to gather that many spirit stones from the sales. The clan blew through all of the resources that they had stashed behind, so there wouldn't be much more. What was left was hunting beasts, gathering points from his students, or just cultivating more as even one percent more in the cultivation art made him slightly stronger.

He looked through the wanted lists, but since his last hunt, most of the criminals were laying low. People were afraid of the strange cultivator that was hunting core formation criminals, so most of the evil cultivators decided to hide and wait it out. All of them had long life spans, so waiting a couple of years wasn't that hard. Matt, on the other hand, didn't have much time left, so spending time on a needle in a haystack was out of the question.

*Heh, wonder if that guy actually followed my instructions..."

He got a bit curious as he returned back to the Zhang clan, a month had passed and he saw his disciples progressing in their skills a bit. There wasn't a big change though as the focus was teamwork and formations instead of cultivation arts. When he arrived, no one noticed him as he was hiding his aura. He peeked at the youths that were training and could hear them singing the tune that he butchered a bit.

*Haha, they are really doing it.*

Matt was holding his hand to his mouth, trying not to burst out into laughter. Soon enough he was spotted by some people, the small floating land didn't really have many places where a white-haired buff dude could hide. He came out of hiding, which caused everyone to take notice and stop with the training. Everyone gave him a proper bow, they were all wearing the gear that he made which made them look like a small army of Chūnibyōs.

*Well... I got myself an army of edgy teenagers, who can stop me now?*

He nodded at the people, telling them if they could show him the fruits of their labor. They demonstrated the formation techniques, some of the youths were quite nervous while looking at their patriarch which caused some fumbles here and there but somehow they pulled through. The giant two hundred people formation needed some work though, he told them to form the water serpent one so that he could test the formation's power.

Matt watched as the crowd worked together like an almost well-oiled machine, they quickly got into their designated spots and started forming the large water serpent. It was quite huge, larger than his avatar form with the many cultivators floating around in its spirit energy body. They were all in the lotus position, with the strongest member that was Zhang Zhi in the snakes head acting as the core. He was controlling the giant thing, the snake gave out a roar that blew the Patriarch's hair a bit.

"Well then, give me all you've got."

Matt produced his lightning shield, setting it up in front of the snake. He was quite used to the technique now so he was even able to layer the barriers together. He made it so that the first one was the weakest starting off at the foundation establishment lower level, all up to the late stage of the core formation. He wanted to see how far the attack would breach in, hoping that it would at least get through the early core formation level.

The snake opened its mouth, he could see the sharp watery fangs protruding. A large water ball was forming in that maw, he could see the spiritual energy getting sucked in from the surroundings like a whirlpool, then a bright blue beam of light was fired off towards the shields. The cultivators inside the battle formation grimaced from the skill usage, the attack draining them of their spiritual energy.

The beam attack hit the shield, going through the first three barriers without a problem stopping briefly on the fourth one before blasting through it as well. When it hit the fifth one it stopped though, this one was the early stage of core formation. The beam continued as the snake kept at with the attack, the people within giving their best to not disappoint the Patriarch. Due to this, you could see some of the youths passing out and flopping out of the formation due to spiritual energy depletion.

After seeing that, Zhang Dong wanted to stop the test but he noticed the determination in their eyes. The attack continued and the shield finally started to show cracks and with a resounding boom, it shattered to pieces. The attack hit the next barrier, but before it could do any more damage the formation started breaking and it collapsed due to too many cultivators tiring themselves out.

"Okay that's enough, you did well. It can be used as a trump card, you just need to keep the formation more stable."

Zhang Dong nodded while trying to give his clan people a pep talk. The youths seamed invigorated as he saw some of them smiling while panting, probably proud of their monthly achievement.

"But don't get cocky, there is still much more work to be done."

He ended it on a serious note, time was of the essence and there wasn't much more left as the last month started ticking down.

A note from Kuropon

Had fun writing this silly chapter, so early release probably next one will take longer to release, enjoy xD

It's is highly advised to listen to this song while reading.

Chapter 80

The people looked as the Patriarch turned around and vanished into thin air after they showed off their skills. He didn't test them out on the defensive formation, but not like they had enough spiritual energy left for that. The Zhang Clan members were in high spirits though, they managed to break through the leader's strong barrier quite a bit. The moment the man came in they could feel the high energy fluctuations from him. The younger members couldn't tell much, but people like Zhang Zhi felt the increase in Zhang Dong's power after he formed the shield that could block an attack of a late stage core formation expert.

*He wasn't showing the full extent of his power.*

The man thought to himself while sitting down into a lotus position to gather his energies. He looked at the youths around him, he didn't think that they would be able to train them up so well. The strange military methods seemed to be working, the catchy workout song was also doing its thing. The upgraded techniques were a lot easier to master and the youths, as well as the elders, were progressing at breakneck speeds. The spiritual energy in this artifact was quite pure so that helped with the training as well.

"Everyone you have an hour to rest, we will resume further training afterward, you did well."

The younger members were sweating a lot more than the foundation establishment elders that looked slightly out of breath. Though they were invigorated after this test run, they just saw their new Patriarch he was quite the celebrity around the clan.

"Did you hear that. The Patriarch said that we did well!"

One of the tired youths said while he flopped onto his back and panted.

"Yes yes, I think he also smiled in my direction, such a manly smile!"

One of the females said while other members looked at her with narrowed eyes. Zhang Zhi's lower lip quivered as he got ignored by the younger generation that started talking about the Patriarch and didn't even reply to his comment. He let this transgression slide this time, as he also was a bit excited that the man that improved his arts gave them a passing grade.

*He was also right about my spear training*

After he received the katana, he was in a bind as he had to train in the sword art manual that he got. He was apprehensive at first, thinking that if he didn't see any progress within a weak he would just return the sword and skill manual to the leader. But to his surprise, after he started training he noticed that the sword was like an extension of his body. He was already a seasoned cultivator and warrior, he knew how long it normally took to learn a new fighting style. The speed at which he was immersing himself in the sword Dao was astonishing. Day by day he found himself improving, getting past the beginner stage and advancing further rather easily.

*The sword does indeed fit me more than the spear, wish I knew this sooner. But how did the Patriarch know about this, he just examined me briefly with his spiritual sense... truly wonderous.*

The figure of Zhang Dong was getting bigger and bigger in the eyes of his clan members, making them think that the man was some kind of one in a billion genius. The cultivators in this world already tended to show sect-like behaviors, having the leader's opinion outweigh their own or their families. Matt was slowly getting put up on a pedestal in the mind of these people, he did make them stronger and did it for free, this was mostly enough for cultivators to pledge their allegiance to the person responsible.

While people were overestimating Matt, he walked out of the secret chambers wanting to check out if there were any spirit stones he could gobble up. His system point tank was on empty after having upgraded so many techniques and frankly, they weren't all that great anyway. The most he spent was on his grandpa's cultivation technique getting that thing to not halt the cultivation process was quite costly. Upgrading unfinished or incomplete techniques cost a lot more than just upgrading finished ones. Guess it was easier to renovate an old building than to rebuild a half-finished one.

He was greeted by his accountant Zhang Kuo, well at least that's what Matt started thinking the man was as he was mostly responsible for the numbers. After selling off all the weapons he had gained some spirit stones, but it wasn't nearly enough. He spent all the crafting resources on the robes and weapons for his clan members. The rest were used on weapons that he could absorb, finally managing to get his body into the late-stage along with his regular cultivation level.

*This isn't enough to evolve my lightning cultivation into that golden one... Should I try hunting for some core formation beasts...*

There was less than a month remaining, the dark palm sect had given them instructions to gather their forces in a certain place at a certain time. The Zhang Clan had one flying ship left, it looked like a large galeon with a dragonhead at the front. It was different from regular ships, it didn't have sails or anything as everything around this world worked on spiritual energy. It was the last one the whole clan had, as the ones that it previously used in the first expedition never came back, probably pawned off by the dark palm sect or some other clans. He would probably look into that later and get their stuff back.

*The trip there will take about a week, so that leaves less than three weeks to tie up loose ends around here...*

The option of running away was still open for Matt, but for some reason, he didn't feel like it. He was slowly bonding with these strange people and their quirky ways, finding it funny as they overreacted when they saw him do 'unfathomable' things. They were clearly a violent bunch, but most of them were good people. There was also the thing that he promised to himself, not wanting to be a coward anymore.

"Well, hold the fort while I'm out Kuo. I'll be heading to the mountains but I'll be close by. You know how to reach me if something happens."

Matt headed out to cultivate at the mountain peaks and maybe hunt some beasts for points, he might get lucky in his travels. While he was charging into the distance on his flying sword, the light in the hidden pocket dimension was dimming. The people there noticed that the place had a night and day cycle, the nights took about eight to nine hours.

The dorm was quiet as most juniors were resting, but there were four youths sneaking to a certain place. The dorm was only used for living, there was nothing besides the rooms that could be used for sleeping, no plumbing or lights to speak of. But the water wasn't a problem around here, so the people just dug out a couple of holes and transported some spring water from the outside. The water had healing properties and could also help with stamina recovery. There was a separate place for the boys and girls, blocked away by a large bamboo wall. The youths in question were clearly heading for that wall.

"E-elder brother Teng, are you sure about this... if we get caught w-we will be severely punished."

Zhang Bao asked while he looked at the grinning elder brother that was smiling and licking his lips. There were two large males behind him as well, the buff Zhang Peng and the round Zhang Hong that had replaced some of that fat with muscle now, but he still looked round as a ball. The smallest from the bunch was blushing, still wondering how he got himself into this. He was just outside to pee when he saw the trio sneaking out of the dorm, he went to check on them but they just pulled him along to go peek at the girls.

"No need to fear, my part of the family is renowned for their hiding skills and the Patriarch even improved on our skill so if you just follow my instructions, the lovely thighs of junior Sister Xue and the lovely front peaks of Sister Ai will be all for us to behold!"

The youth's started doing obscene motions with his fingers almost drooling while talking about the peaks in question. The other two members that got roped in had dopey expressions as well. The burly guy looked like a perverted older man, the chubby fellow seamed to be salivating as if he saw a jelly-filled doughnut in front of himself to devour.

"Little bro hehe, you remember how the elders told us to work together, we must get through this as a team!"

"Yes Bao, remember what the drill sergeant said, it's all for the team, it's a team-building exercise!"

The three looked like hungry wolves sneaking through the night, due to Teng's sneaking technique their footsteps were muffled as he could produce a mist around the whole group making them hard to spot within the dark night. The idiot quartet approached the bamboo wall, they could hear the girls chatting on the inside. The group clearly went out the moment they saw their female team members leave to take a bath, as the four girls were talking inside.

"Oh, little Xue your hair sure is shiny, what do you use to keep your hair so smooth and soft?"

"Not much, think it might be the cultivation art that Master taught me, my hair turned white too."

"Not fair, I also want to be the Patriarch's disciple, do you think he will take me in as well?"

"He looks so dashing, not like the boys from our group."

The males heard their names getting mentioned as the girls chatted, though it wasn't anything good. Teng was thought to be a big pervert, due to his snake-like appearance that gave the girls the chills. Peng was said to look like an old uncle and was too buff for the girls taste, Hong... well Hong was just a thick boy, the girls were scared of him crushing them. There wasn't much said about Bao, Liu and Tai got some praise from the girls though they didn't like the older ones stuck up attitude. The girls laughed as they joked that elder brother Tai looked like he was constantly constipated.

The pervy youths were listening but at the same time working on the next stage of their masterplan. The next stage would be poking a hole in the wall so that they could peek on the girls, what could go wrong? It was just bamboo, they were high-level cultivators they should be able to poke a hole in it with their fingers by now. But while the three hornballs were pushing their cheeks against the wall, as they tried to listen in the bamboo started buckling under their combined weight.

The wall started to shake as the young male's hormones got out of control. The females on the other side noticed the shaking wall, it was giving out under the weight. Hong had gotten too excited and tripped, slamming into Peng on the way making the two large males fall face-first on the bamboo, which gave out in seconds. The girls saw three males on the collapsed wall one was missing though as Teng was nowhere to be seen, he had dissolved into mist the second the wall started falling down and made his escape. Using the commotion to get out before the impending thrashing.

*Kekeke, oh well guess I'll try another time alone~"

"Kyaaaaa... damn perverts!"

A girl screamed loudly alerting all the other women in the spring, everyone started covering up while the three guys sweated profusely. They looked back to their 'leader' but he had vanished into thin air, long gone.

"Team building my ass!"

The three youths shouted in unison while trying to run, but there were too many angry women around them cutting off their escape route. Teng sneaked away while the other three youths were pummeled by the angry girls on the other side. The four females from their platoon weren't the only ones in there, so there were many more girls eager to stomp them good. The three youths' faces looked like they were stung by bees and they had an allergic reaction after the beating was done. Their lips were swollen and many bruises could be seen on their bodies, the three were pulled away by an elder to get treated.

The next day, the three were punished by Zhang Jie that was fuming with anger due to her daughter being in the bath while the three were peeping. Though after some scolding she let them go, they were beaten badly so there wasn't really a reason to punish them more. She didn't see the part where the three youths started chasing their snaky looking friend with drawn weapons, the drill sergeant didn't know people could run so fast. He just saw a blurry snake-like youth sprinting away, with fear in his eyes.

"Get back here, I won't be satisfied until I punch your face at least ten times!"

Zhang Peng shouted while wielding his knuckle looking weapon, that covered both his forearms.

"Hey, it's not my fault that you lard asses can't keep quiet! Lieutenant Jie save me!"

While this was happening the girls were looking at the four with shifty eyes, Zhang Liu was just laughing to the side while the last male member from the platoon didn't know what those four fools were doing, so he just jogged on.

Chapter 82

A note from Kuropon

Come join the discord, we have uncomfortable silence https://discord.gg/GDTwD4P

This was truly an uncomfortable feeling, Matt felt like puking as the suppressive force crushed into him. His clan members were worse off than him as they started collapsing onto the ground, not being able to hold on. The oppressive force vanished soon after and a floating person appeared. He was floating right in front of them, his hands behind his back while his back was straight up.

"Our sincere apologies Grand Elder Guo, we were attacked by some beasts on our way here."

The older woman said while cupping her fists and bowing before the dark palm sect elder. The woman next to her just turned her head to the side, seemingly annoyed by the whole thing which made the older one sweat bullets not wanting to offend a nascent soul expert. Elder Guo just floated in the air, he was a baldy with a long goatee and a really wrinkled up face.

"I see that your Matriarch hasn't learned her lesson yet, you're lucky that time is of the essence."

The woman was quite lovely looking and had a high cultivation level while being fairly young just having turned thirty-nine, though she looked like she was in her early twenties. A woman like this would have many suitors from strong clans going after her, even though her complexion was a less desired one than the pale one. She mostly found the old masters disgusting and the younger ones kept giving her perverted looks, so she always turned them down.

One day she caught the eye of a young dark palm sect master, this wasn't any regular member but the son of the sects Patriarch. She, of course, didn't want to have anything to do with him, finding his character not up to par with her standards. Her clan members couldn't force her to marry the man even if they wanted to as she was their Matriarch. The sect started blackmailing the whole clan after a while, culminating in the matriarchal clan being recruited for this expedition that had a very low chance of succeeding. This was seen as a way of getting rid of the person that didn't give them face, without having to get their own hands dirty in the process.

Matt didn't know any of this though, he was just staring at the people that clearly had some bad history. Soon the nascent soul elder went deeper into the mountain, ordering the clans to disembark. He had scanned the nascent soul cultivator, finding out that he was only in the early stage. The area was littered with tents and hastily constructed buildings, the dark palm Sect cultivators were all over the place. There were many core formation cultivators around, even more, foundation establishment ones making Matt wonder why they even had the clans do their dirty work for them if they had so many resources.

He was a bit surprised after seeing the gyaru ship, even the old elder lady looked peculiar with a lot of makeup and glitter on. Due to him staring so much, the leader of that ship finally noticed him. He kind of froze at the moment their eyes met, the woman took a look at him and then moved her index finger right below her right eye. She then stuck her tongue out at him, while closing her left eye and pulling down her the lower eyelid under her right eye. Matt didn't know how to react so he just remained in place, the woman moved away after a while after having stuck her tongue out at him.

*Well... that was a bit strange...*

After the strange reaction the woman gave him, Zhang Dong waved his hand forward, giving the signal to disembark. They all jumped down from the airship, only a couple of Zhang Clan members would remain on it, waiting for their people to return later. Their clan did turn a lot of heads though, the peculiar-looking robes that they were using were quite unusual in the eyes of the other cultivators. The youths inside the robes puffed out their chests and took long strides forward as they followed their Patriarch, fear wasn't something that they felt now. They just wanted to bring honor to their families and return safely.

It didn't take that long to arrive in front of the humongous tower, they all looked up but couldn't see the end, clouds were just blocking off the view. There was a large gate in front with some cryptic writings above it, it was mostly faded away and unreadable. From what Matt could decipher it had something written about chains and unity, but couldn't really decipher it further.

Inside the 'tower' there were more people, there was a wide corridor and on the walls, you could see many murals depicting some fighting between beasts and people. Torches lined the passage, only the footsteps of people could be heard as everyone walked forward without saying much. Not like they didn't want to talk, but they were getting escorted by the core formation sect members with the nascent soul grand elder in the front, so they didn't really want to say anything that could offend the man.

After a while they came up to another large door, this one had more ancient writing on it. To the side were some stairs, they lead to the 'testing' area that would teleport them somewhere. Matt looked around the place, it looked really old but the large door did indeed give of immortal grade fluctuations. It looked more like a giant castle gate than a door, this was probably the one that had the immortal grade treasures behind it.

"Listen up, soon we will arrive. You all will be handsomely rewarded for your participation, as agreed you can keep anything up to the heaven grade from the secret ground. If you find anything in the immortal grade you are to relinquish it, you will get payed in spirit stones instead."

The people in the room rolled their eyes at the mention of the immortal grade items. They knew that if they tried to take something like that out of here, they would get eradicated by this overbearing sect. The number of spirit stones that they would offer would probably also be a scam. But not like they could do much about it, might made right in this world. At most they could hope for some immortal grade pills that they could swallow before leaving.

You could cut the tension in the air with a knife, the dark palm sect continued with their self-righteous mumbo jumbo. Some clans were here on their own volition, but there were also clans like the Zhang and Feng that were forced to participate. Matt sure hoped that the clans with various agendas wouldn't start fighting against each other in there. He was thinking about a couple of possible outcomes after the initial teleportation but wasn't sure which one it would be. He sure hoped that it wouldn't be one of those battle royale settings.

*Well, I did all I could and this system is even denying me more points now...*

He looked at his Chūnibyō corps, he was the only one wearing a white robe which made him stick out like a sore thumb amongst them. He wanted to give them a pep talk, but couldn't really interrupt the sect elders monologue. Soon they were led up to the platform room, there were ten of them. The platforms were circular in shape and had many runic patterns scraped into them, making it look like something magical.

"Remember your training everyone, don't forget that we are all with you."

Matt said after they finally had some time to talk, the other clan members exchanged some small talk. You could see people patting each other on the shoulders, some girls holding their hands while preparing for the unknown. They all could very well die in there, get teleported to different places and never see each other again. Matt walked over to his two disciples, trying to get some weight off their shoulders.

"Listen to your superiors when we are inside, don't worry I'll be with you as well."

The two nodded, they were wearing the masks already so he couldn't really see their facial expressions but thanks to his tranquil mind skill, he was sure that they were keeping their cool. These siblings were quite tough even though they were so young, he felt that if they made it through this in one piece they would probably soar to new heights. Matt was trying to play it cool, but he also felt butterflies in his belly. This was it, everyone was ready and the dark palm sect elder was slowly walking up to activate the teleportation mechanism.

"Remember, this is a test created by the immortal Senior that design this secret ground. Any forms of contact with the outside will be blocked so you will be on your own once inside. You will get rewarded accordingly when you return."

*Guess this is it, I should be able to take down anything up to the great circle level, there shouldn't be anything above that level in there, right?*

He thought that the enemies inside shouldn't be above a certain level due to only allowing people of the core formation to go inside. It would be quite unfair if they made ten core formation cultivators fight a nascent soul one inside, they would just get squashed like bugs. He looked at the dark palm sect member walk to the center, there was a strange-looking console there. The man placed his hand on it and then closed his eyes.

The console started glowing, slowly illuminating the room with it as rune-like patterns started appearing on the platforms everyone was standing in. The floor slowly lit up, going from one platform to another as the contraption got activated. The people started hearing a buzzing sound each time a platform got fully lit up, the ground looked like some kind of magical circle. After each podium got activated Matt felt a strange sensation wash over his body, more light covered all of the people around him and the scenery around started getting blurry. Finally, everything went dark as the people vanished from the spots they were standing in, the sect members just looked at the vacant platforms and snorted.

"Are the new communication treasures responding?"

A couple of people walked out from the shadows and approached the console the grand elder was standing in. Truth be told the sect didn't expect much from these backwater clan members, the plan was to let them go inside the testing grounds just so that they could test out some measuring equipment they had some of the clan members carry inside. They wanted to get some information about what was happening inside before sending their own people in to actually complete the whole task.

The sect members brought out some communication jade slips, trying to connect to the ones that were inside the secret ground. Then they brought out some other magical items, their brows wiggling a bit as they shook their head to the elder.

"No response for now grand elder, we will need to wait and see if a signal comes through later."

"I see..."

Elder Guo rubbed his chin, not really expecting anything from this test run. They were poking inside an old immortal's secret ground, it was reasonable to assume that if they wanted to communicate they would probably need items in the immortal grade. They used some high-grade items this time around, but it seemed that it wasn't working either. Now they had to think if it would be wise to send their own people without knowing what was inside.

"Very well, keep sending the signals maybe one will go through."

He didn't think that the idiots that were stuck inside would amount to anything. They were either ones guided by greed or weaklings that couldn't defend themselves like the Zhang clan. This was survival of the fittest, the sect was trying to protect their own assets first. They didn't see a problem in sending some treasure hungry cultivators to their doom if it furthered their own agenda.

At this time Matt felt like he was riding a rollercoaster, the teleportation was a lot different than what he expected. It wasn't instantaneous and he felt like he was getting tossed around like a ragdoll. His feet suddenly landed on the ground, he had to muster up all his strength just not to fall down to his knees, cold sweat covering his back.

"Where did we end up?"

He looked around, the area he was in was a forest, not something that he was expecting. There was one problem though, there was no 'we' here. He looked left and right, he even jumped up high to see if he could spot someone from his clan or from another one. There was no one here though, he spread his spiritual sense outwards trying to scan for life forms but could feel it getting blocked by something he couldn't really see past a kilometer from where he was standing.

"Damn, if everyone got split up the team training and the formation training was pointless..."

He facepalmed and then got ready to take his flying sword out to see if he could find someone. There was another problem though, the blasted spatial ring wasn't opening the same thing that blocked his spiritual sense was cutting off the access to his items. He had everything in there along with provisions, weapons, change of underwear. Luckily he was at least wearing his longsword at his waist and he had ordered everyone to take out their weapons before arriving, just wanting to be ready if a fight broke out. But other than that, he had nothing. All his healing pills, magical items that he saved up for this expedition were in his ring.

"I've made a huge mistake..."

Chapter 83

Matt took out his sword, ready for a fight not knowing if anything would jump out at him from the bushes. This reminded him of the forest area where he was transported to this world in the beginning. He wasn't in an open field now though, but deep in the forest which looked more like a rain forest than a regular one. The trees were quite high and thick, blocking the sunlight with their large leaves.

*Where am I anyway, why is there a sky in here, am I in that big tower?*

He tried scanning the surroundings with his senses again and picked up some life signs, but something was messing with his abilities so he couldn't really tell if it was a human being or not. He brought up his system map to check, but after pulling it up he just got an error message.

Error Error System map is being blocked by an outside source Error Error

*Wasn't this supposed to be some kind of super system, why isn't it working in here?*

He wanted to give his system window a smack but he would just be slapping the air. He also tried using his crafting abode but was constantly getting the nearby enemy prompt. It never went away though, making him think that the system might be considering this whole secret ground an enemy of some kind. The second option would be, that it was getting blocked like all the other system functions by the unknown force.

He decided to check the nearest life signal in the area, hoping that it was some of his clan members. He wouldn't take any chances though, he was ready for a fight. He hid his aura as much as possible and started sneaking with the sword in his hand already drawn and ready to slice and dice. There were some nice footwork manuals that his clan had, not everything required water elemental affinity so he could use some of the neutral ones.

His feet shuffled in a pattern as he moved closer, even if he stepped on some twigs they wouldn't snap alerting any enemies to his location. He came up to a big tree and could feel that the thing that he felt was on the other side, he could even sense some movement from it. He slowly wiggled next to the tree, trying to not get spotted by the potential enemy and peeked out to check.

*Wait... is that a... Goblin?*

Yes, it was something that Matt knew well, it was a creature that was a popular mob in a lot of games and novels alike. The goblin came up to his waist and was quite thin, it had a protruding belly and was wearing only a moist loincloth to cover its nether regions. It had no boots as you could see the calluses on its feet, the nails looked more like claws. It was carrying a short sword that was rusty and probably would break the moment it hit something hard. The other interesting thing besides that it was a goblin, was the system indication above its head.

Common Goblin (Formation Establishment Late stage) [ Summoned creature ]

*Why is a trash goblin mob in the formation establishment stage, even in the late one...and what is that summoned part?*

It was still weak, he could take it on without any problems but how would his clan members fair when the strongest person was at the great circle of foundation establishment. He really hoped that his clan members were sent to some other spot with weaker enemies if they run into a big group of these goblins they would get wiped out. While thinking about that he scanned the area, there were no other life signals close by so he decided to test things out.

He came out of his hiding spot, letting the Goblin spot him wondering what the creature would do. Would the thing gauge his superior battle aura and run away? Or would it blindly attack him instead? It did the latter part, it's beady eyes going red and it just charged at the larger man that was holding a sword. Matt didn't falter while just waiting, the monster charged jumping upwards and grasping its weapon with both hands as it brought it down with an overhead swing. The goblin was flying through the air, focused on its enemy but suddenly the man in front of it vanished. Appearing right next to it, the thing was mid-jump so it couldn't really stop itself now.

Matt slashed upward with his sword in a lazy fashion, cutting off the weaker goblins head. The creature's momentum sent it crashing into a tree, its head went flying upwards and landed a couple of meters away from the fallen lower-body.

Common Goblin Slain ( Formation Establishment Late stage ) Earned 5 Spirit Points.

"What? How was that only 5 points?"

He wasn't sure if the system was just lowering his point count due to his cultivation level, or if he was getting fewer points because of the monsters having that 'Summoned' part in the name.

"This thing acted like a game monster, the moment I got into its line of sight it got aggroed."

He rubbed his chin and then poked the dead body with his sword, wondering if this thing would have a beast core in it. But after a few moments the body started vanishing into light bubbles, nothing remained beside the used up loincloth and the sword that the creature was welding. Matt looked at the chipped weapon, getting surprised that it was a mortal graded item and even at the middle level. It looked like trash but was apparently deadly.

"This is bad if my clan members get jumped by these things..."

He started to worry, this goblin looked weak but was carrying good gear and could hold its own against a foundation establishment cultivator his Qi condensation juniors were in trouble if they were scattered around this palace as well. Time was of the essence so he decided to search for his team members, he wanted to take the rusted weapon that could be used as resources but couldn't put it into his storage ring.

He started running into more goblins, taking care of them with his sword skills. There was a problem though, the further he went into the forest and killed more of these trash mobs, the less he knew where he was. The area was covered with bushes and greenery so he had no way of telling where he was, his system map didn't work and his aura detection technique was getting blocked as well.

*Damn, I should have learned some regular tracking skills...am I running around in circles?*

He brought up his system window, but he couldn't use the cash shop either getting the same error message as before. This showed him how reliant on the system he really was. Before coming here he thought that if he ran into some trouble, he would just spend some points on some skills or items and that would be it. But now, he was left with only a sword in hand and couldn't even use his storage ring to get anything out.

*Guess next time I'll get a backpack...*

He thought while slicing the thick bushes with his sword using it like a machete to get through. The further he went in, the more goblins he came across, they were variations of the creatures. There were warrior variants, scouts and archers making him feel like he had changed genres and was now in an RPG world and not in a xianxia one. The goblins weren't the only things in here though, there were your typical slime monsters that spit acid at you, snake monsters that looked like vines. Luckily his detection skill still worked it just had limited range, so he could tell when something was trying to hide and pounce on him.

*Still, the monsters aren't giving me many points...*

He didn't get much more from even the warrior gobbos that were in the great circle stage, just between 6-10 points for them. He would need to kill hundreds of thousands of those things to get his upgrade at this rate, but he had other things to worry about. Where were his people? Was there something to eat around here? He had no water or food, though being a core formation expert he would last a couple of months without that by just meditating. Still, he would feel hungry and parched, he needed to at least find some water. This was a rain forest area so there shouldn't be a problem, it was even raining already.

He finally saw some light as he was walking out of the forest, he could see a narrow river and some rocks that lead into a hill. In that hill, he spotted a cave, something he could use as he didn't want to be stuck in this rain all day. It was also getting dark, so he headed inside. He was sure that there would be some kind of monster living in there, though he hoped that there wasn't goblin poop all over the floor.

Large Fang Bear ( Core formation early stage ) [ Summoned creature ]

He got startled a bit, this was a core formation creature but he could still handle it. The monster growled at him and tried charging as it used its huge body to attack him. The cultivator just gathered his spiritual energy into his longsword and held it in a somewhat fencing position, he then thrust it forward releasing a condensed shockwave from the tip that punctured a hole in the monster's head.

*These things sure like to charge at you with no plan eh? and only 500 points for that thing?*

The bear dropped dead instantly, the glowy lights forming from it as it vanished into the ether. Matt wondered if everything in this dungeon area was a summoned creature, maybe he would have to find himself some fruits or berries to sustain himself. Also, he needed water, though that problem was solved by the clear spring that was close to this cave that he was in. It was still raining and was getting cold, the inside of the cave didn't lead anywhere, the only things he found inside were bones from some animals which made him think that some of them could be eaten and hunted.

He had been trekking for two days now, there was a day and night cycle and some strange creatures came out at night. He was concerned about his people, but even after spending the entire previous day and night, he still couldn't find anyone. This place was huge and he couldn't use his flying sword so he had to move on foot, there was also another problem.

When he tried to use his range javelin skill, throwing it high into the air. It started flickering and dissipating after about 100 meters. He wanted to see if this palace had a ceiling or if perhaps someone would notice his attack from afar. But due to this, he noticed that ranged attacks would fizzle up prematurely. Cultivators that were dependant on long-range skills would probably be severely weakened. The spiritual energy seamed to weaken the moment it left the cultivator, he was lucky that he always could go back to his body refining skill which left him unscathed from most attacks.

*Guess I'll stay here for the night.*

He wasn't sure how long he was in here, but it had been at least a day. He spotted some bamboo and having the knowledge of survival videos on his side, he knew exactly what to do. He found himself a sturdy looking bamboo pole and sliced it up so that the segmented parts weren't damaged. He then poked a hole on one side, which would be used for drinking while the bottom was left untouched. He was surprised at how sturdy the bamboo was, guess it was some special spirit bamboo. He also used the bamboo narrow top part as a cork to the bottle so that the water wouldn't spill outside and ended the whole construction with wrapping vines around it so that he could even carry it over his shoulder.

He filled it up, but before drinking, he examined the water wondering if he'd catch some parasites if he drunk it. Luckily for him, it looked clean and this bamboo was quite special as well, as it could resist his lightning energy somehow and was partly heat resistant. He could heat it up like an electric tea kettle, which meant that he could even make some tea if he found some good leaves. For now, he just drunk the boiled water and meditated, he didn't want to stay here for longer than he needed as he still was lost. He couldn't find anyone and he was even meeting core formation monsters from this point on.

The night went by without much happening, so he filled up his water bottle and went further in. He started running into stronger and stronger monsters the more he traveled, there was quite an abundance of core formation monsters now. They weren't giving him many points though, but not like he could spend it on much at the moment with the cash shop closed. After three more days of travel, he felt something. There was a large gathering of life signals in a spot about a kilometer away from his position, from the type of the signal he reasoned that it were probably goblins but there was one that was a lot stronger than the others.

"Is it a boss? Maybe a goblin king?"

He couldn't really tell as he was still far away, so he slowed his pace and hid his aura sneaking up at the goblin encampment. He shuffled up getting closer and closer while almost falling to his doom as there was a large river below him while the goblins were on the other side, separated by a deep chasm. He could see their dwellings built into the side of the chasm, there were stairs leading up where he could see more of the green skins. They were gathering in a spot and they looked like there were preparing a feast with a large cauldron in the middle.

But then he noticed something, there was a different life signal coming from there, it felt like a human. He used his enhanced vision to zoom in on the area, spotting a person there. This person was getting carried by two larger looking goblins, though they looked more like a hobgoblin. The person had their hands and feet bound to a large log and the monsters were carrying them out like a hunted deer. He could see the person's status, so he knew that they were alive, so he would help them. This was the first human that he came across after almost a week of traveling alone, maybe they had some answers. Also, he wouldn't just let the monsters eat someone if he could stop it.

Chapter 84

The chasm was about five hundred meters wide, Matt reasoned that he should be able to jump this distance if he took a good running start. Before engaging the enemies he took his time to examine the situation, he could still see the levels and names of the monsters thanks to his system and analyzing skill.

*Okay, there are a lot of the small goblins everywhere... don't really have to worry about those...*

Besides a large number of regular goblins, he could see some hobgoblin warriors they ranged from the early to middle stages of core formation. There were also a couple of goblin shamans around also in that power range, probably those were the long-range caster types perhaps they could heal their monster allies as well. There was also a really fat looking hobgoblin with a stained apron by that large cauldron, looking like a green lunch lady. The strongest goblin from the bunch was a chieftain class and was in the late stage, he was sitting in a large throne-like chair not doing much besides looking at the human that was getting carried and about to get cooked.

*Don't see anyone in the great circle, so it should be okay... But I was wrong about them acting like game mobs. They are somewhat organized and even brought in a living human to eat. *

The goblin encampment was large, they had buildings and towers placed in front of the wide chasm. The area from the other side was walled off by a simple wooden log wall, sharpened spiked logs were shoved into the ground so that other monsters couldn't just charge into it. They had some shacks acting as buildings past that wall but by the way that gorge was looking, they had burrowed into the landscape as Matt saw openings and lights coming out of the side of that fissure. There were logs inserted into the rocky side, allowing the goblins to move along but it didn't look safe at all.

*Can't even use my range attacks to snipe them, guess this is going to be close and personal.*

He didn't really have much time to prepare a throughout plan, the person on the log was about to get boiled alive. Thanks to his system, he could actually see who it was, name included.

Feng Liena core formation late stage [ Poisoned ] [ Weak ] [ Bleeding ]

Matt didn't know when he started seeing status effects, but the woman in question looked like she was about to die. There was no more time to lose, he took a running start and started charging in the direction that the goblins were preparing their feast, hoping that he could vault this wide chasm. His feet produced thudding noises, breaking the ground and leaving cracked footprints in the hard soil.

The woman in question was close to passing out, just like Zhang Dong she had been split up from her clan members and found herself alone in this place. She was a pampered princess so she relied on others for things like shelter and food, so she didn't really have many survival skills. The only thing that she had on herself were her two fans that produced wind attacks when swung around. She found it difficult to use her techniques here as the wind blades weren't as effective in this strange place, still, the weak foundation establishment monsters didn't pose a problem so she moved along.

After two days of walking in high heels, she was getting annoyed, there were mosquitoes everywhere the monsters constantly attacked her so she couldn't even take a break. Her skills were getting hindered by some outside force, so the encounters with the more evolved monsters were exhausting her spiritual energy fast.

About an hour ago she had an unfortunate encounter with an evolved Vine-Snake. This creature as the name stated, liked to take the form of a vine just hiding and waiting for some prey to come. While Liena was sitting by a tree, trying to rest after defeating some monsters the snake pounced. Her sluggish reaction cost her dearly as two puncture wounds appeared on her thigh. She managed to cut the snakes head off afterward but the paralyzing venom was already working. She felt feverish, all of her detoxification pills were in her storage ring that she couldn't use.

The goblins came soon after, probably alerted by the high pitched screams after she got bitten. She tried to use her cultivation to halt the poisoning process to a minor degree of success. Liena got overwhelmed by the combine goblin attacks, cut wounds soon appeared all over her body. After she fell, the monsters took her away to their chieftain, who had ordered to gather up any non-monster intruders that they came upon.

The goblins didn't need food that much, the energies in this strange place kept them alive. But they still felt hunger, so any being that didn't turn into ethereal energy would be taken back to the encampment to get eaten.

Feng Liena was battered and bruised, but still alive. She was barely awake, still squirming while tied on a long log and carried by some disgusting looking monsters. She thought about the dark palm sect, cursing their name. She promised to herself that if she somehow survived she would do everything in her power to destroy that blasted sect along with its pig of a young master that forced her into this position. She was placed over the boiling cauldron, she would slowly get steamed by the boiling liquid and then maybe lowered into it. While she was about to pass out, she thought back to her clan members hoping that they would forgive her for pulling them into this mess along with her.

Her sight was getting blurry, she couldn't distinguish the faces of the drooling goblins anymore. But on the cusp of giving in to sleep, she heard a loud noise, it sounded like something heavy crashing into hard rock. This was Zhang Dong, that didn't quite make it past the half kilometer jump and crashed into the side of it. The goblins looked to the noise, grabbing their weapons as they prepared for battle. After the initial sound, they heard another one, a loud thumping noise followed by additional banging that continued and got closer.

Matt's head burst out from the ground, right in the middle of the festivities. He held back the urge to shout out 'Here's Matty' as he jumped out and delivered a devastating right hook to the closest hobgoblin, punching his head right off, his fist shining with a golden metallic luster. The wind pressure created from his fist strike made some of the lesser goblins fly backward, kicking up a storm.

*First things first...*

He thought while kicking the boiling cauldron to the side, right onto the fat goblin cook that screamed out in agony. He quickly grasped the log that the female cultivator was on and tossed her over his shoulder. He wanted to jump back over the chasm at first but due to his previous blunder, he feared that he might hurt the woman. He ran in the opposite direction, wanting to get the girl to safety first before facing off against the monsters.

The goblins weren't having it though as they all started chasing him, with murder in their eyes. The girl felt that something was happening as she was now moving in another direction and someone was carrying her. The trip was quite uncomfortable as the person was zig-zagging all over the place dodging arrows and some fire bolts that the shaman goblins were firing of.

Matt vaulted over the wooden wall and pulled out his sword. The girl got tossed into the air even further, she couldn't see much but could feel that the rope bindings were cleaved by something. Then she found herself in someone's arms, the person carried her like a princess and she could feel herself getting snuggled into a wide manly chest. Strength was leaving her body, but she could see the outline of the man's face that was saving her followed by some calming words.

"I've got you, everything is going to be okay"

She passed out after that, her body going limp as Zhang Dong escaped from the goblin encampment. It was more important to get this woman to safety, he didn't know how bad the poisoning was he needed to treat her wounds fast. The goblins wouldn't let their breakfast just up and run, so they started chasing after him. But Matt was a lot faster, the small goblins had short legs and wouldn't be able to catch up as he bolted into the thick bushes taking long strides, cracking the ground with each step he took.

After running for about twenty minutes he stopped by a waterfall, he could see that there was a cave hidden behind all that water. This looked like a good place to lay low till he treated the woman, the falling water would also probably block the smell of blood that was coming off her. Though not like he was afraid of fighting the monsters, just first aid came first.

He moved inside the cave, there were some strange green mushrooms that illuminated the inside. Luckily there was nothing strange living in the cave, so he placed the woman down on the ground. He started tearing up his white robe, making white bandage strips out of it as he still had no access to his storage ring and his clothes would just replace themselves anyway.

The first thing he did was striping her down, he felt apprehensive about it but he just had to bandage up all of her wounds. The woman was quite stacked, she could give his previous love encounter a run for her money. The most glaring thing he saw was a wound on the woman's thigh, he could see two puncture holes right there and puss leaking out.

*This looks like a snake bite... but the venom has already spread through her body at this point.*

He was no doctor and the people in this world mostly used pills for treating everything. He knew that sucking out snake venom from a wound was more or less bs and didn't work as the venom spread through the body quite fast. There were some people that claimed that you could neutralize venom by electrocuting a person, but it was never really proven to work.

*Well, not like this is the old world though.*

Matt had gone through the whole Zhang clan library, so he had a lot of knowledge in his brain. There was one method he could try because he didn't think he could produce antivenom, or make pills with a similar effect. Firstly, he used the purified water from his water bottle to soak in some torn up robe parts. He started washing the female cultivator from all the dirt, blood and grime that she got over time. He bandaged all the cuts, slowly turning the woman into a cute looking mummy. Then came the second part, there was a technique where you could share your vital energies with others.

The technique in question required skin on skin contact, so Matt sat down with the woman taking up the spot in his lap. He was bare chasted due to having ripped up his robe. He brought his arms around her, her soft body was now pressing into making him quite excited. He would nourish Feng Liena's body with his inner energy. The technique was slow working and you didn't need much practice to use it, it was also the only healing skill that he could use due to his low elemental affinities.

Time passed as he leaned back against the cold stone wall, the calming waterfall could be heard from inside the cave. After an hour, Matt was more or less sure that the goblins had lost their trail or just given up on the chase. He looked down at the curled up female in his arms, she looked quite cute if you got past the copious amount of make-up that had washed off by now. She was shivering and quite warm, probably having a high fever due to the snake bite.

*Well, at least the bleeding status vanished.*

His healing technique had managed to close off most of the wounds, but it was quite slow working she would probably need a lot of rest before everything healed up. More time had passed and Matt sighed, he couldn't move from this spot. The only thing he could do was look at the glowing mushrooms and whistle to himself as staring at the naked body of the woman in his arms was a bit too stimulating.

*Ah, I hope everyone is doing well...*

Around this time, a group of two hundred twenty cultivators was marching through some rocky terrain. There wasn't much besides rocks and debris around, but there was something in the distance. There stood a large fortress, it had gigantic walls that connected into watchtowers. There were four gates coming from each side of the structure that was cubical in shape. The placement of this fortress was strange, it was as if someone took it and dropped it in a deserted area. The structure looked sturdy and all, but it could be surrounded from all sides easily with no natural defenses in place whatsoever.

"So, is this the place that voice told us to gather up?"

Zhang Zhi asked while standing with his clan members, all of the officers were together and fine. The youths behind them had all of their weapons out and looked like they had battled something previously.

"It said that after clearing the first stage, we were to move to the fortress defense stage."

One of the officers replied while wondering what that meant, but that castle-like structure looked like a fortress. There was no one in the surrounding area besides the Zhang Clan, they might have been the first ones clearing the first stage.

"Mmm... very well, everyone get into formation we will approach slowly, keep your guard up."

Chapter 85

Two days prior:

Zhang Liu collapsed to his knees while holding onto his belly with one hand, the other was used to push himself off the cold floor as he tried not to vomit. The teleportation had twisted his insides making him feel like he had just finished riding some over the top rollercoaster. Some of his friends weren't as lucky as he could hear Zhang Hong barfing right next to him, though he was still wearing his mask.

He quickly gathered himself, moving off the floor wondering where they ended up in. He glanced about and could see the clan elders assessing the situation while the juniors were picking themselves off the ground.

"Quickly, everyone gather up, The General is missing!"

Everyone quickly jumped up to their feet, getting into formation as they all practiced. They did a headcount and everyone was there, but their Patriarch was missing. The elders used their detection skills to scan the area, but couldn't find their leaders aura signature anywhere in the vicinity.

They were in a circular cavern, the ceiling was about ten meters high and filled with stalactites. The place behind them was blocked and there were five corridors in front of them, leading to the unknown. Every corridor had a number above them and was lit by some torches and similar glowing fungus that Zhang Dong had come across.

"Everyone, check your equipment and gather with your lieutenants."

Said Zhang Zhi who was the second in command after the Patriarch, taking up the mantle in his absence. The Zhang Clan had designated a chain of command for situations where people got killed or split up. Matt didn't want to have clan members arguing on what to do, splitting up or infighting when one of the leaders was missing. The chain of command was quite rudimentary, starting with the first platoon and the twentieth was the last one going in order.

Zhang Hong had his helmet down now, rinsing it with some water that he took out of his spatial ring. No one really thought there was something wrong with that, as they didn't know that their patriarch was having problems with those at this moment. The twenty lieutenants gathered up at the five passages, they had a choice to make. Should they split up or move into one passage and hope for the best.

"The Patriarch said that we shouldn't split up, or at most split the teams in half if we had to."

Matt warned his people about the splitting up trope, which frequently weakened the whole group. Most of the time the smaller groups would encounter some overpowered monsters and get wiped out, due to having less manpower. Other times they would set off traps which ended in a similar fashion. Luckily, the Zhang clan members had their patriarch's detection skill so they decided to look into the aura around the entrances.

There were a lot of demonic and death energies around four of the corridors, with one of them having significantly less of them. This was the fourth corridor and after some deliberation, everyone agreed that they wouldn't split up and try to follow this path together. The passage was surprisingly wide and the ceiling left a lot of room to maneuver as well. The first three platoons were in the front with Zhang Zhi's team at the front, Zhang Jie's team was in the middle with the rear end guarded by the last platoon.

The sounds of their boots on the hard rocky floor could be heard, they walked for hours without anything happening the long corridor just continuing without end. Everyone was vigilant, but after trekking for so long they were wondering if this blasted corridor would ever end. Suddenly you could hear a strange crackling sound, everyone stopped in their tracks. They looked around but couldn't see anything in front or behind them, but then they looked up. There were many holes in the ceiling, those openings were giving off the strange noises.

They spotted the holes just in time as a greenish liquid was discharged from one of those openings, the people jumping to the sides as they couldn't activate their defensive formation in time. The moment the strange liquid came in contact with the floor it sizzled and started to dissolve the bedrock. The Zhang clan members then saw many centipede-like creatures slithering out from those holes. They were all about two or three meters long and started pouring out of the openings like a tide.

The cultivators managed to remain calm while getting into the defensive formation, quickly activating the water shield with about half the people in the large group. The rest that were the designated long-range attackers pulled out their weapons and trinkets. Some of them had bows, others had staff like weapons that aided with their Qi management. They started firing off their long-range attacks, blasting the creatures with pressurized water that mostly took the form of water serpents.

The insect monsters spit their venom on the shield but couldn't get through it. The creatures got whittled down quite fast by the organized defensive and offense combination, the monsters weren't that strong either just somewhere at the Qi condensation levels. There were quite a lot of them, falling down from the roof gnawing on the watery shield to no avail. The officers didn't have to act, so they just remained vigilant only acting if something stronger showed up.

The creatures kept coming for quite some time, the large hall quickly filled up with the creature carcasses which started dissipating into bubbles not so long after. In the end, a stronger version of the centipede monster arrived, it was about ten meters long and in the foundation establishment stage. It was taken out without any problems though, while the Qi condensation members did their thing Zhang Zhi pulled out his katana and bisected the creature in one go, showing off his swordsmanship in the process.

The monster attack wasn't anything dangerous, but without this shield, they might have been done in by the venom that the creatures used. They suffered no casualties this time around, showing off their teamwork in the process.

"Strange, these creatures are just vanishing... no beast cores either..."

The people were bewildered by this but they moved on, not wanting to wait here afraid that there might be more of these beasts. They continued walking for hours, getting attacked by the insect monsters on occasions. The further they went in, the more intense the fighting got, the creature's levels and numbers had also increased.

At the end everyone had their hands full, the officers had to chip in as they fought the larger monster centipedes that thrashed around, causing rocks to fall on their heads. Soon enough they could see the light at the end of the tunnel, prompting them to increase their pace. They ended in a room that looked similar to the first one, it was circular and had more tunnels leading out of it. But there was also a spring to the side, this spring had Qi recovering properties. If Matt saw this room, he would probably describe it as a safe zone.

More than half a day had passed since they set out, the juniors were feeling slightly tired so this would be a good spot to rest up. There was enough space to set up their tents, people took turns in guarding while everyone got to rest for a couple of hours. They were still in a closed-off dungeon with limited light, so they had no idea if it was day or night time.

"Where do you think Master is? Hope he is alright..."

Zhang Xue asked her brother while munching on some bread.

"I'm sure he is fine, Master is the strongest!"

The boy replied while shaking his fist at the ceiling, then just bit into his own piece of bread.

"I wonder if the other clans are also stuck in a place like this..."

Zhang Bao chimed in, as all of the 9th platoon members were sitting by a makeshift fire, eating. Everyone was in deep thought, the place looked gloomy and they wanted to get out of here as soon as possible.

"Stop overthinking things, just focus on the mission."

Zhang Tai replied as he stood up, getting ready for more marching through new corridors. The clan elders were examining them with the same method, it seemed to work out the first time as the monsters weren't overly powerful. Soon everyone packed up and they headed into the corridor that was the safest, what waited for them was more monsters. This time around it were skeletons, but the Zhang clan members made quick work of those. Without the need of keeping the defensive formation up, they could just unleash their wrath on the braindead monsters.

This pattern continued, they passed into another save zone, rested up and then moved on to fight a different type of enemy. They were lucky enough to never run into a corridor filled with traps or a dead end, probably all thanks to their detection technique which was the MVP of this expedition. After close to two days they ended up in a similar circular room, but this time around there was only one corridor leading out.

This seemed a little fishy, but not like they could turn back now as they felt that this might be the last one. Everyone got ready, with weapons drawn they all went in. The moment they entered the passageway unlit torches started lighting up, the passage went up and they all saw the large number of torches getting lit. It looked like something was inviting them to go there, this corridor was a lot shorter than the other one only taking five minutes of time to get to the end.

They didn't get attacked by anything on the way up, this was the first red flag. At the end, there was a large room, bigger than the rooms with the springs in them. There was a big closed gate right opposite where they came out, but there wasn't anything in this room. They looked up and to the sides but couldn't find anything out of the ordinary, some people stayed in the corridor while others went to check out that gate. It was quite sturdy, it didn't look like much but they could tell that damaging this thing would be impossible for them.

They decided to gather everyone in the room, trying to brainstorm the next move. But just at the moment when the last person entered the room, they heard a rumble. The passageway that they came from quickly closed itself as a giant rock wall slammed the thing shut. Everyone was at high alert as they got into their defensive formation. Quickly putting it up, not even waiting to see if it would be necessary.

They could hear strange clicking sounds and gears working as the whole room was rumbling. At first, they thought that perhaps the gate was about to open, but then some members looked up and could see that the ceiling was splitting apart.

"Above us!"

Everyone reacted, the defensive formation running at full capacity as some kind of creature descended from above them and slammed into their shield. The monster was really ugly, looking like a fusion of man and a scorpion. The lower half was a scorpion while the top part was humanoid. It had a hideous head with many sharp teeth protruding from its mouth, its tail flailing around and slamming into the defensive formation that shook from the impact. The creature was holding a weapon in its humanoid hand, that looked like a torn off pillar, it also possessed two claw-like appendages below the human torso. The monster's size was immense, it would be able to easily hold a person in one of its claw-like hands. Though the bigger problem was, that the creature was giving early stage core formation energy fluctuations.

"Don't falter, switch to the attacking formation!"

The lieutenants knew that the only way to defeat this monster was their large Spirit Serpent Formation, with everyone taking part. The monster kept pounding on their defensive formation, but they had trained to quickly shift between the two as well. The shield rippled, pushing the monster back for a couple of seconds before it started compressing back towards the Zhang clan cultivators. The monster flew back slightly, its large claw-like legs forming a skid mark as it got pushed back. The water-energy started taking the shape of a water serpent that towered over the boss monster.

The two large entities roared at each other, before charging out. The biggest problem for the Zhang members was that even though the room was large, there wasn't that much space to maneuver for this large battle formation of theirs. The water serpent slammed its head into the other creature's body while it tried to dig its crab-like claws into it. The formation was quite stable now and it would take more than that to take it down, also the way to get rid of battle formations was going for the cultivators inside and not for the energy construct itself. The creature was a bit too dumb for that, as it kept slashing at the watery body that just mended itself back.

It was looking good for the Zhang clan members, all their training came into fruition as the large serpent tail sent the creature flying into a wall. They slithered away, while the monster was momentarily stunned through the impact. The water serpent opened its mouth, gathering up energy as it charged its finishing move up. The boss monster didn't recover in time as when it looked at the enemy with its many eyes, it only to saw a blue beam coming its way. It raised those large claws to defend its upper body but to no avail, as the beam attack possessed an attacking power over the early stage of core formation quickly dissolving the monster into fine particles. To the Zhang member's surprise, the wall behind the monster didn't suffer any damage from their most powerful attack. The monster was slain and the cultivators rejoiced, but then they heard a strange robotic voice.

"Area 7 Girtablilu has been defeated, the first stage has been cleared. Please continue to the tower defense stage."

The members looked at the dissipating monster, the closed gate opening soon after the strange voice delivered the message. The people had no other place to go but forward, so after eating some Qi recovering pills the headed to the second stage.

Chapter 86

A monsters head rolled off its shoulders and plopped down to the ground. A silver-haired man was standing to the side with a sword over his shoulder. The night had passed and the female's fever had gone down, he had moved out to gather up some larger leaves. He managed to make a makeshift bed for the girl so that she didn't need to sleep on the cold rocky floor and placed a large boulder at the entrance of the cave so that no strange creature would wonder in. He ripped up his self regenerating robe to make a blanket, but that left him bare-chested yet again.

*I'm going to catch a cold like this...*

He came across a scouting party composed of some goblins and hobgoblins which he promptly sliced apart. He decided to pay them a visit, maybe there would be something that would explain the situation at that goblin encampment. He was a bit apprehensive about leaving the woman back in the cave, but she should be okay for the time being. The monsters didn't really show any good tracking abilities, they didn't even find them after a whole night had passed.

"I guess it's time to slay some goblins."

He vanished from the spot and appeared up on one of the tall trees. He started jumping onto the thick branches, heading towards the enemy headquarters. He noticed a pattern in how the monsters operated in this 'training ground', they tended to react to noises and started attacking you the moment you got into their line of sight. Well, at least the more stupid ones did the ones above the core formation and with special classes had some intelligence to them. The goblin chieftain, for instance, didn't chase after him and the girl leaving it up to his followers instead.

*Well, maybe its a boss monster and needs a special trigger to aggro?*

He started thinking about the monsters as MMORPG mobs, that had a limited range and wouldn't chase you after you got out of it. Maybe someone from earth was reincarnated here and he made this place to work as a game? This would probably be something that he would do if he got bored enough with time.

Matt came to a stop, he was back at the front gate of the goblin encampment. The small green skins were leaning up against their makeshift gate, sleeping on the job with some rusty looking spears. He scanned the area again, wondering if something stronger than a goblin chieftain would be in here.

*Well, I guess I can let loose here...*

He formed a fist and raised it up, delivering a blow to his peck looking as it turned to golden metal at the moment of the impact. The enemies he would be facing shouldn't be able to pierce his metal-like skin so he could test out his techniques without worrying. He nodded to himself and took out his sword, forming a thin layer of lightning energy around the bladed part for added sharpness. He jumped up, causing the large wooden branch to snap in the process. Lightning energies gathered around his frame and expanded as he activated his newest Heavenly Lightning Terrain technique.

The sleeping sentry didn't even react before he got bisected by the energy sword, the downward slice forming a fissure on the ground as the wind pressure and lightning energies continued on, crashing into the large wooden gate. The makeshift doorway burst open, many large splinters raining down and delivering some residual damage to the unsuspecting goblins inside.

Matt heard some kind of horn being sounded, large amounts of green midgets poured out of holes in the ground and from the large wooden shacks in the surrounding area. They were greeted by electrical discharges the moment they entered Zhang Dong's lightning terrain. The technique was less powerful due to the Qi dissipating properties of this area but it still worked as intended passively delivering damage to the invaders while Matt delivered the finishing strikes with his sword.

He was constantly aiming for their necks or hearts, each strike meant death for one of the green attackers even the more powerful hobgoblins couldn't do anything against this human intruder. It was more or less a one-sided massacre, blood spraying everywhere but soon dissipating into nothingness along with the summoned monsters. The goblin chieftain was sitting in his makeshift throne, looking at the human attacker while gnawing on some kind of bone.

Soon enough though, he roared out in fury the scream causing Matt to halt his actions momentarily. He had taken out most of the hobgoblins and shaman goblins in the vicinity, maybe this was enough to trigger this mini-boss to action?

"Oh, are you approaching me?"

The monster's small beady eyes went red and it snorted something in an unknown language at the human, Matt kind of imagined what his reply was. The goblin chieftain was about the same height as Zhang Dong, he had some strange tribal tattoos all over its green skin. There was a big gash from his left eyebrow going up to his lip, letting you see some of his teeth as it hadn't healed fully. The monster was carrying a huge bladed weapon, it looked like a slightly elongated cleaver with a hooked part on the tip.

The monster kicked itself off the ground, quickly closing the distance between itself and the attacker. Some smaller goblins that were in the way got trampled and turned into meat paste instantly. Matt didn't feel like evading as he took the attack head-on, the ground trembling under his feet as the monster's cleaver collided with his sword. Matt didn't budge a muscle as his feet remained firmly planted on the rocky ground, the monster gnashing his teeth at the human in front and then giving out another outcry.

"Ugh, your breath stinks."

The goblin chief tried using a bite attack but it was unsuccessful as he received a punch to his face instead, the monster's nose was now indented as he flew backward and crashed into a wooden shack. More goblins appeared to back up their leader, but they weren't much use after getting sliced up by the enemy's blade.

*I feel like I could keel these trash mobs faster if I had a second sword...*

He picked up a goblin sword from the ground, it used to belong to one of the hobgoblin warriors so it was a bit better than the rest. He went into a stance, holding one of the swords higher and the other one lower. This felt a bit awkward, the monsters dashed at him but he just started dancing around them quickly slicing the weaker monsters apart. This did indeed make him kill the monsters faster, but he felt that he lost some measure of control and his defense suffered as he had to pay attention to his second sword as well now.

*Maybe it will be better if I put a third one into my mouth...*

He looked at another sword that was on the ground, the handle was just wrapped up with something and didn't look sanitary at all.

*Ehh... think I'll pass...*

He threw the borrowed sword at one of the goblins impaling it to a wall and then heard a monster roaring. This was the Chief that burst out, swinging his blade at Matt. He looked slightly different, he was now a head taller and all red. Muscles bulging and an angry face as he tried to overpower his attacker once more.

*Is this the second phase?*

Matt glanced at the monster, but it was still in the late stage, it had the berserker prefix added though. He was slightly more powerful and faster, but not nearly enough to bring this cultivator down. He sparred with the goblin Chief for a while, using the creature as a training dummy. He didn't have anyone to spar with back in the Zhang Clan, so this would be a good training session. But after a while, he found the monster's attacks to be quite sluggish and easy to evade or parry. It was more brawn than brains so the pattern was quite easy to get used to, so soon enough he delivered the finisher sending the beast's head up into the air.

There were still some monsters left though, so he used this chance to test his another attack out. He placed his palms together making it look like he was praying, his Heavenly Lightning Terrain technique started closing up decreasing in size and gathering around him. The lightning energies inside the terrain started acting up though, becoming more random and chaotic. The Qi started getting compressed more and more while the enemy goblins charged at him. The moment they closed in on him, he separated his palms making a 'T' like pose with his palms pointing upwards.

The energies burst out with an explosion of lightning energy, everything outside where he was standing lit up like a Christmas tree and was surrounded by bright blue energy. The goblin silhouettes vanished within the energy dome that was formed, quickly dissolving into fine particles as he delivered a wide-area attack. After the energies dissipated, he was standing on a little podium of ground, everything within a wide radius was blasted into nothingness. There was a large hole around him now, some burnt up hatchets and other broken items. Anything past that was blown back as well, he destroyed the upper encampment of the goblins in one attack not leaving much behind in the process.

"Wait..."

In his battle excitement he forgot that he wanted to search this place for clues, he scratched his cheek while looking around the desolated area wondering if anything of value was left behind.

"Well... luckily no one saw that..."

He started going around the place, managing to find the boss monsters hatchet weapon that was of a high earth grade. He also managed to find a fan type weapon suited for wind elemental users, this made him think back to the lady that he saved, this probably belonged to her. He was glad that it survived his explosion. He didn't find much more of note besides that, the goblins were all dead now. He even went into one of their burrows, but most of the tunnels had collapsed after his qi explosion. He didn't really want to dig through the debris, and the fan weapon made him think about the sleeping woman that he didn't want to leave there for more than he had to.

*Time to go back, there were some fruits on the way here, I'll get them for that girl, she might be hungry.*

After being here for a week, he started thinking that his clan members were probably in another area altogether. This was probably a place to test the party leaders, making them fight without having an army to back them up.

*Though, still wonder what those guys are up to... nothing left but to move forward.*

He thought to himself while going back to his temporary state of residence.

Back in the cave, Feng Liena was dreaming about her childhood, she was running around with a ball in her hand tossing it at her father who did the same in return. She was smiling wide, hugging on her daddy while enjoying her day to day life. But then things changed, she was taken away the scenery changing. She was now ten years old, a woman was screaming at her making her do various exercises, shouting that she had to get strong for the clan.

The Feng Clan was a Matriarchal one, this meant that the ones on top were all women and they didn't allow men into the upper echelon. After a woman from the Feng clan got married to someone outside a deal was made, every female offspring was to be sent back to the clan after they reached the age of five. This was a favorable agreement for both parties as regular patriarchal clans preferred offsprings of the male gender, so they were okay with sending the females back while receiving the boys in return.

The girls were trained hard, causing them to be rough and rigid. The Feng clan didn't really care about having their cultivators be very womanly, as power was the driving force. This was also the cause of their appearance, most of the girls didn't want to be treated like jade-like beauties. Thus they produced the more tanned gyaru look, to mixed reactions of other people around them. They also tended to be quite tomboyish and aggressive.

Feng Liena opened up her eyes slowly, she felt quite refreshed for some reason. She remembered that she was captured by some monsters, but the rest was a blur. When she opened up her eyes she saw a large man above her, he was bare-chested and reaching out with his hand to do something. She reached out to him, placing her hands on the man's cheeks. The silver-haired man had a strange expression, that quickly turned to shock as the female cultivator gripped those cheeks with all her strength and delivered a headbutt straight to his face.

"The hell do you think you're doing!"

Chapter 87

Matt had returned to the hideout with some fruits and water in his hand. He placed the cleaver he had gotten and the two green fans that belonged to the woman on the side. He looked at the sleeping beauty and noticed that the makeshift pillow he created from his robe and leaves was to the side, so being the nice guy that he was, he tried to move it back under her head. That was when she woke up though, her face quickly switched from one of surprise to one of rage as he felt his nose get hit by her forehead.

Feng Liena noticed that she made a mistake as the moment her head connected with the 'pervert's' face, she felt like she headbutted a lump of spirit iron. He did get a bloody nose due to the hit, but she got a lump on her head as well. She fell back and finally noticed that she was covered in bandages all over, the wound on her thigh that the snake monster had bitten in was mostly gone.

"God damn... that hurts...what was that for?"

Matt wobbled back due to the sudden hit, his nose all red, luckily no bones were broken. Liena looked at the cave, her robe was to the side still covered in some blood but there were signs of it getting washed. She noticed the man's robe that was ripped all over, the bandages clearly came for that. There were some scattered fruits on the floor and she remembered that there was someone that looked like this guy back before they entered the secret ground. The gears started turning in her head as she looked at the situation, she moved her head a bit to the side, her mouth twitching between a smile and a thrown.

She slowly recalled what transpired yesterday, the snake bite, the goblin attack and the soothing voice that called out to her during the rescue. She then just moved her hands to her hips and started laughing.

"Oh ho ho, sorry there little bro. I thought you were just some pervert."

Matt looked at the woman that started laughing like some old man, blood was running down his nose. He was a bit surprised that she managed to injure him through the headbutt.

"L... little bro?"

Feelings one's age through their aura wasn't anything special, so the woman knew that the man in front of her was younger. She looked at her robes that were to the side, Matt didn't actually know how to wash things properly so he kind of soaked them in the river with not much success. Then set them to the side after drying them out with the use of his Qi abilities.

"Ah, could you turn around?"

He wanted to ask her some questions but then saw as she grabbed her robes from the side. Those robes were slightly torn up from the goblin attack. Normally he would be able to fix them in his crafting abode, but his system still wasn't letting him in there.

"Ah..sure..."

He nodded and turned around, wondering if he should just leave the cave but as he was about to do so, the woman started speaking.

"You were with one of the other clans right? What was your name again?"

Matt stopped in his tracks as the woman spoke, the rustling of clothing happening right behind his back. She had gone from hostile, right to being quite buddy-buddy, guess she liked to do things at her own pace.

"Yes, I'm from the Zhang Clan, the name is Zhang Dong..."

He didn't turn around, he already saw the woman naked so didn't really feel embarrassed or anything, just wanted to be courteous. The girl hadn't introduced herself yet, so he tried not to say her name that the system already showed him. He had a clear idea about Liena's capabilities, she might have been only in the late stage of core formation but she had a higher graded cultivation method.

"Zhang Dong... think I heard that somewhere... oh, you're that young brother that trashed all those clans single-handedly. Never liked those old coots, they always gave me those lecherous looks. You can turn around."

Matt craned his neck back, he had some questions he wanted to ask the woman. When he looked at her, she was just standing there and munching on a peach-like fruit that he found. He tried it out previously, it was quite rich in spiritual energy and was sweet. But as he was moving his hand up and opening his mouth to speak, Liena spoke up first once again.

"I must thank you for the timely aid, but I could have gotten away myself!"

Matt was holding his hand up high, his index finger outstretched as he wanted to say something but couldn't quite put his thoughts to words. His mouth opened but then closed again as he watched the tanned woman stick her chest out, proclaiming that she would have been just fine.

"Uhhh... s-sure..."

Matt didn't really know what to think of this person, he thought she would be the silent jade-like beauty type. Or maybe, some sensual older sister type. She felt a lot more chipper than he expected, it felt more like he was talking with a dude than a chick. She even started punching the air with her small fists, showing off her battle strength as wind elements gathered around that cute fist of hers. He thought that this lady would be a lot more violent after the first headbutt. Most of the time in novels, they would misunderstand the protagonist and start battling or calling them a pervert. This girl on the other hand after the initial misunderstanding caught on quite fast and figured out that he was the one that saved her. The problem was the little brother part...

"So you see little Dong, you just need to leave the rest up to big sis Liena. If you follow my lead, I'm sure we can get through this blasted forest in no time!"

*The hell, little dong?*

This needed to stop if it continued he would be a designated henchman of this older sister. He didn't really mind if she tagged along with him, but it would be another thing if it was he that would be tagging along with her. Soon enough, he would have to carry her stuff around and act like a retainer.

"Okay, let's get one thing straight Feng Liena. I'm no little Dong... I'm more of a Big Dong... no wait... that came out wrong. Let's just forget about the names."

He moved his hands over his chest and leaned back against the cold cave wall, making his face look solemn and all cultivator like. He tried furrowing his brows to look extra serious and menacing.

"I have been wandering around this forest for about a week now, you're the first person I've come across. Do you have any clues as to where we are? I think this might be part of the test that the immortal that made this place came up with, I reckon our clan members are in a different section taking part in a different type of test."

Feng Liena moved her thumb to her chin and looked with her eyes to the side as she contemplated. Matt looked at the woman, was that steam that was coming out of her ears? The woman wasn't much of a thinker, the old cultivator lady and her retainers did most of that, she only needed to cultivate diligently. So, she just stomped her foot on the ground making the rock below her shatter as she shouted out.

"Ahhh... who cares! We just need to beat up some beasts and move forward! Don't worry little Dong, I have it all figured out!"

She proclaimed her finger pointing at the ceiling as if she wanted to point it at the heavens. Matt realized that his first party member wasn't all that bright, he sure hoped that the woman wouldn't be a burden. Abandoning people wasn't his style, so he wondered what would be the best way to move forward. He tried asking about some other things, but the moment he spoke up...

"Miss Lien..."

"Big Sis!"

"Missus Lie..."

"Big Sis!"

"Lien..."

"BIG SIS!"

He dropped his head, the woman was probably used to getting called elder sister back in her clan. He wasn't sure why she was so adamant about giving up her title.

"Fine! Big Sis Liena... how about we travel together, I'm sure we can achieve more if we travel in a group. The elders from the other clans must be around here somewhere, maybe we can find them before those beasts get to them."

The woman crossed her arms over her own chest, copying Zhang Dong's way of standing. Though due to being quite stacked, her forearms squished into those two mountains making Matt's heart skip a beat. She nodded a couple of times while looking to the side as if she was considering his proposal.

"I agree, but on one condition!"

"Which is?"

"I'm the leader and you have to call me big sis~"

He wasn't sure why the woman was acting like a middle schooler but due to being an introvert he was getting tired of the prolonged conversation that was going nowhere. The woman didn't seem that stuck up, was she really the stuck up young Matriarch that denied any men that approached her. She sounded quite friendly, well besides the headbutt part, but that was an understandable reaction in that situation. He just shrugged and nodded at her request, he didn't really care about things like being 'Team leader' at least his new companion was cute.

The two people headed out, Matt constructed another water bottle so that Liena didn't have to drink from his. It felt a bit uncomfortable when he was making it as she kept staring at him when he was skillfully wrapping the vines around the bamboo bottle. Did this woman never go outside or something, she was like a little kid with stars in her eyes looking at the construction process.

They started running into more monsters as time passed, Matt could detect their life signals so after getting an okay from his new big sis he was now the scout. The woman didn't get to fight that much as Matt still wanted to get the points from the kills, even though they were minor.

There was another strange phenomenon that they came across. After killing some trashy mobs, they turned to spirit bubbles as always. Soon enough though, he felt a high concentration of similar energy particles. He looked at the spot it was coming from and could see a monster getting created or summoned in that spot. The fresh creature looked around and went on its way like it was a natural thing.

*They have a respawn time as well? So there is no way to kill them all?*

He wondered if the goblin town he previously cleared out would be populated again. This would be a good thing if he had time to farm for things like this high grade hatchet weapon. He took it with him not as a weapon, but as something that he could absorb later. The regular creatures only had lower graded gear with them, only the boss monsters had the good stuff with them.

While adventuring forward the two people spotted something, it was a giant pillar of fire just shooting into the air along with a gust of wind that indicated an explosion. The two looked at each other and quickly headed in that direction, it looked like other cultivators were fighting. They arrived at the spot after a couple of minutes only to find a charred corpse and gore bits all over the place. The torn-up robe had a familiar-looking emblem on it.

*Isn't this the emblem that pimp guy's ship had? Did he get killed, or was it another member from his clan...*

That person had more ships with him and back in the teleportation chamber, Matt made a mental note to count how many clans were participating. His clan took out just one spot, Feng Liena's took up two with the busty big sis here and with the baked potato granny that she came with as the second core formation expert. The red-haired male came with two other core formation cultivators which left him with three spots. The remaining spots were taken up by two other clans, with two spots each. The Zhang clan was considered the weakest from the point of these other clans as they only brought one core formation expert with them.

"That's one down...I hope we find the rest before these monsters get to them..."

The explosion was fresh, so Matt could sense a fight in the distance. He followed the energy reading quickly, hoping that he would be there on time.

Chapter 88

Matt slung the large cleaver weapon over his shoulder and headed out while Feng Liena followed after him. He could feel multiple beings in that area, they were mostly in the core formation. After the two arrived closer to the scene, they could see the battle unfolding.

The first person Zhang Dong saw was someone he was familiar with, he could see his name thanks to the system and it was Huo Qiang. It was the red-haired man that he saw before entering the secret ground. There was another person with him, an older looking gentleman with mutton chops that looked injured. He was wearing the same clan pattern on his torn up robe, it being of the same clan that the burly red-haired man belonged too. The two were standing back to back while surrounded by some monsters, it weren't goblins this time around but orcs. There were quite a lot of them and Matt could even see an ogre amongst the group. Most of the monsters were in the middle stage but there were some in late stages of core formation.

The two cultivators were both in the late stage of core formation, so all things considered they were quite strong. There were many green skins that were evaporating into dust after getting slain but they just kept coming at them. Matt wanted to jump in and help the two guys out, but when he looked to the side, his big sis was just scoffing and walking in the opposite direction.

"W-wait, where are you going? We have to help them..."

Matt asked while looking between the battle zone and the female cultivator that had furrowed brows and a rather cute frown.

"Pff, just leave those bastards be, we don't need to help people like them out."

The woman moved her face to the side, Matt caught on fast deducing that there must be some animosity between her and the people that were fighting. Though this didn't really sit well with him, the more party members they got the better their chances of survival would be. He was sure they could talk it out in the end, if not he could always show his hand to reel them in. He tried out some reverse psychology to get his team leader to follow him into battle.

"Ah, it's fine to be afraid elder sister. There are so many of those monsters, it's only natural that you are hesitating. Just leave this to your little brother, you can just watch from afar."

You could see the pink-haired girl fuming with rage the moment Zhang Dong insinuated that she was afraid of the monsters. He didn't stay long enough to hear her complain as there was no time, he just bolted for the battle area and felt that the lady followed behind him soon enough, at least she could offer him a bit of range support with those wind techniques.

The two fighters weren't aware of Zhang Dong and Feng Liena as they were fighting for their dear life. The two belonged to the Huo Clan, this was a fire element type clan with the younger-looking youth being the strongest son of the current clan Patriarch. The man next to him was one of his bodyguards that his clan sent out with him to this secret ground. The dark palm sect had requested help from them and promised riches and even cultivation resources if they managed to figure out the testing grounds. Being the proud clan that they were, the Patriarch decided to send quite a force consisting of the three strongest core formation experts from his clan beside himself.

They all miscalculated that the whole expedition thing was a hoax and that the dark palm sect didn't actually expect anyone to return from it. Being the stuck up clan that they were, they expected riches and an easy payout even though it was known that the previous exploration attempt failed. They naturally thought that the reason was that the people sent were just too darn weak, the Zhang clan was just a middle-sized clan and the Huo Clan was a grade above it in strength even before the previous one lost most of their fighting potential.

Huo Qiang was quite lucky in the beginning, he found one of his clan elders just a couple of days after being spirited away into the wilderness. After about a week they even found the second one as well, so now they were all together and fighting with the monsters in their own little group. But, the creatures just kept coming and coming. They had to constantly move and fight, the monsters were everywhere and they were getting harder to defeat the more time passed.

The life-saving trinkets and talisman started getting used up, they only had a few out the rest was locked in their storage rings. Soon enough they came across the large Orc tribe village, the three masters weren't that good at sneaking around so they were spotted by the green skins while trying to avoid the settlement.

The monsters poured in like moths attracted to the flame while the three tried to escape, but they found themselves surrounded. One of their clan members tried buying them some time so that they could escape. He burned his cultivation base making himself burst into a flaming inferno opening up a path for his two clan members to escape. The plan didn't work though as even though they managed to run away from that group another one was waiting for them around the corner and they were surrounded by them again.

"What's wrong with these beasts? Don't they fear death at all?"

The red-haired man said while the gauntlets that he was wearing on his hands glowed red. He delivered a devastating blow to one of the nearby orc's sending the creature flying back, it's head broken as its body collided with a close-by tree. The two cultivators were quite strong, but the monsters just kept swarming them not caring for their own safety whatsoever. The two men were getting tired slowly, their spiritual energy was getting drained as they landed attack after attack, killing the monster mobs one after another in quick succession.

"Young Master, you must save yourself. You are the future of the clan, you must not perish here!"

The mutton chop beard elder said, his fists were also covered by some kind of glove weapon along with his legs. From the way the two were carrying themselves, it looked like they were close range specialists. The older man had a robust build as well, his body was already battered and bruised from the prolonged fighting. He was tasked with protecting this young master of his, he was a one in a million genius of the Huo clan, his only fault was that he was quite the womanizer.

The elder was contemplating doing a suicide rush as the other clan member, but before that could happen he heard a strange sound coming from afar. It sounded like thunder and lightning, but there were no clouds above them. The monsters were focused on the other two cultivators so they didn't pay attention at the white-haired cultivator that was charging at them from behind, coated in lightning.

Zhang Dong burst to the scene, swinging the large goblin cleaver with one hand and his charged up sword with the other. Feng Liena just stood up on one of the large trees and started blasting the creatures with her ranged attacks, not keen on getting into a close melee fight.

The orcs finally noticed the other intruders as they were flanked by Matt's charge, he managed to decapitate a couple of them with his two-sword style that still needed some work. The Huo clan cultivators saw this as a chance and started battling their enemies with more vigor as some backup had arrived. They recognized the white-haired man from the clan assembly but didn't know why he was helping them. They were sure about one thing, this Zhang Clan Patriarch was a lot stronger than they had thought, by the way, he was cutting into those monsters, he must be in the great circle they thought.

"Thanks for the assistance brother!"

Huo Qiang shouted while charging up his fist, you could see small red dots gathering around the man's fist. The metallic gloves he was wearing were made of a silver looking alloy, they had various runic patterns etched into them and as he gathered the fire energies they gave of a crimson glow as well. He struck a nasty looking orc with an open palm strike, caving the monsters whole chest in and blasting it back into the orc group that was charging at them.

The fight continued, the bodies of the monsters continuously vanished with the help of the Zhang Clan Patriarch and his lovely helper that was pouting in the back. Soon enough the large ogre appeared, it went after the red-haired man while swinging a tree, using it as a club. Qiang's punch connected with the makeshift weapon, the tree catching fire and turning into a mass of splinters.

Mutton chops was doing a bit worse than the rest of the group, he was still in the late stage but if you ranked everyone here, he would be last in terms of spiritual energy. He was already battered as he and the other retainer were being overprotective of their young master and they used their bodies to defend him. He was about to get impaled by a similar-looking hatchet weapon that one of the orc warriors was aiming at his head, but just before it landed a wind blade came from afar and deflected the attack, this was enough for the man to land a killing blow on the creature that attacked him.

He looked in the direction the attack came from and saw the Feng clan matriarch, she was standing on one of the branches and looking quite haughty. The battle continued, the cultivators managed to wiggle out of the spot that they were surrounded. This gave them some leeway as they didn't need to watch their backs anymore and could unleash a wider range of attacks.

The monsters weren't letting up though, but with time they got whittled down by the combined might of the four cultivators that started working as a team. Matt looked at all the weapons that the monsters dropped, if he could just gather those up he might be able to reach the great circle with his body refining skill. Though he didn't really want to start absorbing it with people next to him, plus he would need to carry the pile of hatchets and strange-looking weapons with him.

*If it only didn't take so long to absorb one of these...*

"Well, if it isn't Feng Liena, have you reconsidered my proposal?"

Huo Qiang asked in a cheery tone as he walked over to the busty gal. Matt could see the woman's expression changing from a neutral one, to one of rage and disgust. He didn't know that a beauty like her could furrow her brows that much, that frown was quite impressive.

"I would rather marry a donkey than someone like you! How many concubines do you even have?"

Feng Liena stomped the ground while scoffing at the proposal, the red-haired man just looked at her and shrugged.

"Oh, just about ninety nine, you could be the hundredth one~"

He laughed to himself while looking at the woman whose face started going red, she was really fuming. She even took out her battle fans and went into a battle stance, the mutton chop uncle intervened putting himself between his young master and the woman.

"Halt, you will not harm the young master!"

A fight was about to break out, the old guy was taking his job very seriously and he would pounce on the young lady the moment she showed animosity towards his young master. Matt just facepalmed while looking at the scene, guess these people weren't good at working together. He raised his fist up into the air it crackling with lightning, he activated his avatar form on it along with his condensing skill. He didn't need to cover his whole body with the technique, being able to use it on separate body parts which cost him less spiritual energy.

He slammed his fist into the ground, making the group of three turn their heads. The slam caused the ground to shake, the residual blast kicked up a storm, the people using their forearms to protect their eyes from the sand that was blown up.

"Enough! Stop fighting, we need to work together to get through this... don't you get what this place is by now?"

Matt made sure to add some spiritual energy to make his voice sound extra menacingly, his fist glowing and discharging electricity into the surroundings.

The three people gulped a bit after witnessing the strike, they clearly knew that if something like that landed on them they would turn into meat paste. They realized that the white-haired man was clearly the strongest from this group, probably at the great circle of core formation.

"Little Dong... didn't know that you were this strong... big sis is impressed!"

Matt wanted to run up and bonk the pink-haired dolt on the head after hearing that, she kind of ruined his cool move with just a few words. He gave out a sigh and moved over to the group, he wanted to ask some questions and also force everyone to cooperate as he was still sure that this was a place where you couldn't just do things alone.

Chapter 89

In another place.

The Zhang Clan members approached the large fortress. The walls were immense making the cultivators feel like tiny ants, the moment they came close to the large gate it started shaking. The people took up their combat stance, ready for battle. The doors opened up from within, the loud creaking noises made some people from the group feel quite uncomfortable as they fought the urge to plug their ears up.

They thought that perhaps some enemies would burst through that door, but after they opened nothing but silence greeted them. Zhang Zhi waved his hand forward taking two squads with him, forming a small scouting party. The insides were quite barren, the cultivators couldn't feel any life coming from the surrounding.

The rest of the group slowly crept in, there was still a chance of a surprise attack coming like from those centipede monsters. Also, a boss monster might appear in that closed-off room, so they kept vigilant as everyone entered the large empty structure. The outside was quite basic, consisting of four walls connecting to four towers. Each wall had a large gate in the middle, it was made from some strange material and quite resistant. The fortress looked unsuspecting, the only thing out of the ordinary was the place it was in and its size.

The inside of the structure had an inner area, the structure looked like a smaller castle that was protected by more walls. The Zhang Clan members started looking around, they found barracks that had basic living quarters where they could sleep in. There was a kitchen area as well as a large well that was also close by, so they wouldn't run out of water anytime soon. The kitchen had a large storage area which surprisingly had some food in it, there were formations that kept it cool and from rotting.

Zhang Zhi and the other officers went into the castle-like structure, which had many smaller rooms and one larger hall. The moment the people walked in they heard a strange sound, green light filled their eyes as something appeared out of thin air. It was a miniature version of the fortress, just made from light. The people backed away, looking at the green projection, if Matt was here he would probably be able to figure this thing out as it was something a gamer would find interesting.

These old fashioned cultivators didn't know what they were looking at, there was a panel with some numbers in the corner. There were some blue dots spread out throughout the hologram, and there were exactly 220 of them. More people came into the room, in hopes of figuring out this strange spiritual treasure. The officers went closer, Zhang Jie was there as well and being quite curious she poked at the panel where the points were, this prompted it to glow and show her a tiny miniature version of a ballista with the number 25 hovering above it.

The people were surprised, the small siege weapon could be picked up by them but when they let it go it vanished and appeared back next to the display panel. After investigating more, one of the people dragged the weapon to one of the towers the hologram that was red started turning green for some reason. When he let it go, the weapon appeared to be stuck to the tower now. Soon enough a commotion could be heard outside.

"What's wrong? Report!"

A junior member appeared soon enough, it was a familiar-looking chubby fellow by the name of Zhang Hong.

"Reporting sir! Just a moment ago we felt a surge in spiritual energy by one of the towers and a crossbow like weapon appeared out of thin air!"

The foundation establishment elders looked at each other, then to the miniature version of the fortress. They quickly looked outside one of the small windows and could see the weapon now being placed on the tower wall, ready to fire and with some ballista bolts included. They tried repeating the process and managed to place another one of those siege weapons on a different tower. But when they tried doing it once more on the third one, they couldn't pull the small weapon hologram anymore.

"...Wasn't this number higher previously..."

Zhang Jie said while looking at the control panel, the number was, of course, the number of points they had for the building. They figured out that this number correlated to the one above the ballista, they had 15 points left and it cost 25 to build.

"But how do we increase this number now... and is there a use for those weapons out there..."

The people examined the siege weapon, it looked a bit strange in the way that it couldn't be shot manually. It was closed off and they couldn't insert any of the bolts that were lying next to it. Later on, the clan would find out how these tower defense items worked, but for now, they all headed inside.

Junior members were stationed on the walls and towers, but the whole fortress was just too huge so they had to spread themselves thin. This thing was clearly built for more than two hundred people to run, they needed at least a thousand people for it. The first night went by fast, nothing happened no monster attacks and no enemies in sight. The cultivators started wondering if the voice had something else in mind with the second phase. The elders were in the control room, figuring out the game like controls while the juniors looked at the gate opening and closing on their own.

Just as the next day was coming to a close one of the sentries noticed people walking towards them. Everyone peeked out from the safety of the fortress, they could see a small group moving towards them. The group was filled out by tanned ladies with way too much makeup, they looked disgruntled and tired. From the 220 strong group only about half of them remained.

"Open the gates, help the wounded!"

The gates were opened, the Zhang Clan was quite good at the healing arts and they also had various restorative pills. Their Patriarch ordered them to support the other expedition participants if it was possible. They were told to offer assistance, but react accordingly if the other clans or cultivators were hostile.

The dark-skinned females were on their toes as they saw the large gates opening and cultivators pouring out. They recognized them to be one of the people that came with them to the secret grounds, mostly due to the eye-catching gear that made them look like a bunch black power rangers.

"Don't worry, we are here to help, come inside of the fortress for treatment."

Zhang Jie said while moving in with her platoon along with a couple more. The Feng clan members looked at each other and nodded, there were a lot of injured among them. They thought that if the other clan was hostile, they wouldn't offer them any help in the first place and just slaughter them instead.

"The Feng clan offers their respect."

One of the older cultivator women bowed with cupped hands while all of them headed inside. Most of the deaths were from the Qi condensation members from the Feng clan. They went through a similar dungeon like the Zhang Clan, but they weren't prepared as well as them for the things that were inside. Somehow they managed to get to the boss room while using up quite a lot of defensive trinkets and losing some of their members on the way here. Some died to traps, some to the monsters that kept pouring in.

The last boss was a snake-like creature, spitting venom and thrashing its tail at the female cultivators. They managed to slay it with the help of some battle formations and treasures that allowed them to deliver an attack at the core formation level. Without the help of their treasures, they would have been wiped out by the strange-looking creature.

The Zhang Clan offered their help, placing the most injured people in the barracks while offering them their healing arts. They kept their pills to themselves, mostly worried that they would run out too fast if they used them all willy nilly. Luckily most of the cultivator women that survived to this point, weren't in critical condition. Most of them would recover in a couple of days, with some meditation and aid of the water-based regeneration healing arts that the Zhang Clan implemented.

As time passed more and more of the other cultivators started showing up, most of them being in a sorry state. Life in this world was harsh, most of the cultivators on top didn't really care about their weaker clan members. You really had to show that you were worth it, for anyone to throw a bone your way. The other way was through family ties, but even then the most promising offspring usually monopolized everything from his or her lesser siblings.

The Qi condensation members of this expedition were the most likely to be tossed aside. The losses were immense among that power bracket. Even though the Zhang Clan started off with the least amount of members of all the participating powers, they didn't lose anyone while the other people burned through their defensive and offensive treasures to survive their boss battles.

The most people belonged to the Huo clan though, they did have 660 members participating. Though their numbers were cut by more than half, one team only returned with about thirty members. If you did a headcount, there were 220 Zhang Clan members, 326 Huo clan members, 233 Feng clan members. From the remaining four participating parties, only one team from each returned amounting to about 250 members.

The moment that the last person set foot in the fortress, the people heard the strange robotic voice once more.

"Attention, the second stage will commence in exactly twelve hours."

"Please get ready for the first wave."

The message repeated itself for a minute before silence fell on the cultivators, everyone looked at each other a commotion ready to break out. What was that strange voice, what was the first wave? From their experience, they knew that it wasn't anything good.

The Zhang Clan members were the first group to arrive, so they explained a couple of things. The Feng clan members showed to most respect for the help, but the rest was a bit reserved. Everyone from the top cultivators gathered in the big hall with the hologram to discuss the next step. Everyone got clued in about the strange magical treasures, the clan also revealed that they thought that the blue dots were the people that were around the fortress. The other people were a bit suspicious that this clan with the strange-looking combat robes, was just revealing all of their secrets, but they were just following the instructions of their Patriarch.

"That is why I hope we can all work together, the strange voice said that something will start in twelve hours, we need to prepare and station our people on the walls."

Zhang Zhi chimed in, while some other older-looking cultivators contemplated their next move. There were too many separate forces here, no one knew if they wouldn't get stabbed in the back by the other people in this room if push came to shove. The Zhang Clan wanted to spread people around the walls to prepare for battle, they were the only force without casualties so they could head out at any moment.

"How about we station out people on the walls... we found a lot of bows and arrows stored in the fortress..."

The leading figure from the Huo clan was a grizzled old man, his beard was white and he had multiple scars on his face. His frame was imposing and he didn't look like someone that would follow orders.

"Don't think that just because you were here first, you can order us around. The Huo clan will wait and see what this 'wave' is, then we will decide."

He scoffed at Zhang Zhi, spitting onto the ground before turning his back and walking to the side. The other fire clan members came to their leader's side, they outnumbered the Zhang clan two to one with their foundation establishment elders so they didn't really fear them.

The leading person from the Feng Clan was an amazon looking woman, her midsection was covered by armor with her legs and arms exposed letting you see her bulging muscles. The brown skin just made her veins pop out even more.

"Well if it isn't old man Tao, don't mind him. He was born constipated like that."

She laughed out in a loud voice, making a lot of people uncomfortable in the room.

"But I agree, lets put our clan members on the walls and wait for this wave."

She gave Zhang Zhi a wink while licking her lips, the man felt a shiver run through his body when the almost seven-foot-tall woman did that. Though she seemed friendly enough and ready to cooperate with their members. Soon two camps formed before the first wave, one consisted of the Zhang and Feng clan, while the Huo clan absorbed the remaining members mostly by threatening them with sheer force.

"The first wave will commence in 5...4...3...2...1..."

The robotic voice proclaimed and almost instantly the cultivators could hear rumbling in the distance.

Chapter 90

Zhang Jie and her team were standing next to some battlements looking out into the distance. The woman was using a telescope-like treasure that let her see far into the distance. There was a lot of dust getting thrown up as something approached in their direction, after a moment some shadowy outlines could be seen.

"Those look like the beasts in that corridor."

Zhang Jie said while the monster outlines changed to actual beasts. There was a swarm of centipede monsters coming at them, they were gnashing their jaws with their feelers wiggling. The beasts were running at full speed and would soon arrive close to the wall that the Zhang Clan was occupying. Due to there being two factions in this fortress at the moment, the sides of the fort were divided. The Zhang Clan and the Feng Clan occupied the north and west area along with the two towers that were placed at the north wall. The Huo clan got the south wall towers.

The monsters were only charging at the north wall at the moment, but Zhang Jie didn't feel threatened as even though there were a lot of those insect monsters coming at them, they were quite weak.

"They are far weaker than the ones we met before... Line up at the battlements, bring out your ranged weapons!"

Zhang Jie shouted to her platoon while other team leaders did the same. The cultivators didn't only have bows and crossbows that they could use for range attacks. There were various treasures that allowed the cultivators to fire off their Qi that had more penetrative power than your typical arrows.

While the junior cultivators were waiting for the seniors to give them the signal to fire, something strange happened. The ballista that was placed on one of the towers started moving on its own. Zhang Liu jumped back in fright as the siege weapon turned in the direction of the monsters and started firing large bolts. The projectiles were like small logs and the moment they connected with the advancing monsters they blew them to bits.

"This weapon is reacting to the beasts..."

Zhang Jie was there when the ballista was placed on the wall, this made her realize its use. The other siege weapon was further away on the east wall, so only this one was firing. She decided to observe it some more while also giving the order to bombard the beasts with their ranged attacks. Various projectiles rained down on the monsters along with colorful energy-based attacks that some of the cultivators fired off.

The creatures were quite weak, each hit meant a dead monster that vanished into nothingness almost instantly after collapsing to the ground. These creatures were only at the Qi condensation first and second stage, so they were nothing more than target practice for the junior members. One of the senior members would probably be able to decimate these weak monsters on his or her own if they wanted to. For now, they remained vigilant as the beast tide continued and the monsters couldn't get closer than five hundred meters outside the fortress.

The ballista weapon continued firing, releasing a large bolt every ten or so seconds. Zhang Jie noticed another peculiar thing, the ballista bolts that were next to it started vanishing. The large ammunition evaporated into nothingness after a shot was fired. Soon there was nothing left and the weapon creaked to a stop and remained motionless. This prompted the platoon leader to frown, but she had thought about something and decided to put it up to a test.

"Peng, Hong... there were similar looking bolts in one of the rooms we searched, bring as many as you can carry over here."

She gave out the order, to the two that weren't really good at range attacking in the first palace. The macho and fatty nodded and bolted to the storage room where the ammunition was placed in. There was a peculiar thing about these bolts, they couldn't be placed in storage rings. The two juniors had the largest frames from the team, so they would be able to carry more of those mini log sized bolts.

Peng was carrying a bunch of them, propping them between his forearms and head with his arms raised in the air. Hong did the same, almost tripping on the way back. After the two were back, they just dumped the ammunition in the spot that the previous stash was in. The ballista twitched the moment the items were placed next to it and resumed firing.

Zhang Jie nodded as her theory came out to be true. She instantly assigned the two to restocking the weapon, though with only one of these ballistas on the wall there wasn't really a shortage of the bolts. The weapon also had a slow firing rate, so one person would probably be enough.

The first monster wave didn't take long, ending in under an hour after the last arrow impaled a monster in the rocky ground. The robotic voice soon announced that it was over.

"First wave complete...next wave will commence in twelve hours..."

Everyone stopped and looked out into the distance. They could see the monster tracks left by the centipede many small legs along with a lot of arrows loitered around the place. Only the north wall that the Zhang clan was occupying was attacked, but every cultivator in the fortress moved to see what the commotion was about.

Soon some people were dispatched to retrieve all the ammo that could be recycled or used again. Zhang Jie returned to Zhang Zhi to give a report about the self-working weapon and the reload mechanic that it was using. All of the top brass returned to the hologram room, they wondered if there would be some way to place more of those weapons on the walls. There was a tiny problem though, the not so friendly Huo clan was also there. The Zhang clan officers deliberated if they should share their intel with the other clan, but under the order of their patriarch that said to work with the other clans, they gave in.

"You can place weapons on the fortress with this magical treasure?"

The one speaking was Huo Tao, he wondered why the other clan was sharing this information with them. Normally you would hold such information to yourself to gain an edge over your opponent, or at least trade the info for something in return.

"Oh ho ho? Shouldn't you at least show some gratitude you old fart? We are giving you precious knowledge, how about you kowtow at least five times?"

The one walking was the large amazonian woman by the name Feng Daiyu, she was lazily sitting in one of the chairs with her legs spread apart and a cup with some alcohol in her hand.

"Shut your mouth, you she-devil!"

Huo Tao went red in the face spitting out some profanities at the well-built woman, that just looked amused by the man's outburst. After a moment she stood up, moving her neck side to side her bones and muscles releasing some cracking noises in the process.

"Ha ha, Want me to give you a spanking like last time? I bet the revered Huo clan would love to see their esteemed elder eating dirt~"

The woman laughed out loud while getting closer and closer.

"You just got in a cheap shot, this time it will be different."

You could see a large vein expand on Huo Tao's forehead, his hands showing fists as he waited for the woman to get closer. Soon the two were standing right opposite each other, the woman was taller than the scarred man but he was a lot wider. His frame was muscular and imposing, but the woman didn't seem frightened at all. She was showing her pearly whites, grinning from one side to the other while the other foundation establishment people around the room got sweaty palms.

The fight was about to commence but soon the woman and man that were staring daggers at each other felt a chill run down their spines. It was like some kind of beast was staring at them, making them unable to move.

"That's enough!"

The one shouting was Zhang Zhi, after all the training and all the improvements that the Patriarch made in the techniques he was practicing, his battle prowess was second to none amongst these cultivators. The two glanced to the side, the man was giving off an oppressive aura as he was grasping the handle of his sword.

"You might not like it, but we are here together. You heard the strange voice, there will be another wave soon and I bet there will be another after that one."

He slowly got closer and closer to the two fighting peacocks, he walked between them and then towards the large glowing map in the middle as he got their attention.

"We have to assume that the monsters will get stronger with time. I'm sure you know that our clan previously took part in this expedition right?"

Zhang Zhi turned around to face the two bickering parties, his brows unmoving as he looked at the two.

"We have been here for about two weeks now... but even in the previous expedition, our elder members only started dying after a month or so...you know what this means?"

Huo Tao glanced at the man in front and rubbed his chin.

"You're saying that they arrived here just as we did... and started faltering after a month's time?"

The man wanted to blame the failure of the previous expedition on the lack of strength, but the other cultivators had to be at least competent if they managed to get through that dungeon area. That boss monster that they faced wasn't anything to scoff at. Their clan didn't really have much information about the secret ground, the sect didn't give them much and the clans that took part in it previously were mostly gone. The time it took for the people to die didn't prove much, though it could be an indication of the increasing difficulty of the task.

"What if they left this place and just perished elsewhere?"

"That could be true, but what if they didn't and the monsters attack just continued? They are weak now, but what if something like that thing appears?"

By that thing, Zhang Zhi meant the boss monster that every clan fought. You could reason that if there were things like that hidden here, they could also appear at this fortress.

"I believe that the key to this is this magical treasure."

Zhi proclaimed while moving the attention from the people gathered in this room to the large hologram map. He noticed that the points went up by 50 after the beast wave ended and he could demonstrate by placing another ballista on a tower. Tao rubbed his chin even more after witnessing the siege weapon appearing out of thin air.

"If you are willing to cooperate, we will tell you what we know."

Zhang Zhi spoke, trying to hook the others in.

"Work together..."

The Tao members knew well that even if they battled it out, the losses would be immense even if they felt that they would win in the end. It wouldn't be bad to wait for now and gather more information about this place. They could decide later if they needed to cooperate with the other cultivators, there wasn't any bad blood yet either.

"We can assist each other for now... but I want some of those weapons on our side!"

Huo Tao proclaimed and got a nod of acceptance from Zhang Zhi, Feng Daiyu just looked at the smaller man and gave him a strange look. The man gulped a bit as he had the impression that he was looking at a beast that saw him as a juicy piece of meat, she even licked her lips. Soon everyone got clued in about the points and re reloading mechanic that the siege weapons had. After some time passed the second wave was upon them, the creatures came from another side of the fortress and had an increased number and strength.

Chapter 91

Back in the jungle area, the party of four changed to five after they came across a granny hiding in a hollowed-out tree stump. As they were walking next to the stump, she had noticed her Matriarch amongst the group which prompted her to peek her head out. This almost caused Huo Qiang to punch her as the granny's face was similar looking to a goblin female.

"Wait it's me Feng Maling! Stay your hand!"

The grandma shouted out while still being stuck in her hiding place, she wouldn't be able to dodge the incoming punch if Qiang went through with it. Luckily the man jumped back, looking to Feng Liena with question marks hovering above his head.

"Ohoho, you were fine grandma?"

Feng Liena acted a bit surprised that the elderly woman made it out alive in one piece, mostly due to the old woman having a cultivation base in the core formation middle stage. The woman was good at hiding though, even Zhang Dong didn't pick her up with his enhanced senses.

Matt squinted with his eyes as he looked at the old woman, she had really wrinkled up brown skin, which looked like the type of color you got from overusing spray-on tan. She wasn't very good looking and the smudged mascara that made her look like she was crying didn't help either. He had the urge to dump some water on the woman's face and rub that mascara off but held it in.

"Why wouldn't I be alive!"

The granny managed to escape the tree stump, on which her butt got stuck after trying to squeeze out. She rolled forward and quite smoothly landed on her two feet. Matt wanted to hold up a '10' number and clap his hands, the old lady seemed to be quite nimble even for her advanced age.

Feng Liena shrugged and stuck her tongue out at her clan member, the elderly woman shook her cane at the busty Matriarch. The cane and robe that the woman was wearing, made her look like some occult wizard. Matt didn't say anything just yet, as he just looked at the two women bickering. He wasn't sure what kind of relationship the two had, but it made them look like close family by the way they were interacting with each other.

After a moment of some back and forth between the two, the woman gave out a cough and looked at the cultivators around them.

"Little Liena, I see you are traveling with the Hou clan young master... and this is..."

Feng Liena immediately jumped in, moving closer to Matt and patting him on the shoulder.

"This is little Dong, my little brother!"

Gloom filled Matt's face at the mention of his 'little' title. He thought that the granny would talk some sense into the strange Matriarch but the woman just squinted at him, her hand moving to her cane as she got closer.

"Are you sure... he...?"

Feng Liena just stuck out her overdeveloped chest and did a sideways peace sign over her eye, then stuck out her tongue in a strange pose that Matt only remembered some manga or anime characters doing back in his earth days.

"The Zhang Patriarch... could you give me a moment with the Matriarch..."

The old lady asked while the three men looked at the Feng clan members with strange expressions. Matt watched as the two moved away from the group and behind some treas, he had question signs in his eyes not knowing what this was about. He sat down on the tree stump that the old lady popped out from and strained his ears, trying to listen in on the conversation the two women were having.

"... yes, it was just like in the ancient texts..."

He could hear the two talking, it was mostly the young lady saying something about some old scriptures.

"Oh? so he carried you like in the writings of the great ancestor? "

"Yes, yes... he even..."

Matt continued eavesdropping as Feng Liena recounted their first meeting, but he had no idea what these old 'texts' or this 'great ancestor' was. Supposedly his rescue was something that those texts were describing, or prophecizing but when he tried to listen in some more as he tried to figure the situation out a booming voice next to his ear almost made him fall down from his seat.

"Hey brother, I think we shouldn't stay here too long."

The voice belonged to his new self proclaimed brother Huo Qiang, the young master had apparently taken a liking to Matt after the rescue party. After some bonding time which consisted of constant battles against various fantasy-like monsters, he started calling him brother. He even offered one of his younger siblings as a concubine to bring their clans together, though his gyaru sis didn't take to that offer kindly and he had to pull the two parties apart again.

"Ah... sure, after they are finished talking let's move out."

Matt rubbed his neck slightly before standing up, he gave up on the idea of listening in to the conversation now as it seemed to be over. The two women returned, Feng Liena beaming with a smile while the lady looked at Zhang Dong with a mixed expression.

"If it is so... I approve."

Feng Maling cupped her hands and gave a bow to Zhang Dong, the man not really knowing what this was about along with the 'approving' part.

'What are these two talking about... am I missing something here?'

The two apparently came to some kind of conclusion during their conversation, something probably related to those ancient texts. He didn't really feel like those things were important at the moment, as there were still some people missing. From the ten core formation elders, five were here and one was dead. This wasn't as bad as it looked, but considering that if he didn't arrive to save them they would probably be all dead by this point, besides the granny that knew how to hide.

They all headed out, the granny was the weakest member from the group and was more a backline attacker compared to the men in the party. They decided to keep the two ladies in the back along with mutton chops elder, that Matt forgot the actual name of and was embarrassed to ask about again.

Soon enough they spotted another casualty of the secret ground they were in. It was a mangled up corps of an unknown cultivator, which left them with three more potential survivors. They decided to rest up for the time being, no one was sure how long they were here anymore the day and night cycles kept changing. Matt managed to shoo his big sis away, for the time being, telling her that she should take care of her grandma while he cultivates for some time.

She gave him a cute pout, then repeated the same motion she did the first time he saw her on the flying ship and stormed out. He gave out a sigh and squatted down on the floor, there were a couple of machetes and axes scattered around all in various grades of the earth grade. He was slowly absorbing the scattered monster weapons from the hunted beasts, he found them to be slightly less potent for the progression of his body refining skill than the ones he was able to make himself of the same grading.

'Maybe it has something to do with how they are made... I get fewer points for slaying these monsters as well."

His progress was slow but he was at about thirty percent now, soon enough his body art would pass his regular cultivation. The time required to advance his regular cultivation technique was just too much, so this was the fastest way to get results. His body was giving off a golden sheen, it illuminated the cave that he was sitting in the people outside could feel their 'team leader' cultivating inside getting goosebumps from the strange energy fluctuations the part of the cave he was in was giving off.

Back outside Feng Liena exited the cave passage that Matt was cultivating in and headed into a different section. They had found this monster dwelling not long ago and decided to settle in for the night after clearing out the creatures inside. The busty woman walked to a separate cave room, that the granny was sitting in a lotus position. She gave out a sigh and sat not so far away from her clan member.

"Were the texts wrong... I don't think he is willing..."

The old lady opened up her eyes and replied while still sitting in her cultivation pose.

"You must not doubt the teachings of our great ancestor young Matriarch."

Feng Maling was skeptical at first, but after seeing Zhang Dong's high cultivation and how he just bulldozed through monsters that she would have trouble fighting one one one, she believed that he would be a fitting partner for this young Matriarch.

"The teachings are clear, maybe you must create a new starting point as the text proclaimed"

The baked potato announced in a wise tone and shut her eyes as she tried to rest up, her Matriarch thought about a couple of things and came to some kind of conclusion before departing, her face showing an odd determination that didn't fit her current character.

"Yes, I will create a new opportunity!"

After a couple of hours, Matt was done with absorbing the weapons. His golden skin glistened even more and he was sure that he would be able to reach the great circle soon. He hopped back to his feet and stretched out, he was a bit sweaty so he decided to wash up by the spring, which was nearby the cave they were staying in.

While he was walking through the cave corridors he felt a life signal close by, it seemed to be Feng Liena by the Qi imprint. He wasn't sure what she was up to, but she was clinging to the wall waiting for something.

'Is she waiting for me? Guess I'll act surprised?'

He was bare-chested at the moment, so he put his robes back on even though he was still sweaty. He whistled a bit to himself as he approached the corridor in which his favorite big sis was waiting for him, wondering what this was about. At the exact moment that he peeked out from around the corner, the girl came rushing at him.

She had a very cutesy way of running at this moment. Her arms were pushing into her chest, with her forearms to the side. She was waiving them around with her feet shuffling forward at an amazing pace, this made her chest bounce quite a bit, thus successfully making Matt focus his attention at the display. She was holding a piece of flattened fruit in her mouth for some reason and running right at him.

"Oh no, I will be late...Kyaaaa"

She bumped into the large bewildered man in front of her, she bounced off of him and landed on the ground with the piece of fruit flying out of her mouth. Then she just sat there, her legs bent a bit so he kind of could see the part between them. Still, there was some cloth covering the important parts, this made him swallow hard before shaking his head and finally reacting.

"Uhh...Are you alright?"

He wasn't sure what to do as he kind of instinctively reached out to help her off the ground while trying no to look at her undies. Feng Liena blushed hard as she grasped his hands back, Matt could have sworn that he saw stars in her eyes the moment he reached his hand out to her.

"Oh silly me, I didn't see you there~"

She stood up from the ground and dusted her posterior off, but before he could ask more questions she said that she was in a hurry and had to go. The man just rubbed his head and shrugged, leaving afterward to get himself cleaned in the nearby spring. While he was out, his elder sister was contemplating her next move as this was just the beginning...

Chapter 92

Matt noticed that his 'sis' was acting even weirder than usual. She kept insisting that he eat some of the food that she made, though by the looks of it it just looked like some nuts and berries she found in the forest. She even tried feeding some of those berries to him, treating him like a baby.

"Say Ahhhhhh~"

Matt evaded the feeding attempt, the woman was holding some sticks that were used as chopsticks. He started seeing a pattern in this woman's actions soon enough.

'It's as if...'

She bumped into him with some food in her mouth, she tried feeding him some homemade food, she kept falling down while trying to act all cute for some reason...

'Aren't those just bad romance manga tropes... are those the secret texts ...'

The gears in his brain started turning, this would explain why the clan women all looked like Japanese gyarus. Maybe the old 'ancestor' was someone that actually lived there, maybe due to the total worship these cultivator nuts have for their ancestors they decided to copy her looks.

'Well saving a girl from bad guys is a popular trope in novels... those two did say that the way I carried her was important too..."

He wasn't sure what this woman wanted from him before, but now he had the reason to believe that it had something to do with romance. The things she did and the way she acted sounded like stuff a manga protagonist would do, the going to school and the two leads bumping into each other was a really old one at that.

'Why do these people have to take everything at face value...'

He wasn't sure how this female clan ended up with this mindset exactly, did their 'ancestor' play some kind of prank on them, or was it some kind of weeaboo nut instead. The woman even tried luring him into peeking at her when she was taking a bath, though he didn't take the bate and just evaded that flag the other day. He started getting worried, would she move on to worse tropes, like those bipolar ones and he would end up getting assaulted whenever he glanced at the girl's cleavage.

'I need to nip this in the bud otherwise, she might end up stalking me later on... or even turning into one of those murder heroines that stab people for looking at her love target...'

He wasn't sure how he should go about this, how do you explain to a cultivator bimbo that the thing she is doing is total hogwash? Would they be seriously offended if he told them that their ancestor was an idiot? Or that they just found her manga stash and interpreted it wrongly... maybe he could go with that angle.

'Ugh... I still hate talking to people...'

He groaned and palmed his face, contemplating on the bs that he should tell these two Feng clan members, would probably talk to the two at once otherwise they might talk themselves into some nonsense later when he isn't around. He found the two going through some large leaves, the elderly lady was pushing vines through it, it made the large leaf look like a green apron. The younger girl with the healthy tan was looking at some coconuts, Matt didn't really know where she got those from or what she needed them for either.

Matt loudly caught into his hand to get the two ladies attention.

"Could I have a word with you two, it's about your Ancestor and those ancient texts..."

The two women looked at each other, their brows furrowing as they stopped doing their preparations. The two just nodded at Zhang Dong and followed them into the cave, somewhere where the two Huo clan members couldn't hear them. The two then looked at the white-haired cultivator, that was standing to them with his back and looking slightly upwards, his hand resting on his chin.

"I overheard your previous conversation about your ancestor, Firstly, I have to apologize for eavesdropping on you two. Secondly, I think you are interpreting the teachings of the senior wrongly..."

He didn't want to talk while facing the two for two reasons, one he looked more mysterious that way and two he was bad at keeping eye contact and he might break character if they stared him down too much. The tranquil will technique didn't do much for his sweaty palms. First to speak out was the granny, giving off a somewhat grumpy and annoyed tone.

"You dare? How did our Feng clan wrongly interpret the teachings of old, the old texts have been passed down through generations, they have been throughout studied by the previous Matriarchs, are you saying that they were all wrong? Do you even know what the old texts are?"

The granny started getting quite angry, this man was saying that the old seniors were wrong. That they somehow translated the texts wrongly. She wasn't even sure if this man knew what the secret texts were, there was nothing like it in this world so she was skeptical of his knowledge, but then he spoke up.

"You might refer to the ancient texts as texts... but in reality, they are mostly drawings... with the writing portion placed in white bubbles of sorts... aren't they?"

The Zhang Clan Patriarch cut her off

The woman stopped, Feng Liena also looked curious. The ancient writings were in manga form, this form of art was something foreign in this kind of world setting, thus the two women were quite surprised as the man talked even more.

"Is it mostly about young teenage girls and boys, the girls wearing short skirts, everyone wearing a uniform and they seem to go to some kind of place of teaching where they spend time in a group between twenty and thirty, everyone having a desk..."

Matt wasn't doing much besides describing the usual high school setting that most of those manga's had. The uniforms varied but the school remained the same, there would always be some recurring things that he could mention while keeping the rest vaguer as he had no idea about the core characters in this story, but he was sure that the female lead was a gyaru.

"How could you know that... did you sneak into our clan and steal out secret writings!?"

The woman's eyes were turning bloodshot, even Feng Liena was looking strangely at Matt that didn't like where this was going.

"Nothing of the sorts, I've just come across similar secret writings in my travels, so I just thought I could offer you some insight into your own."

The two women looked at each other, Feng Liena nodded and replied in an uncharacteristic mild tone.

"Please continue."

Matt swallowed hard as this would be the point in which he had to explain everything to them.

"I also came in contact with similar secret writings, in it, there was a certain youth he was carrying a strange rectangle bag in his hand and rushing to the stated place where the was tough by his elders..."

"I wondered why the ancient elders created it, was there some kind of secret technique buried in the teachings? I wondered and then also tried following the instructions, but then I realized that it was mistaken!"

He grasped his fist tightly, looking at it for more dramatic effect.

"The seniors didn't want me to follow the secret texts literally, it was all a test! In reality, they wanted me to follow my own path. Pave it with my own two hands and awaken the greater Dao that slumbered in me..."

He moved his hands apart, the greater Dao of lightning radiating from his being as the two women gasped.

"So you see, I think your ancestor wanted someone from your clan to create their own way. Following into the footsteps of your seniors is a noble cause, but only when you follow your own Dao the real path will lay in front of you."

He wasn't sure what he was rumbling about, but the two women had strange solemn expressions on their faces. Was it working? He wasn't sure, but he at least hoped that Feng Liena would stop bothering him with her silly antics.

"Well, this is all that I wanted to discuss, maybe if you pave your own path you might awaken the greater Dao of wind, instead of using those derived techniques that you are cultivating at the moment..."

He quickly left the room, leaving them with some vague explanations hoping for the best, well at least it couldn't get any worse than this, right? Feng Liena stopped interfering with his affairs after that, mostly hanging out in the back with a complex expression on her face.

Later that day Matt relaxed and thought to himself about his surroundings and this secret ground. He had gotten used to life in this strange jungle, the monsters capped out at the late stage so he didn't have any problems with those. He was even able to defeat people of that level when he was at the middle stage mostly with ease. Time went by and they kept exploring, they even started drawing up a map on one large leaf so that they could keep track of the places they visited. They had to do this, as this place was highly disorienting and huge in scope.

Soon enough they came across the last survivors, though they wouldn't last for long as they were tightly bound up in spider webs. If it wasn't for Matt's aura detection capabilities he would probably think that the people inside those cocoons were already dead, but he could clearly feel life force radiating from them, though it was quite dim.

The young fire lord wanted to jump right in and trash those monsters, but due to the fiery nature of his attacks, they had to change plans. The webs were highly flammable, so one wrongly placed fire uppercut could incinerate the cultivators that were paralyzed in the spider webs. There were quite a few of those human-sized spiders up in the trees, the webs were spun all around them and one false move would alert those monsters.

Huo Qiang wasn't out of the loop though, it would be a waste to not use his skills that were clearly the bane of these spiders. They only needed to get the people out of there first. The plan was quite easy, the three men would distract the monster spiders first while the women snuck up to where the captives were.

It didn't take much to set off these creatures, as the moment they poked some of those webs and made some noises they appeared from the treetops. They were spitting venom at them, wiggling their spider legs in various directions as they came at the trio. Spiders always gave Matt the creeps, there was something deep down that made him fear that form even back on earth. This made him fight at a distance, firing off multiple Qi filled sword strikes that sliced and diced the large arachnids to pieces.

Zhang Dong didn't notice the looks the two men were giving him as they looked at his swordsmanship. The man himself got all of his skills thanks to the system so he didn't think anything of it but to the two the superb mastery of the art was mind-boggling. This man was about thirty years old and he had already mastered sword intent.

The system had a strange way of inserting the knowledge into his brain. It was as if an old pro boxer picking up some boxing gloves and throwing a couple of punches after years of rest. The knowledge and skill were there, but it took some time for all of it to come back to him. The techniques that he bought came with the required knowledge to perform them, the sword arts had a requirement of sword intent so after practicing for some time he naturally was able to use it.

This sword intent was the most basic one, but even then he would probably have some large sword sects trying to recruit him as a disciple if they knew that he was able to do that at such a young age. Matt knew that his fighting strength increased by quite a bit when he was wielding his sword, but he didn't really correlate it to the sword intent that let him chop up his enemies mostly in one clean cleave.

Soon granny baked potato sneaked up to where the cultivators were being held captive, she had quite a nifty technique to fade into the surroundings. Thanks to this she was able to cut up the web that the two were hanging from with the help of Feng Liena. They carried the two to safety while the men unleashed on the monsters. Huo Qiang unleashed his fiery wrath, setting everything ablaze around himself, the screams of the spider monsters could be heard almost instantly.

The spider webs were even more flammable then expected, thus the trees they were connected to them were quickly burning with them. The forest fire continued to burn, the spider creatures scattered escaping the flames the group of cultivators didn't give chase as the reason for the attack were the two wrapped up people.

After they brought them to a safer location they removed the white outer shell and saw two pale-looking men inside. Their veins were bulging out slightly from spots where the spiders injected venom into them. The elderly lady was handy for such occasions as she had extensive knowledge about healing. She found out that the two males were only paralyzed and should recover within the next 24 hours. The two were wearing a different kind of robe, making Matt think that they weren't from the same clan or party. Both of them looked to be in their late fifties with a cultivation level in the core formation middle stage.

Chapter 93

The two men regained their consciousness, they were indeed from two separate factions and one even mentioned that his clan brother had been slain by some other monsters not long ago. This brought the number of core formation elders up to seven, three had passed away in the jungle filled with game monsters.

The first man had a full beard and black hair, his stature was average the same as his height. His hair was all over the place, the days in the jungle weren't kind to this man as he looked a bit sickly probably some side effects from the spider venom. The second gentleman looked like a Shaolin monk. He had six dots on his forehead and a long white beard that went to about his navel, he was even wearing large round beads around his neck.

The first man's name was from a clan called the Kwok clan, and the baldy wasn't from a clan at all but instead from some kind of small Buddhist sect. It was quite a low-level sect, core formation cultivators were the strongest warriors that they possessed. The name of the sect was Tranquil Lotus Sect and it was also participating in this expedition to earn some resources and favor with the dark palm sect.

Matt's attention moved to the dark-haired elder though, he was grasping his hair tightly, eyes bulging out and red, his brows furrowed.

"Blasted Dark Palm Sect, they lied to us... we are doomed..."

He kept holding onto his head and trembling, he was seemingly in shock as he kept mumbling to himself and not really paying attention to the group that had rescued him. He was firmly slapped into shape by the Huo clan young master, that was getting annoyed by how he didn't even thank them for the rescue.

"What are you mumbling about you old fart, get a hold of yourself, what is this about the dark palm sect?"

The man looked up at the crimson-haired man, then at the other people that were staring at him as he let out an uncomfortable sounding laugh.

"Ah ha ha, don't you understand... they played us all... there will be no reward... there is no treasure, we will all die here..."

Everyone looked at him suspiciously, the man knew something that they didn't.

"Oh, why would you say such a thing?"

Matt chimed in moving closer, as he was afraid that his new brother would do something drastic to the man that lost his marbles. The man just looked at him and took out some kind of jade, it looked like some kind of more advanced communication jade but it was a bit cracked. He threw it on the ground and started talking, even without the other people having to ask.

"The Sect contacted us a couple of months ago, they mentioned this forsaken place and promised treasures and riches if we took this communication jade with us and reported what was in the secret ground to them."

"We didn't think much of it, we only thought that we would go in and leave. They must have blocked most of the information about this place, we just assumed the previous people were incompetent..."

The man slumped onto his knees, clearly not thinking that he could get out of this alive.

"But there hasn't been any word from outside and these monsters just keep coming, they never stop."

Matt placed his hand on the man's shoulder thanks to his tranquil will he was able to somewhat calm other people down. The calming feeling washed over the nervous cultivator, that slowly started to calm himself down.

"Calm down, Everyone knows that we were probably sent here as some kind of experiment, but if we stay together we still stand a chance."

Kwok Xun looked up at the man that had a strange positive outlook on things, he could feel that the cultivator was quite powerful, probably being in the great circle of core formation but he wasn't quite sure. He wanted to believe him, but after having spend weeks running away and battling strange monsters he was just tired.

"You should listen to brother Dong, but we can also just leave you here if you are going to be a hindrance."

Huo Qiang chimed in, Matt's brows furrowing as he started threatening the dude that had PTSD. Though it showed some effects as after calming down, the man went red in the face with rage and jumped up.

"Me? a hindrance?"

He glared at the younger crimson-haired man, who was just grinning back not really caring one way or the other. In his opinion it would probably be better to just leave this guy here, why would they need someone that was a coward? Though when he looked at Zhang Dong, looking for approval he found the man staring daggers at him which made his smile turn upsidedown.

'What are you doing you meat for brains, I even managed to calm him down and you riled him up again.'

"I'm sure you were through a lot, but so were all of us, before brother Dong came and rescued us all."

Feng Liena moved in, she was carrying herself a bit differently than usual. Matt expected her to threaten the guy, or even try to give him a couple of smacks. Instead, she was quite calm, she was talking softly while keeping eye contact and with a gentle smile on her face. Was this her normal character when she dropped the female lead act? She also called him brother without the little part, which was a sign of progress.

While the tanned beauty was talking, he glanced to the baldy on the side. The man was remaining silent while sitting down, he was clearly in a cultivation position and by the Qi signature, he was trying to heal his wounds. When he noticed Matt's gaze on him, he just nodded while clasping his hands, probably just his way of saying thank you.

Kwok Xun looked at the lady, then back to Huo Qiang who turned his face to the side, seemingly embarrassed when the woman mentioned that he was rescued by Zhang Dong as well. The man let out a long sight before nodding and turning to Matt, he made a decision.

"Well, if you are willing I will accompany you."

The man proclaimed while thinking that he didn't have any other choice if he wanted to survive.

The group got reorganized, they had seven members now which meant that the overall battle strength had increased. Matt wasn't sure how to arrange the group this time around, but he decided to put the girls in the middle, the two new arrivals were in the back with mutton chops elder and he and Qiang were in the front.

They tracked along and finally, they spotted a change of scenery. There were two massive mountain ranges to the side, going straight up into the clouds. This mountain range formed a path of some sort as the path to the sides was blocked by them and the path forward was getting narrower with each step. It looked like the secret ground wanted them to move between these two mountains soon enough they figured out why.

There was a clearing, in that clearing stood a massive monster. It looked somewhat like a snake but it had two large legs protruding from the front part and the middle body part was a lot thicker than the rear tail part, it also had two serpent heads. They were a bit away from the thing that looked like the guardian of this area, behind it was a large gate embedded into bedrock.

"I bet the next area is past that gate... we either have to beat this monster of sneak past it?"

The group looked at the monster while thinking about possible ways of getting through. Matt didn't think sneaking was an option, the gate would probably only open after the monster was slain and busting through it would probably be more difficult than killing the boss that was guarding it.

Netherserpent [ Core formation late stage ]

'Hm, only in the late stage?'

Matt thought that a final boss would be stronger than the minibosses like the goblin chieftain he came upon in the jungle.

'Maybe the jungle part is harder than the actual boss?'

The thing was just standing there, probably waiting for trespassers to get into its domain. The party of cultivators was eager to move on, they spent many weeks in that godforsaken jungle and just wanted to get out of here. Matt couldn't really see any problems in attacking this monster as it didn't pose much of a threat so he decided to move forward along with the strongest members of his party to back him up.

Firing of range attacks was still not working out so the warriors had to get close and personal. The moment they got into what the monster deemed as its territory, it gave off a loud roar. It thumped with it two huge legs making the ground shake, but instead of running towards them it opened up that large snake-like mouth.

Everyone was a seasoned fighter so they knew what the monster was doing, part of them dodged to the left while some to the right as the breath attack was fired off by the green beast. One snakehead was breathing regular crimson fire, while the other was blue in hue turning the ground to ice the moment it connected.

"Can you get its attention?" Matt shouted out.

"Leave it to us, brother Dong!" Huo Qiang replied as he moved in closer towards one of the heads along with his retainer.

Feng Liena moved over to the other head with the other cultivators, pelting it with weakened ranged attacks the serpent head snapping angrily at them as they came closer.

It didn't take long for Zhang Dong to move closer, he waited for the monster to fire off its breath attack at his party members. Soon the time came, sword Qi formed around his longsword that gave out a humming noise as if it was resonating with his energies. Just as the left head closed its mouth, moving slightly upwards to charge its attack up he moved in. He stacked his condensation and avatar form onto each other for a speed an power boost, vanishing from everyone's sight for a fraction of a second and appearing behind the monster head that he was aiming at, the sword already having drawn blood.

The monster's head flew up into the air and flopped onto the ground, green blood gushing like a geyser from the stump. The monster's remaining head quickly looked at the giant wound, eyes all read as it looked at the person that delivered the blow. The man in question only looked at it, a smile on his face.

"Shouldn't you really be looking at me?"

The monster, of course, didn't reply as it was getting ready to burn the puny human with its fire breath but before it could do that if felt something coming from behind. When it turned around, it saw a fist clad in fire coming right for it the creature couldn't react and got sucker-punched right on the chin. It fell backward, its lower jaw popping out if the joint and just flopping against its elongated neck in a gruesome fashion.

Matt didn't really need to do much now, the other cultivators overwhelmed the monster with sheer numbers. It couldn't use its mouth anymore or use its breathing skill either. The serpent quickly turned into a punching bag, the ending came after Liena managed to decapitate the remaining head with the help of her battle fans.

The heads remained on the ground, the monster was slain and unmoving.

"Haha, there still might be hope."

Kwok Xun declared while giving one of the giant heads a kick. But Matt was still remaining vigilant, the large gate wasn't opening and he couldn't really tell if the monster was really dead. He should have delivered the last hit, then he would know when the system gave him a prompt but now he could only wait and see.

Suddenly he felt something and quickly shouted.

"No... get back!"

Kwok Xun turned to Zhang Dong who was charging towards him, not knowing why. But when he turned to the head that he just kicked he saw something bursting out from it. He didn't have enough time to react, only being able to watch as a metallic glint was swiping towards his neck. He then heard a sound of metal colliding with metal as Matt intercepted the attack that came for the cultivator's neck.

What was standing there was a human-sized snake man, holding two large sabers and locked in a battle of strength with Zhang Dong. The smaller monster somehow jumped out from the cut of head of the previous slain beast. The same happened with the other severed head, the two snake men were both giving of different auras, one of fire while the second of ice.

"I'll handle this one, go help the others with the other one..."

Matt managed to push the creature back, he already noticed that it was a lot faster and more diverse with its attacks than the regular Netherserpent. Luckily the remaining body didn't seem like it would be turning into more monsters. These two were just slightly stronger than the larger beast and the surprise tactic would only work once, the peculiar thing about these two creatures was that no matter how much they stabbed and maimed them they just wouldn't die.

If they chopped off its head again, it would just grow back instantly. The wounds on its body regenerated at an astonishing pace, the cultivators were slowly losing their stamina and Qi during the prolonged fight.

'Are these creatures immortal? How do we beat them?'

Then an idea popped into Matt's head as he moved. He sliced off both of his hands and legs, slamming it down to the ground, his foot placed on the monster's chest as he held it down on the ground.

"Hey, quickly cut off the head of the one you are fighting!"

Matt shouted at the other cultivators, that didn't think cutting its head would do anything but the team leader was saying it so they had to try. The moment the decapitation happened, Matt sprung into action. He cleaved downwards on the thrashing monster that was regenerating its limbs, being sure to decapitate it at the same time as the others did the other beast.

Just as planned the moment the two heads rolled onto the ground, the monster's bodies started shaking. There was no regeneration anymore, the fight was over as the bodies dissolved into nothingness leaving only the sabers behind.

"Finally..."

The large gates started creaking open and the cultivators could finally see what awaited them behind them. What it was, was a world filled with lava and a giant castle in the distance.

Chapter 94

The large gate-like door slammed itself open, the moment that happened you could feel the change in heat as the warm air started surging from the created opening. Matt didn't receive any points for slaying one of the snake-men, maybe it was the system acting up or maybe the thing they were fighting wasn't considered a normal beast.

"Hoh..."

Everyone's mouths opened wide as they saw a narrow path in front of them, there was lava coming out from the sides and dropping down into what looked to be a giant lake below. The path in front of them went on for a while, bending a couple of times before you could see a giant castle-like structure in the distance. This time around, there was a clear path towards the next destination the lava was everywhere so they couldn't really go anywhere besides forward.

Before they moved onwards Matt looked at the large sabers that the creatures dropped, they were quite high quality and there were four of them. Though he picked up the two that the monster he was fighting had on it, the other two were picked up by his companions. He was about half done into the great circle with his body refining technique by now, these two weapons would probably add quite a bit. Even more, if he got four of them, but the items were already gaining new owners.

The mutton chop elder took one, while the other one got snatched by the new guy. He was thinking about getting them to cough those items up, but on second thought the new guy lost his weapon on the way and the Huo clan member earned his keep already. He would probably have a hard time beating the previous boss if he was alone, you have to share the loot some times, he thought to himself. He wanted to propose a short break so he could absorb the weapons, but the door started slowly closing itself.

"Damn... will those monsters revive or will this entrance be blocked for now..."

They had to make a decision, there could be other places like this that they could enter or they could be lost in the jungle for eternity. Matt didn't feel like he wanted to gamble on that so everyone rushed inside the lava chamber.

"I---it's' hot..."

Feng Liana aired her robe a bit, sweat running down her neck and making her cleavage glisten in the red light. Everyone felt that this place was really stuffy, the two Huo clan members weren't as uncomfortable as the rest though.

"Hah, this heat is nothing!"

Huo Qiang proclaimed as he strode inside with large strides. Matt's body refining skill was keeping him safe from the heat, but he wasn't sure about the rest.

"I think we shouldn't linger here, that castle over there isn't that far, let's go there just stay vigilant, we have no idea if more beasts are going to show up while we are crossing."

They were in a disadvantageous position, the path was about ten meters wide but the drop-down was close to one kilometer. Even if they survived the drop, the burning hot lava would probably burn them to a crisp.

This was closed off space, the door slammed itself shut behind them soon after they entered. There was clearly a ceiling with many sharp stalactites coming out of it. The walls around them had openings throughout which lava was rushing down, filling up the flaming hot river below them that run on both sides of the bridge they were walking on.

They were about halfway through without anything coming out to bother them. The large castle started getting closer and they could now clearly see what it was. It was situated on an island surrounded by a lava lake, the path they were on was leading towards the gate. It was quite sharp looking with many pointy towers coming out from the structure with the middle one being the largest of them.

They weren't able to digest its looks as the moment they passed the halfway mark something started rumbling. They could feel the rocky bridge shaking below them, something was clearly wrong.

"Oh no, the bridge is collapsing"

Feng Maling shouted as she pointed behind them, in the distance from where they came from the bridge was collapsing. Sections of it just started crumbling and falling into the lava river below them. Everyone started running with all their might, quickly going towards the ominous-looking structure on the island.

Matt looked back and could see one of the cultivators falling behind the others, it was the baked potato of a lady that was huffing and puffing, clearly running wasn't her strong suit. Being the gentleman that he was he stopped and backtracked, he grabbed the woman like a sack of potatoes over his shoulder and bolted for the fort in the distance now having to catch up to the rest of the cultivators.

"Ahh... Zhang Patriarch, you have my gratitude!"

"Don't talk or you might bite your tongue, I'm going to increase my speed..."

Matt replied while gathering spiritual energy in his legs, his feet made deep indents in the rocky ground as he pushed off with long strides quickly catching up to the remaining running cultivators with granny in tow. The whole place was shaking and crumbling, but everyone managed to make it the last one being the monk-like character whose sweaty head looked like a shiny marble.

"Sabbe satta dukkha pamuccantu..."

He took off his beads and started doing some chants, a holy aura surrounded his being as it washed away his anxiety. The people had unwillingly charged into the large castle-like structure, the gate was open but the bridge leading up to it had crumbled as the rest.

"At least this place isn't crumbling..."

Matt noted while he placed the granny that he was carrying back on the ground. The woman was blushing a little bit, but he couldn't really tell due to her dark complexion.

Feng Liena run-up to the two, her finger pointing up as if she wanted to say something but stopping mid-sentence.

"Ah... uh ... thank you for your help brother Dong, granny isn't the youngest anymore..."

He wasn't sure why the woman was having a hard time talking now, guess the previous conversation was showing some effects as she wasn't acting all hyperactive anymore. Matt just smiled at the woman and nodded.

"No problem, you can count on me!"

He replied while looking at the girl, she, in turn, covered her mouth and giggled a little bit.

"He he, brother Dong is really reliable."

The reply came with a cute smile, which made Matt stare slightly.

'What's with this comfortable atmosphere all of a sudden?'

He just nodded and tried steering the conversation away from himself and to the lair of potential monsters they were in. He couldn't feel any life signals for now, but a monster could just be summoned out of thin air here so they have to be warry of their surrounding.

"How about we check this place out, don't stray too far away from the group though we don't know if there are any more beasts here."

Huo Qiang's retainer chimed in while holding onto his new saber weapon. He looked like he was eager to chop someone up with that thing. There wasn't much inside the structure, the area looked deserted. The structures around here looked old and shabby, there was dust everywhere and no sign of life anywhere. In the middle of the castle-fort stood a giant spire-like tower, there was a large door there with a peculiar familiar writing.

'Those who enter here abandon all hope."

The door had a palm drawn on it, probably something used to activate the opening mechanism so, for now, he told everyone to not go near it. This was also a tower structure, so there would probably be some levels with increasing difficulty.

"I think the next part is behind that door in the middle, I propose we rest and recover our Qi for now and then try opening it. We might not have time to do that later."

Matt proposed, wanting to absorb those two weapons that he got and it was also good to take a breather for the other people. No one had anything against that, the cultivators already gave up the motion of working separately here there were just too many strange things around for one or two people to handle.

Everyone scattered to their own corner to prepare for the next battle, but before Matt could start absorbing those weapons the more friendly version of the Feng Matriarch came over to chat with him again.

"Could I have a moment~?"

She said in a cheery voice, Matt just stood up from his lotus position not really having a place to sit down comfortably for a chat so the two just stood there opposite each other.

"Sure, how can I help sister Liena"

Guess he could drop the big sis part and just go with how peers talked to each other in this world. They were both in a Patriarchal position in similar clans.

"Could we talk about the ancestral scriptures?"

Matt gulped a bit, not really wanting to talk about those as he wasn't really sure how those people interpreted those manga panels like that.

"You see, the texts were incomplete but they were supposed to guide us on the path of Dao..."

Leliana asked while sitting on a more well-kept piece of the castle wall.

"Um, well the texts that I saw were similar to yours. It's not like everything that's in the secret scriptures is false, you just need to look into them on your own... and pick out the truths."

Matt replied while trying not to show his sweaty palms, arms behind his back as he stood straight up hoping the woman would buy his response.

"Oh, truths..."

Liena looked to the distance, appearing like she was thinking about something for a moment, uncomfortable silence filling the surrounding which prompted Matt to speak up.

"F-for instance... your lovely darkened complexion, It's a lot better than the pale one most female cultivators stand by... like you get a lot more vitamin D3 ... it's good for your health and will progress your Dao further..."

Matt kind of trailed off at the end, his voice getting fainter as he wasn't sure what he was even talking about.

'Why are you talking about vitamin D3, you dumbass!'

"Vitah-min Dee Tree?"

'Does he mean that I need to be steadfast as an unmoving tree... or bend like a slim tree that survives even great cyclones. Is that the name of some kind of secret technique... D-did he say I had a lovely complexion?'

Feng Liena thought to herself, while Zhang Dong wanted to hit his head on the nearby wall.

"Tee hee~, you sure have a way with words brother Dong. Maybe the texts weren't all that wrong, I'll have to examine them once more when we return."

She looked at him while covering her mouth with her sleeve, she then walked away after excusing herself with a proper bow. Matt wasn't sure what the cultivator woman took out from his nonsense response, but at least she looked happy when she was going away. After the coast was clear, he gave out a sigh and went back to cultivating managing to absorb the two weapons within the hour. His body refining progress jumped up by ten percent, these last boss weapons were a lot better than the ones he found along the way in the jungle.

'Guess it's time to check that tower out... will it be that hell motive... think limbo came first...'

Everyone gathered up in front of the large locked door. Matt nodded as they decided that one of the weaker members would try to place their palm on the door. They didn't want their strongest members to activate any traps as they needed them for fighting. The monk volunteered for this and after placing his palm on the door they heard gears moving as it opened up.

The moment the door opened a peculiar sweet fragrance hit their noses, Matt covered his mouth and churned his cultivations to stop the fragrance from going further into his body, not knowing if it was poisonous or not. Then they entered inside, the inside looked quite high class. It was only a short hall at first and another door inside, they tried opening it but it wouldn't budge probably because not everyone from the group had entered through the door just yet.

"Okay let's go then..."

The door shut itself behind them, the red carpet on the wooden floor guided them forward as the previously shut door finally opened. Inside it looked like a ballroom, many crystal chandeliers lit it up and there were some people dancing inside. Matt narrowed his eyes, the people were wearing fancy dresses but there was something peculiar about them, they had horns and thin black tails

Incubus [Core formation middle level]

Succubus [Core formation middle level]

They were dancing in pairs around a certain woman. The woman had larger horns and a larger tail, her eyes were glowing in a red hue. She was wearing something that looked like a Victorian-era dress, with a lot of space to see her ample cleavage, that corset was doing wonders for it.

The Sin of Lust [ Core formation Late Stage+(Half Step Great Circle) ]

'Wait, never saw that plus sign before... Sin of Lust? did they mix up the genres?'

Matt was expecting the nine levels of hell, but it looked like he would be getting the seven deadly sins instead.

Chapter 95

Matt eyed the lady standing in the middle, she had a demonic air around her. She was looking straight at them, there was an alluring smile on her face. The other people in the room were dancing to the old fashioned music in the rather large hall, Matt wasn't sure what this was about but before he could think about it more, one of his party members moved forward.

"Hoho... what a beauty!"

It was Huo Qiang, he had a strange look in his eyes while staring at the alluring woman in the victorian ere dress. Matt took the time to look at his horny brother's status, he was even starting to drool while staring at the busty succubus.

Huo Qiang [ Core formation late stage ] ( Charmed )

He thought that he had managed to pass the will or fortitude check, he wasn't sure himself as he didn't really play those kinds of games back in his day. Besides the hornball that had close to a hundred concubines, the member from the Kwok clan was starting to pant the monk was chanting as some kind of energy shield formed around him giving off a golden light. Qiang's retainer was somehow holding up, but he was shaking a bit as well the women in the group seemed unaffected.

"We shall not fall under your demonic plot, foul demon!"

The monk proclaimed as the golden light surrounding his body burst forward encompassing the whole group. Matt could see the charmed status vanish after the shield formed around them, Qiang staggered forward while rubbing his head not really sure what was going on.

"Huh? What was I doing?"

"Well, I think you almost went and proclaimed your undying love to that demon lady over there"

Matt replied to Qiang's question while pointing at the Sin of lust, after the monk formed the protective shield the woman's seductive gaze turned to one of rage. The music stopped and every succubus and incubus in the room looked at them.

"Insolent creatures!"

The horned lady shouted out as her body got surrounded in a shadowy aura, covering her whole body and only leaving the face out in the open. The aura looked like gray liquid and it moved around her limbs quickly switching to a darker and sinister coloring. The reason for it was soon revealed as the clothing that the demonic woman was wearing switched from a classy lady dress to something out of a bondage dungeon.

Matt gulped as he heard the loud whip cracking, the woman's high heels clicked on the floor as she moved slightly forward. She was wearing a skin-tight black latex suit, with a window to display her tightly squeezed bosom.

"Watch out, they have some kind of ability that deludes your mind, you might attack others around you if you aren't careful."

Zhang Dong shouted it out while pulling out his longsword, he moved forward he wasn't affected by the charm debuff so he could go out of the shield and fight it out with the demonic woman. Though there were quite a lot of those lower monsters to clean up too, would be difficult if he had to face them on his own. But luckily he wasn't alone and one of his party members had just the thing for this occasion.

"Everyone, take a talisman it will protect you from the demonic influence!"

The monk was coming in handy, he had carved out some talismans from some leaves that he plucked from the forest area. Thank's to his foresight everyone in the group was able to attach an evil repealing talisman that would temporarily shield them. How much those would hold out was unknown, but it was probably better than having them remain in that small golden shield while he got whipped around by the angry-looking horned lady.

The first stage of the tower was turning out to just be a boss area, there were around fifty of those dancing demons. Their clothes were also transforming to look more latexy getups. What was different about their apparel was that they had their faces covered, looking like gimps with spikes attached in various places. The men of the group were quite shocking, having a large metal spike right between their legs which made Feng Liena look away in disgust.

When the battle started the Sin of lust gave out a shrill scream, shattering all of the crystal chandeliers in the area. She gave her own followers a couple of good whips with her weapon, the creatures screaming out in ecstasy as the pain washed over their backs.

"Kill them all my lovelies, make your Mistress proud and you might get rewarded~"

The gimp army charged out, everyone looked invigorated at the mention of a reward from their Mistress. Matt wasn't sure who designed this place, but he wanted to give him a couple of smacks. They were outnumbered by quite a bit, but luckily the boss of the area decided to use her minions first while sitting back in a throne. Her legs were crossed over one another and resting on the back of one of her minions, the high heels were digging into the incubus' back and drawing blood, but the person in question looked quite ecstatic.

'Should I engage the boss alone or should I help the others and whittle them down with them...'

He wasn't sure if the people behind him could handle the assault of the gimp troop. He wanted to believe in them though, during the jungle part they showed to be capable and there was even the monk with good anti demonic abilities.

"Can I trust you with those creatures' minions?"

He asked the other cultivators, the boss wasn't all that strong judging by the system message but if they truly thought that they needed his help he would play it safe.

"Fear not brother Dong, we will handle these trash demons, go and give that bitch a good thrashing!"

Huo Qiang spat on the floor as he got to the bitch part, he looked quite angry due to the fact that he got charmed before.

"Leave it to us, young Patriarch."

Replied the old lady, while already gathering wind energy into her staff.

"That's reassuring."

He gave the people a smile then turned around, looking at the charging monsters. Some of them were running on their hands and feet, some were clawing their way onto the walls and ceiling as they tried to surround the group from all sides. Matt ignored them as he pushed his Qi into his legs again, he used his body as a battering ram and with a thumping sound took off running.

The wooden floor burst open the moment he charged forward, the monsters tried to block his advanced but they just lost their limbs in the process. He burst through the small wall of latex-clad people and aimed his sword at the sitting seductress, but just as he was about to strike her down, his sword encountered a hidden barrier.

"Ufufu~ What's the rush little piggy? Why don't you play with my lovelies first~?"

He smashed his fist into the barrier but to no avail and then jumped back as one of the incubus men tried swiping at him with a clawed hand. The monsters around here looked like beings from a fetish video, they had hooks going into their flesh that was getting pulled apart. Some of those hooks were in their eyes or in their mouth as well, they truly looked grotesque.

'Guess I have to clear out those guys first...'

While Matt was battling the hellish guards his cultivator friends were doing their best as well. The monsters were quite strong all things considered, but luckily they were attacking without any tactics just rushing in blindly. They were still at a disadvantage though, they were outnumbered and there wasn't really any place to run. The hall was quite large, about the size of a football field but even though there were windows to the sides they were indestructible.

They found that out the moment they tried flinging one of the monsters outside. They expected the glass to shatter but instead, the gimp's head burst like a tomato after it made contact with the transparent material. This was clearly a sealed-off space, either they would kill the monster or they would die instead.

Matt looked back while smacking a monster to the side with a well-placed kick, shattering its body in half while electrocuting it at the same time. The others were holding out, the Feng clan members were good at blasting the gimp rush back while the Huo clan members were quite adept at setting them ablaze. The new sabers were showing promise already, as many heads were rolling around on the hall floor.

"Enough!"

The woman on the throne shouted just as Matt managed to slay the last one of her guards, the barrier vanished and she strode forward. Her hips swayed side to side, but that wasn't all that was swaying with them. At this point, Matt was mostly immune to womanly charms as those so he just gripped his longsword and defended himself as the woman's fingernails extended and she tried to tear his face apart.

"Who are you... you're the first one that can actually talk..."

Matt asked while evading a couple of high heel kicks to the face and groin area, the latter attack made him sway backward while sweating.

"Silence pig, you could have had a pleasurable demise, but now you will only suffer!"

She clearly didn't want to talk, or couldn't if she was actually a real person with a mind was still up to debate. Matt wanted to pry some answers from her, maybe she would be more willing to talk if he cut off an arm or two...

His eyes started glowing in bright blue light, electricity forming around him as he got more serious. He activated his body refining skill, perceiving the surroundings in slow motion. Soon the attacks rained down, the monster woman was quite fast and the whipping attacks were quite hard to read, but soon enough she found herself with her weapon arm missing after Zhang Dong got a good shot in.

"YOU INSIGNIFICANT PIG!"

She looked quite mad, her body started executing a terrifying aura as it glowed in purple light. The next attack was a lot harder to receive as Zhang Dong found himself getting pushed back, instead of the whip the Sin of lust used her remaining arm and legs raining down a barrage close-ranged blows.

'She suddenly powered up... similar to when a boss monster loses half of its HP and goes into a second form or changes its attacking pattern.'

She was quite fast and strong, but still, she wasn't in the great circle stage while Matt was content on fighting experts at that level without a problem at this point. Soon enough the monster's head was flying through the air, the only injury he suffered was a rip to his clothes and some cut hair while he was dodging, maybe a shorter haircut was due.

The moment the monster was slain the remaining mobs disintegrated into colorful lights. The cultivators behind him gave off a sigh of relief as they also managed to survive the predicament with minor injuries.

"Congratulations on passing the first floor, you may now proceed to the library, the next floor will open in exactly 24 hours."

The voice sounded quite robotic, like something a text to speech app would sound like. A new door appeared out of nowhere with a sign ' Library first level' the cultivators that he was with were bewildered by the strange voice, but Matt kind of knew what it was about.

'This is probably some kind of resting area between the levels, might also be a safe zone.'

"I think we should go inside not like there is anything left in this room for us."

The monsters had vanished and there were no weapons left for him to take with him, after some deliberation everyone headed through the door to the so-called library. What greeted them were books, scrolls, and manuscripts, quite a load of them.

Chapter 96

The door behind them vanished after everyone passed through it. The group found themselves in a corridor at first, torches on the sides as the only thing they could do was walk forward. Soon enough they could see some light at the end of that corridor and they were greeted to rows upon rows of books. A peculiar feeling washed through the people here, their stamina and wounds were recovered almost instantly after going through the library entrance.

'This is an actual safe zone... would be nice if it also had a save point'

The so-called library was quite circular, the long shelves of books formed rings around each other as the collection expanded outwards. In the middle of the large library hall, there was a large circular tube. The tube went upwards and into the ceiling, in the middle there looked to be something akin to sliding doors and a number '1' above it.

'Is that an elevator...?'

It looked like a normal elevator, it had all the required buttons like the ones that opened and closed the doors. While the other cultivators were glancing at the books, Matt walked up to the elevator and pressed the button that should open it but nothing happened.

'The doors aren't opening... maybe it's locked until we clear the other levels?'

There were seven buttons on that elevator, which correlated to the seven deadly sins theme of this test. He left the elevator for now, as after poking every button nothing was happening. He then heard some of his companions speaking out.

"These books are all for Qi condensation practitioners... but the quality is astonishing!"

He looked at them going through some scriptures, their eyes focused as they were going through the old knowledge. Matt didn't wait much before he picked up one book and used the help of his system to scan its worth.

Crimson Phoenix Immolation Palm (First Scripture) [ Mortal High Grade ]

'Oh, it is indeed a high grade technique for a Qi condensation manual... and only the first part of it...'

He glanced over it, his system gave him more statics than just the grade of the technique. He also had the option to save it to his system library without having to actually absorb the knowledge outright and get a migraine while doing it.

Name : | Star Phoenix Immolation Palm(First scripture)
Meant for : | Qi Condensation Cultivators ( 6+)
Grade : | Mortal High Grade
Requirements : | Fire Affinity C+ grade and up
Qi usage: | Moderate-High
Description : | This art has been designed with close combat in mind, the practitioners gather their Qi into their palm transferring it into their opponent's body during a clash. The inserted Qi wrecks havoc inside the enemy's body burning them from the inside. The correct use of this art will produce a Phoenix tattoo on the practitioner's palm. Further scriptures allow the summoning of an actual Phoenix that aids in the attack.

'This doesn't look bad... quite deadly as it's an internal attack, it might even go through someone's body refining defenses.'

He started going through the manuscripts closest to him, they were all for practitioners in the Qi condensation and they were all above the mortal low grade. He looked up at the bookcase, it had the symbol of fire above it this was probably why everything in this section was for fire-based cultivators.

"Think this section of the library would be fit for the Huo clan."

Matt brought this to attention as Huo Qiang came over. He and his retainer's jaw opened up wide as they read the previously picked up Crimson Phoenix Immolation Palm, but this wasn't even the best one amongst the techniques that were lined up there. There were various ones, punching arts, kicking arts, ones for using weapons even regular cultivation manuals that were probably above anything that the Huo clan had in their own library back home.

"This is a treasure trove of knowledge if we could bring those books back with us..."

The two men had sparkles in their eyes as they went through some of the displayed cultivation manuals. Matt was a bit less optimistic than the two as he didn't think that the person that made this place would just let them clean the library out. He was more inclined in thinking that they might be able to take a couple of them later, or even worse as they would get none. With the second option, they would probably have to focus on learning the desired art in the limited time period they had in this library.

"I wouldn't get my hopes up, I bet the immortal senior that gathered all these books here wouldn't just let us take them with us."

Well, this was just something that the others had to contend with, Matt, on the other hand, could just copy everything into his library with a couple of clicks. Thus he did that, while his party members were going through some scriptures and old texts he started poking them while they were still on the shelves.

Fist of the Supreme General [Mortal High Grade ]

Do you wish to copy this text to the system library?

He clicked yes and moved over to the next book repeating the motion over and over again. The people in the large room were a bit bewildered as they saw Zhang Dong move his finger up in the air while tracing his other finger through the lined-up books. Was this some kind of technique to find the best secret text or something? They didn't want to ask as the man looked quite focused, his fingers were moving at an amazing speed while he was squinting.

'Damn... is there no faster way to do this... there are thousands of books here... this is going to take a while.'

He was familiar with this procedure already, as he did the same thing back at the Zhang Clan library. Though the clan's library wasn't as huge as this one and didn't have all these varying cultivation arts. He even found some lightning-related techniques here, focusing on copying them down as he frantically went through the entire place, he had to get everything down in those 24 hours, he might not have a second try.

He was soon like a blur, hands kicking up winds as he copied everything down without even reading what the skill was for. Everything was going to be shoved into his database, he dreaded the day when he would have to write everything down or use jade slips instead. Thanks to this library being so orderly and circular, he was sure that he wouldn't miss anything if he just went in order. Time soon passed and the next stage was upon them.

Zhang Dong managed to finish the 'plagiarising' procedure an hour early, so he had some time to think about the new stage and rest up. As the 24th hour ticked down the scenery became a blur. There was no voice or message the scenery just switched to a small room with another door in front. Everyone looked surprised, they were just reading some scriptures contemplating the basics and foundation of their techniques as they got teleported here, the books that they were studying just evaporating into nothingness as they found themselves in a sterile room.

"I guess they won't let us take those books out of there, guess that was expected."

Matt mentioned his theory to the others while going towards the door in front.

"Hope everyone is ready, there are probably be more monsters inside and I bet they will be stronger than the previous ones."

Everyone got ready while Zhang Dong grabbed the handle and swung the door open, soon enough everyone stepped through the door. They were greeted with a flash of bright light and a scenery change. The first thing that Matt noticed after taking a step in that the ground was strangely squishy.

'Ugh... what is this?'

He grimaced as he looked at the scenery, the ground and walls looked like they were made from pink flesh. They were in some kind of corridor once again but it looked to be alive.

"Are we in some kind of beast's belly?"

One of the cultivators asked while poking the flesh wall, it was warm to the touch and when you sliced it blood would gush out. There were no spasming or trembling that would accompany attacks to someone's insides, so maybe they weren't inside some creature just some badly created scenery.

'The person that made these trials sure has some strange fetishes...'

Matt thought to himself, but as he wanted to move on Kwok Xun started grasping his stomach.

"What is this feeling ...s-so hungry... "

He was looking at the fleshy walls in the surroundings with reddish eyes and drool coming out of his mouth, this prompted Matt to look at his status screen.

Kwok Xun [Core Formation middle stage] ( Starvation )

'Yeah... figures, seven deadly sins...'

Luckily they had the monk with them, he was surprisingly good against curses and debuffing effects like they were encountering in this place. Soon a golden shield surrounded them once more, letting Xun sigh out after the horrid longing to eat the fleshy walls subsided.

"I think these trials are going to amplify the humanly desires... how many of those talismans do you have on you...?... you never told us your name..."

Matt asked while looking at the monk that was chanting.

"You may call me Bankei. Forgive me, but I only have a handful left and I don't have any more materials to make more."

He said respectfully while holding the barrier up, Matt rubbed his chin he seemed to be unaffected by the mental game like debuffs probably due to his previously acquired skill that protected his mind.

"Brother Bankei, how long can you keep this golden barrier up?"

"I can sustain it for twelve hours, longer if I have something to replenish my spiritual energies."

Zhang Dong nodded while looking to the side at the other cultivators.

'Think that should be enough... it's not a very hard skill to learn and I already upgraded my Impartation of Knowledge to a high degree.'

The answer to the problems was quite easy, he had the skill and he could easily pass it on to others. So he didn't wait much, before moving over to his first 'victim'.

"I'm going to pass on a secret art to you now, it will protect you from the strange afflictions that these trials are putting us under."

He was a bit ashamed that he didn't think about it sooner if they were placed in a boss room from the get-go it could have turned out quite badly. Kwok Xun was the first person that was left with a migraine, grasping his forehead after Zhang Dong poked it with his finger.

"T-this is... truly astonishing... my gratitude!"

He bowed to Zhang Dong before going down into the lotus position to cultivate this skill. Soon everyone besides the Bankei was down on the ground, trying to cultivate the Tranquil Mind technique, there should be no problems with the debuffs later on after they were done.

'I sure hope that this place doesn't have a timer on it or something...'

Time passed and the cultivators finished at a varying degree, the youngsters like Huo Qiang and Feng Liena were the fastest, showing that their high cultivation stage at their current age wasn't just for show. The slowest was Feng Maling which caused the tanned Feng Matriarch to blush a bit in shame.

The effects of 'starvation' was now gone even though Bankei pulled back his barrier, they could move. The monk didn't need Zhang Dong's cultivation technique as his sect had a lot of skills that shielded them from demonic influences. Matt passed it on to him anyway, he would feel bad if the guy was the only one not profiting while having to hold that barrier up for so long.

The team moved forward, going through the fleshy corridors as the second trial 'officially' begun.

Chapter 97

The second trial wasn't anything out of the ordinary, at least not for Matt. The boss monster looked like a giant head of an obese person with tentacles coming out of its neck area which it used to move and wiggle around the main boss room. He was already 90% sure that the person that designed this so-called tower trial was someone from Earth. If they weren't from Earth they must have either came from a very similar place or they visited it for an undisclosed amount of time.

The monster went through some generic boss phases where it ducked its head into the fleshy wall and started attacking everyone with its tentacles. While doing so the main body couldn't be damaged and the cultivators couldn't do anything besides dodging. It was even telegraphing some of its attacks which allowed the people to dodge with ease. Soon enough the monster was dead and they were taken back to the library.

"That went rather well brother Dong, I'm sure we can get through this trial and get the treasure at the end! But even this Library here is already a treasure trove, only if it weren't only techniques for Qi cultivation juniors."

Huo Qiang furrowed his brows a bit while picking up a fire elemental cultivation technique from the side.

"Oh... I think there will be more than only those..."

Matt said while walking up to the elevator, Feng Liena next to him as she was curious about what he was doing.

"Do you know something about this magical door, Brother Dong?"

She asked while glancing between the elevator and him curiously. Matt smiled a bit as that face that she was making was kind of cute.

'I sure hope this works, otherwise, I'll look a bit silly...'

He pressed the button to open up the door and waited. Soon enough the doors opened themselves up and revealed an open area inside.

"See, now it opens. I bet we can go to the second level of the library with this elevator."

The people gathered around him, slowly going inside and looking at the buttons that ranged from one to seven.

"So this is called an elevator? What a strange name... how do you know this, Brother Dong?"

Feng Liena asked, her face beaming with curiosity while Matt's palms started to sweat.

"I ah... left my clan for ten years and traveled the world, I came across a lot of ancient ruins and found a lot of wisdom that described things like these here..."

Feng Liena clapped her hands while smiling up to Zhang Dong as if she bought his excuse.

"Ah, that explains why you are so knowledgeable about these trials. When we get out I must also travel the world and visite those sites!"

The girl pumped herself up a bit while the old lady from the side started shaking her head.

"You must not young Matriarch, you are supposed to lead our clan now, we can't have you going around visiting strange dangerous places!"

The old woman was clearly against it, the happy expression vanished from Liena's face and got replaced by a cute pout. That was not something a woman in her forties should probably do, which made Matt chuckle a bit.

"Brother Dong you laughed, how could you!"

She pointed an accusing finger at the man that tried to cover his face up with his sleeve.

"I don't know what you are talking about Sister Liena... you sure it wasn't Brother Qiang?"

Qiang looked from the side, eyes narrowing as he looked at Zhang Dong.

"Hey, don't get me involved in this!"

The atmosphere in the elevator became a bit lighthearted as the cultivators started laughing, soon enough they heard a beep and the door opened up to a similar-looking library room. The people spread out to see what was on this level, Matt grasped one book and was surprised when he read the title.

"Oh? It's an encyclopedia about basic herbs found in the world?"

"Hey, these aren't combat manuals or cultivation manuals, they are books about various occupations."

This level had the basic knowledge required to be an Apothecary or an Alchemist that forged pills that cultivators were so crazy to devour at astonishing rates. This wasn't all though, there were crafting manuals, manuals about the anatomy of the human or beast body that would help you become a beast tamer or a physician.

"This is even better than the first level... if we could only get this out of here..."

Huo Qiang lamented while going through the books, he knew well that these books were a treasure trove of wisdom that you could build a strong clan or sect on. What was an Apothecary? It was someone who could make magical pills that increased the rate of someone's cultivation. There were various pill formulas here that even though they were most suited for Qi Condensation and Foundation Establishment cultivators, were quite the gem.

This wasn't all, there were formation array manuals ones for aspiring blacksmiths with a lot of blueprints for defensive and offensive treasures. There was everything to start you off and set you on the path of a master in a given occupation.

Even though this level was even better than the first one, the people here gave out a sigh. They were mostly combating oriented cultivators, none of them would really profit much from these manuscripts and ancient texts. Still, they still dabbled in a couple of occupations so they could use this time to read up on things they got stuck in.

Zhang Dong just did his thing in copying over every last book into his system library, he didn't even know how many points he would have to spend to get these kinds of resources from the system cash shop.

'Jackpot!'

"Ah, if you want to get back to the other level just press the button with the letter one on it, it will bring you down there. When you want to get back here, just press the number two."

He gave out the information, maybe the other cultivators wanted to read up on the combat arts more than about forging pills or swords. So hours passed and everyone diligently read, well everyone besides Zhang Dong that was running around like a madman and waving his finger around in rapid motions.

"Cookie clicker skills, don't fail me now!"

The people didn't know what he meant with that, but he looked absorbed in his task so they left him alone. He was a reliable asset to this ragtag team of cultivators, but he still had his quirks but that was normal as most high-level cultivators were eccentrics. Or so thought the other eccentrics in the group.

So passed the days, the group had been in the secret ground for over a month now but they were still hanging in. They kept finishing the trials which followed a similar pattern. Sometimes they had to move through a larger area killing of monsters or gathering items that would open the path to a boss area. On other occasions they were dropped into the boss room from the start, having to cope with the sudden attacks.

The library levels started opening up as Matt gained more and more books into his library, on the third level there were more combat and cultivation manuals but this time around they were for Foundation Establishment cultivators. They were of superior grading than what the people had in their clan's back home ranging from lower-level earth grade all up into the perfect grade.

As expected on the fourth level there were more pill forging formulas and blueprints, they were on a higher level than the ones that were on the second level. The items produced from here could very well be used by core formation cultivators which made a lot of them try to memorize the pill formulas that increased someone's cultivation rate or replenished their spiritual essence.

"Maybe if I carve this formula onto my thigh I can take it out with me..."

Some of them had some crazy idea's, Matt just smiled as he went through the whole library finishing up a lot faster than before as the higher the level of the library was, the fewer books there were.

On the fifth level, they encountered their first boss monster that was in the great circle of core formation. This was quite the angry-looking beast looking like a behemoth, which fit the Sin of Wrath name quite well. The area they were fighting it was in a colosseum, they even had some strange skeleton-like creatures in the stands cheering at them while they battled the ferocious-looking beast.

The team of cultivators were already used to fighting these trials, so even though the monster's power was above them they weren't afraid. They knew that they only needed to support Zhang Dong by activating various game-like mechanics around the stage, they already knew their own strengths and weaknesses everyone kind of having a sense of comradery as they were even able to joke around in the midst of battle.

Soon the beast was slain and everyone returned back to the library, the new level finally having cultivation manuals that could be used by these elders. Everyone frantically searched for the best cultivation method they could find, hoping that they could remember them. They even begged Zhang Dong for a part of his robe on which they could write it down with their blood as they knew that his clothes could regenerate.

After hearing that Matt wanted to tell them that he could remember the cultivation arts and that he would write it down for them later. But on second thought, in their stead, he would probably write it down himself for safekeeping, even if someone else offered to do it instead. Always better to have a backup plan, he could share some knowledge with them later.

'Envy and Pride left, this monster had an extremely hard hide, it took a while to pierce its defense.'

'Think the only reason we made it this deep in, is due to not being affected by the mental attacks.'

If he were to get a berserk status like in the Sin of Wrath stage, he could very well wipe his entire team out by himself in a fit of rage. The whole party would probably tear each other apart.

'Think Envy would give some kind of jealousy debuff, probably you wouldn't be able to trust each other and get paranoid. Not sure what Pride would do though... being too prideful to ask for help?'

He had some free time as he wandered through the library levels, hoping to find more stuff than just the books, to no avail though.

'I'm close to the great circle with my body refining, but these blasted bosses aren't dropping any items...'

While he was saddened by the fact that he had no weapons to absorb, he looked at a metal candleholder. It was quite elongated and only had space for one candle, it looked like you could clobber someone good with one of those. He focused on it, his analyzing skill getting activated as he was spacing out.

Candleholder Club Middle Earth Grade

'What?'

He quickly snatched the thing from the table it was standing on, the library having various tables and chairs in which you could rest and read in peace. He instantly checked if there was a reaction to his body refining absorption skill and to his surprise the candleholder was reacting.

"Yes...YES!!!"

He shouted out, luckily the people around were already used to his strange outbursts so they didn't seem bothered. He snatched a couple of those candleholders as quickly as possible as he didn't have much time and took the elevator down to get even more. He moved into a more secluded place and started cultivating diligently. The metal from the item started melting as it flowed into his body, increasing his body by refining percentages and pushing it towards that hundred percent mark.

"Body refining great circle, here I come! Golden candleholder body awaken!"

He cheered while thinking if there were some metallic plates or ashtrays that he could also absorb.

Chapter 98

The Envy trial was over, the boss monsters weren't really hard to beat if you took care of the afflictions that the stages gave you. Matt felt like he was cheating with his skills, but not like he was complaining as on the fifth level there were core formation manuals. On the sixth level, there were more crafting, forging and pill formulas reaching towards things core formation and even some nascent soul experts could profit from. His cultivation nut buddies were drooling at the books that they were holding, some were of the Heavenly rank. Matt was holding one of those cultivation manuals in his hand, this was the third part of the series and he hoped that he would find the last one on the next level as well.

Name : | Supreme Thunder God's Penetrative Nirvana Finger ( Third Tome )
Meant for : | Core Formation (Middle Stage+)
Grade : | Heaven Middle Grade
Requirements: | Lightning B+ grade and up
Qi usage: | High
Description : | Finger attack focusing the cultivators lightning Qi into their fingertips. The longer you charge this attack the stronger it will be, possesses supreme penetrating power.

'Looks good, but who came out in that name... I feel like the FBI will come after me if I use that on someone.'

He didn't think he would be able to find some techniques that were better than the ones he bought of his system store. But there were ones of heaven grading mostly the lower one but still. The number of books on the fifth and sixth levels was quite limited so he didn't need the whole twenty-four hours to copy them down.

First came the body refining though, he had pried every metallic object from the walls or ceiling that had some weapon sounding suffix and prefix. He didn't expect that the items around here would have a grading, who would expect to find earth graded items scattered here. But even then he didn't find much besides the candleholders or some metal quills.

While his friends were on the sixth and fifth-level scrambling to write things down, or remembering them he was on the second level cultivating. This was the one that no one really visited, having the most basic crafting manuals on it that no one really wanted.

He could feel the warm metallic substance enter his body as he felt the familiar feeling. He was breaking through, his muscles tensed up and his body started shining brightly. He looked like a golden statue that had been polished and spotlights were pointed at it. After the breakthrough, he glanced at his status screen, which he didn't really bring up for quite a while.

Name : | Zhang Dong
Affiliation : | Zhang Clan
Spirit Points : | 423267
Cultivation Base Qi : | Core Formation [Late Stage 2 %] (Empowered Lightning Core)
Cultivation Base Body : | Core Formation [Great Circle 0,5 %] (Golden Body)
Techniques : | Empowered Lightning Qi cultivation art, Golden Body Arts, Thunderlight Sword, Thunder Movement Art...
Dao : | Dao of Heavenly Lightning, Dao of Smithing and Crafting
Other : | Senior Aura, Impartation of Knowledge, Mentor's Eyes, Apprisal...

'Well, my cultivation base didn't increase at all... but the body refining is finally up there. I wish I could get that upgrade though...'

He still had some candleholders on the side, luckily there were some chandeliers here and there so the place wasn't all dark. But it was certainly darker than what you expect from a library building.

'I bet the guys have some magic arts to see better or spirit up some glowing whisp for it...'

Matt went back to cultivating, the remaining items not really pushing his cultivation forward that much as he was earning fractions of percentages even from earth middle graded items. He would take what he could get, couldn't really complain about the free items but he knew that he wasn't getting to the nascent soul anytime soon. The description on his body refining also had a new line in it, he required a heaven graded item to advance after getting 100%.

'Here is hoping there will actually be some tangible rewards on the 7th level.'

Time winded down and the group soon found themselves at the last stage. They were walking down a curved set of stairs while the surroundings were just a starry void. There was a large platform above them where they were walking to, lights appeared on the side of those stairs that looked like blue Wisps. The whole place was dead silent the only things that could be heard were their footsteps and breathing.

"This should be the last one, wonder what my clan members are doing now..."

Matt said while walking ahead a couple of steps, he was in the front so he couldn't really see the other cultivator's expressions. The others were reminded about their own clans, they hadn't seen them for over a month now and had no way of knowing if they were still alive.

"I'm sure the junior members made it through, Feng Daiyu might not be the brightest but her strength speaks for itself."

Feng Maling proclaimed while looking at her worried Matriarch that was deep in thought after hearing Zhang Dong mention his own clan.

Soon the group was at the top, the stage was round and there was nothing on it besides one thing. A person was sitting on a large throne, looking at them while resting his cheek on his right hand. His legs were spread apart, his eyes wide open and red in coloring. He was looking at the group of people, seemingly annoyed at the cultivator's late arrival.

"It took you long enough..."

Sin of Pride [ Core Formation Great Circle ]

The man looked quite bored as he leaned back in his throne, he looked like someone in his thirties. He was wearing a red robe and had horns coming out of his head that curved inwards. His hair was white just like Matt's and he was of similar stature as the lightning cultivator.

"Let me congratulate you on reaching this point in your journey. Not many people manage this feat."

He didn't look like he would be getting up from his throne anytime soon as he just switched the hand he was leaning on to the other one and continued babbling some exposition.

"Most people never get the Sin of Greed, I congratulate you on resisting your natural predisposition."

Guess he was talking about how cultivators in this world would murder their own family just to get that one pill which pushed their cultivation forward a level. The trial he was talking about just showed them some powerful treasures, they were supposed to fight each other for them. But they were just illusions that were easily dispelled by Matt's mind technique, but he wouldn't tell the boss that the trial debuffs and tricks were useless against his Tranquil Will.

'Think I need to invest in better mind fortifying techniques, they will probably be crucial if I ever visit other secret grounds like this. The people making those always like to test people by showing them illusions or things like their worst fears to test them."

The boss started recounting all the trials, congratulating the whole group while they looked at him trying to measure his strength.

"This one is strong..."

Huo Qiang mentioned while sweating a bit from the overbearing aura that the Sin of Pride was giving off.

Matt wasn't quite sure, but thanks to his level up in body refining he was content on defeating this monster in a one on one.

"After saying this...you have two choices..."

The man finally stood up from his throne, his arms going behind his back as he stood like your regular senior cultivator.

"You may face me together, but if you do that you forfeit further rewards. The second option would be to face me in a one on one battle, if one of you manages to defeat me, you may take one item from the seventh level."

The man grinned and spread his arms as he looked at the people in front of him.

"What say you? Will you attack me all together like a bunch of cowards, or are there any warriors amongst you that are up to the challenge?"

Some of the male cultivators behind Matt went red in the face after they got called cowards, but after feeling the man's aura they decided not to go forward just yet. While the people were hesitating behind him, Matt took a step forward chest straight up, his steps slow and steady.

"I'll face you..."

The horned man looked at Zhang Dong that was approaching him, his eyes scanning his opponent that was only in the late stage of core formation.

"You sure are a brave young man, are you sure about this?"

Matt walked forward, getting closer and closer while hearing the other cultivators shout at him from behind.

"Are you sure about this Zhang clan Patriarch? This might be a trap."

Feng Maling chimed in while trying to look at the surrounding area if there were any other monsters around.

"Yes brother Dong, maybe you should reconsider?"

Feng Liena said while looking worried, the idea of the treasures was tempting but it would be better to play it safe.

Matt stopped for a moment to think about it, but for some reason, he didn't feel like he would lose. When he looked back to when he arrived in this place, he couldn't remember a situation that he couldn't just fight his way through. He had an easy ride thanks to the system so his ego was quite inflated at this point, the trial of Pride was made for people like Zhang Dong. He only suffered minor setbacks which were mostly due to his inexperience in fighting, but due to passing the jungle and having fought his way through it with ease he was feeling confident. So what if this was the creature's plan? He was sure that he could just bulldoze through him like he always did.

"Well then, let the trial begin!"

The Sin of Pride smirked while a translucent dome of energy appeared between the area he and Matt were in and the area where the others were. Everyone looked on nervously as the two combatants moved closer to each other. They knew that Zhang Dong was strong, probably the strongest core formation cultivator that they had ever seen, but he was making a rookie mistake now. He was letting himself get pulled into the enemy's scheme, it would be much safer to fight him as a group. Still though, if he won they would be getting more rewards, on the other hand, if he died they would probably not be able to defeat this monster even in a group.

"Why are the young always like this."

Feng Maling shook her head while looking at the youth that like many others before him, wasn't thinking with their brain and with their muscles instead.

"Let's believe in brother Dong, he is strong!"

Huo Qiang cheered while poking the shield that appeared before him, after the smack he felt a repelling force that pushed him back.

While the others sighed behind the barrier Matt was now standing in striking distance of the so-called Sin of Pride. The man was quite handsome, well built and smiling at his opponent while looking confident. The two stared at each other for a good few moments before the boss spoke up.

"Are you going to just stand there? Here, I'll give you the first one for free."

The man laughed at Zhang Dong while turning his cheek to the side and pointing at it, it looked like he was willing to receive a hit without dodging. Matt raised his brow at this display and shrugged, guess this guy was really sure of his strength he would have to bring him down a peg.

Matt could feel that the restrictions that he felt back in the jungle area weren't that strong inside this barrier. He could probably let loose in here, while thinking like that he started gathering energy into his fist. He pulled his fist back, blue lightning energy gathering into it as he charged his attack up.

Matt's robe and the man's fluttered as due to gathering so much spiritual energy wind was getting kicked up. His muscles bulged as he moved his arm backward, he was going for a normal punch with all his weight behind it along with some lightning energy. The Sin of Pride looked at the large fist that was getting charged up, Matt wasn't sure what he was thinking about but it didn't seem that he was going to dodge.

'Prideful, huh?'

The punch was finally thrown, a loud booming sound resounded inside the barrier as the fist filled with energy connected with a face. Matt could feel his strike going through, but he was surprised. The man's face was extremely hard, even with his body refining skill at the great circle he felt the attack down to his bones.

The man was forced backward, but he didn't fly as Matt expected but slid along the ground with his feet firmly planted on it coming to a stop after about ten meters. His face was turned to the side and you could see a red mark at the spot that Zhang Dong punched him. Sin of Pride moved his hand to his jaw, rubbing it slightly a grin appearing on his face.

"Nice hit!"

He spat out some blood while cracking his neck slightly, his hand on his jaw as he rubbed it slightly.

"Hey, I had an idea! Do you want to play a fun game?"

The man looked quite excited now, his eyes were wide open as he moved back to where he previously was. He moved his hand back, in a similar motion that Matt did and looked at his opponent.

"It's quite the fun little game~"

He replied with vigor in his voice, like he found something interesting.

Chapter 99

The ground shook, Feng Liena covered her face with the sleeve of her robe as she looked at what was happening inside the barrier bubble. She saw Zhang Dong receiving a devastating right hook right to his face. His face was bounced backwards and it looked like it would leave his neck and fly into space while he staggered. The residual shockwave from the devastating stroke tossing up a storm as even the sturdy floor was slowly showing a sign of cracks.

Zhang Dong shook his head a bit as he looked back at his opponent who was grinning widely. He was bleeding from a cut lower lip, the blood slowly dripping down onto the floor and his clothes. He looked quite happy though, moving his hand backwards and then crossing his hands over his own chest as he smirked.

"Your turn~"

Matt looked at the Sin of Pride, not really sure how the situation turned this way. He was having a good old fashioned slugfest with the guy. The man wasn't blocking and neither was he, they were having a competition of strength and resilience. Something was pushing him forward though, the more he saw the demon man smirk and smile the more he wanted to slam his fist into his face.

Another devastating blow landed, the opponent slid backwards yet again his jaw even getting dislocated as he lost a tooth from the exchange. Matt didn't rejoice though as the fist that he hit the man on the face was hurting like hell.

'Go down you fuck!'

He screamed internally while his enemy moved back into place, he could dodge the fist, he could putt out his sword or use some tactics, yet something was compelling him to power through it. Did he suffer some kind of status effect that was making him so prideful, or was this how he really was deep down inside? He wasn't sure, but he thought that he would lose dignity that he thought that he didn't have if he gave up before the other person did.

Soon thirty minutes had passed and the two were just going back and forth, hitting each other. More and more they ended up on the ground, but both of them kept standing up burning passion in their eyes. If Matt didn't know better, he would think that he turned into some kind of meat-headed protagonist that never gave up. Always having to face their enemies in a fair fight, their will unbroken.

While the two were continuing their punch out, the other cultivators looked at them with mixed feelings. Most of the men kind of understood why the Zhang Patriarch was sticking to this approach, while the girls thought that he was an idiot for getting pulled into the enemies rhythm. Though all of them agreed on one thing, the man was really resilient none of them felt like they could take one of those punches and be able to get up as well as he did.

"Do you think he can win it?"

"I'm not sure, they look equally matched... what monsters..."

"They have been at it for an hour, is their stamina infinite?"

"Let's hope the boy manages, don't think any of us can face that monster..."

The people chattered while standing close to the barrier, they had gone around it hitting it in various placed wondering if they could help Zhang Dong out. They didn't find a weak spot that they could slip in though, this barrier would probably hold off a nascent soul master. They could only twiddle their thumbs and wait for the silver-haired man to win this.

'Ah damn, my face hurts... is my nose broken? Will my teeth grow back if I lose any...'

He staggered backwards falling onto his ass, his opponent huffing and puffing as he was showing signs of fatigue. Well, not like he was better off though, he was bleeding from his nose and mouth only thanks to reaching the great circle in his body refining he was surviving this somehow.

'Think my body is harder than his, but he has a stronger healing ability...'

He would knock the Sin of Pride further back, breaking some bones in the process as his face was all bloody by this point. The problem was that after they switched turns, the man would start healing up and his broken jaw, chipped teeth all grew back into place. He, on the other hand, didn't suffer as much damage but it was slowly accumulating.

'I guess that's was his plan, force me into a battle of attrition that I can't win. But did he think that I would last this much...'

The boss monster wasn't grinning as much now as he was before, the two had been punching each other for over an hour now. Both of them had dishevelled hair and bloodied clothes, but the Sin of Pride was looking slightly worse than Matt was. He also stopped taunting him after each hit, he would shout some cocky phrases here and there but he was dropping the act now, his brows furrowing as Matt moved back into place with his fist ready to slam into that face one more time.

Matt gathered more energy into it, he still had some left in his tank as he was smart enough not to go full throttle from the get-go. This looked like a turning point, or just a scheme of the other man to make Matt show his cards. Though he didn't think that would be the case, as going by the theme of Pride the Sin of Pride should be too prideful to pull any sneaky tricks on him

The fist shined in a blue hue, lightning energy filling the space around him as Zhang Dong applied his condensation skill along with his avatar form just targeting his fist. Thunder resounded through the area as his wide fist smashed into the enemy's nose, shattering it on contact. The man's arms and legs remained stationary while his body was pushed back which made it looked quite comedic. The boss monster flew back, making a nice arc as he hit the throne that he was sitting on at the beginning of the stage.

The last punch took quite a bit out of him, his hand spasming and his veins bulging due to the condensation techniques side effects. Luckily the enemy wasn't moving for some reason, he looked like he was sleeping on that throne with his head slumped forward.

"Umm... I win?"

He raised his fist upwards while being slumped forward and barely standing up on his own two feet. Matt was close to passing out himself, he wasn't sure how many punches to the face he took but he hoped that he didn't get permanent brain damage now. He slowly walked over to the passed out Sin of Pride, not knowing if this was over or not. When he was leaning down, the man suddenly opened up his eyes which made Matt stumble back and almost fall on his butt once more.

"Buahahaha, It's my loss!"

The man smacked his thigh like he was having a jolly good time, though he was looking quite awful as Matt had destroyed quite a bit of his face during the punching contest.

"Congratulations oh Prideful one, you may receive your reward now!"

Suddenly he started turning into small spiritual lights like the other summoned monsters when you defeated them, his face still showing a dumb grin.

"Hope you can entertain me again when we meet anew. Enjoy your reward while you still can, prideful one"

Matt didn't get to ask about what he meant with that as he soon vanished and the barrier surrounding the area vanished. This wasn't over as the throne opened up and a small chest rose up from the sitting spot. It wasn't a large chest, something that you would use to store some jewellery at most. After opening it up he found a strange black cube inside.

???????????????????????????????

'What is this?'

The system couldn't analyze it and it was extremely hard, even when he gripped it with all his strength the thing wouldn't budge a muscle.

'Maybe it's some kind of key? Guess I should watch out for cube-sized holes.'

He shrugged and placed it in a side pocket of his robe, but just after doing that he collapsed to his knees. He didn't think his injuries were that bad, but the moment he felt the relief of beating the enemy his body started shutting down. He slumped forward, face planting on the throne out cold while his companions rushed in to check upon him.

He suddenly woke up while resting on a large leather couch, books around him as he was back in the library building.

'Ah, guess I'm not dead... but my face still hurts...'

He stood up and found Feng Maling studying some kind of occult looking book.

"Oh hey, how long was I out?"

He asked without thinking much, but the woman ignored him her eyes focusing on the thing in front of her as if it was something required for living.

'Wait... how long was I out...Fuck!'

He knew that this was the last level, it looked different than the previous ones. But this meant that he was out for an unknown amount of time and didn't get to copy any textures down, he might not make it in time. He started quickly running and poking the scriptures, realising that they were mostly in the heaven grade. On this level, there were both cultivation manuals and ones for crafting and pill making. The amount was less than on the lower levels but he didn't know how much time he had left, he had to copy them down as soon as he could.

'Wasn't there supposed to be some kind of reward as well?'

While Zhang Dong was shuffling through the books, his clan members were still stuck in the fortress. They had spent a whole month at this location and it looked a lot different than before.

Firstly, the shape of it wasn't square anymore or at least the outer walls changed. They had been spending their days killing a monster wave each day, the stronger the monsters the more points they earned for clearing them out. The cultivators figured out how the treasure map in the form of the hologram worked and had placed an octagonal wall, that surrounded the old square ones.

On the new wall, there were other weapons there beside the ballista. There were cannons placed lined up on the walls, shooting out blasts of condensed energy. They required specialised ammunition that was carried over by the Qi condensation cultivators. At the spots where the walls connected to each other stood defensive towers, more cannons and ballistas being placed there. Inside of them, there were people, wielding some weapons like rapid firing spirit crossbows that they also could exchange for points.

It looked like they were doing fine on the outside having constructed a larger fortress that was there before, but the atmosphere in the control room was a bit different.

"We used up all of the resources on repairing, the next wave will be starting in an hour, it's going to be worse than the previous one..."

One person proclaimed while glancing at the hologram of the fortress, the number of points being in the single digits, the amount not enough to buy even the simplest self firing weapon.

Zhang Zhi, Huo Tao, and Feng Daiyu looked tired, they had been actively participating in defending the fort, it wasn't strange for the walls to crumble and they having to bunker back behind the ones deeper inside.

"The number of core formation beasts is increasing, there was one more this time around too, it almost got through the inner walls."

"That formation that your Zhang Clan possesses is really astonishing, Brother Zhi."

Huo Tao declared while rubbing his beard, the Huo clan had long thrown out their misgivings about the other cultivators here. After having fought for a month everyone realised that they had to work together, otherwise they would all surely die. There was some tension in the beginning, even some deaths due to some misgivings, people fighting each other out of stress. Luckily the people somehow managed to get past that first hump, mostly due to the Zhang Clan listening to their Patriarch order and not retaliating as much and instead trying to work it out together.

Teamwork had a limit though, the ferocious beasts were getting stronger and stronger even though they could fortify this base of theirs, they were slowly faltering. Something was coming, past the 90th wave, the time of rest had decreased each time. This would be the 100th one, and they were expecting something big.

"Final wave will commence in 5...4...3...2...1..."

After the robotic voice resounded everyone gulped hard, the people that weren't injured were manning the walls and towers looking out into the distance. The terrain was already destroyed, the ground bulldozed by all the previous monster waves. Soon people heard thumping noises coming from the distance soon enough four giant silhouettes could be distinguished each monster larger than the other as they came from all sides.

From the East came an azure dragon it was floating slightly above ground as it moved forward. From the south flew a vermilion bird, spewing fire as it charged forward. From the west, they saw a white tiger charging right at them while up north was the largest beast a black tortoise lumbering towards them, the immense shell it had didn't look like it could be pierced by anything.

Chapter 100

A note from Kuropon

This one is going to be a bit long also there is an epilogue chapter after this one.

The 9th Platoon was standing in one of the towers, on their side was the large white tiger. It wasn't alone though as there were many smaller feline type beasts moving in front of it. The giant monster strolled while yawning like it was bored that it had to even leave its nesting place to take care of the bug-like cultivators.

"Great ancestors, in what realm is that beast?"

Zhang Jie looked at the far away monster with her looking glass, the spiritual energy coming from the large tiger beast was immense. This kind of aura belonged to someone at the top of core formation, but she wasn't sure if it was in the late stage or in the great circle.

"This doesn't look good... everyone get ready, fire when they are in range!"

The junior members were ready, they had been doing this for a month already some of them were injured from the previous battle. Zhang Peng had a really large canon and was holding it against his shoulder, making it look like he was carrying a rocket launcher. Zhang Hong was to the side, he looked a lot slimmer now than previously, mostly his upper body that turned all that fat into muscle. Still, his battle robe was protruding at the belly part.

Zhang Teng and Bao were to the side, gathering ammunition in the corner making sure that they had enough before they had to return to get some more for their brothers and sisters. Zhang Yuu and Mii weren't here with them as they went to the barracks to help out with the injured, their healing arts having progressed quite a bit during this hard month of battling.

Zhang Ai and Xue were holding crossbows that had a part that you could load bolts into, they were just making sure that everything was in place before placing the weapons against the small windows in the tower they were in and taking aim. Zhang Tai and Liu were sitting in something that looked like a cockpit, they had something that helped them aim the cannon that they were operating as these cost a lot fewer points than the ones that were automatic.

Soon you could hear cannon fire, the monsters exploding into gorry bits as they were hit by the metallic shells. The whole place looked like a more futuristic fortress, with spotlights shining and heavy artillery getting fired from it by the cultivators inside. You could see gyaru girls running around with boxes in their hands, quickly restocking the used up self-working ballistas.

Explosions filled the entire place, the monster wave didn't stop as for every beast that exploded during the charge two more came from behind it and like a tsunami they got closer and closer finally arriving close to the walls. But before the creatures could start climbing and devouring the people inside an energy barrier appeared to block their path. The monsters scratched it with their claws, bit into it and just charged at it in a fit of rage, the energy bubble wouldn't be able to stop them forever.

The biggest problem were the flying enemies, the largest of them looked like a phoenix made from fire. It was circling above the large fortress casting a shadow over it, while the people inside tried shooting it down with their spiritual cannons, to no avail as it was out of range. They had to leave it alone for now as the smaller flying beasts started slamming into the transparent energy field. They turned into hedgehogs due to the many crossbow bolts that the defending cultivators fired into them.

It looked like they were in a standstill for now, but that was only due to the boss monsters not really moving in. The monsters stopped and watched as their minions attacked the castle in an angry rush, the only huge beast that was constantly moving was the turtle that was almost as big as the whole fortress that the cultivators were defending.

Time ticked down and minutes turned into hours, the monsters still kept coming. The people inside recognized a lot of those beasts from the previous waves but due to the increased firepower and defensive structures, they went down a lot faster than before. Soon enough the monsters from the previous wave made their appearance, prompting the elder members from the clan to head out into battle.

The battle looked bleak as the first defensive barrier got breached and the cultivators had to flee into the inner fortress. The automatic weapons were quickly destroyed or they run out of ammunition as the beast burst forward. It looked like it would be a repeat of what happened on the previous wave, the Zhang Clan members were already in their serpent formation firing off their breathing attack to bring down one of the core formation beasts that made its way past the barricade.

Everyone was desperately fighting for their lives, but the most powerful monsters were still just sitting outside the first wall and waiting. Only after the beasts moved into the inner sanctum and were defeated once more the ones outside moved. The tiger roared out loudly prompting the remaining feline beasts to part ways for it, the same happened on all sides.

"Damn, there is no place to run and those beasts are still coming..."

Zhang Zhi propped himself upwards, the last attack that he performed along with his clan members having drained his reserves. The last wave was bad enough, but even though they defeated the monsters the path was open. All the walls were breached, just a couple of cannons remained with some leftover cultivators still reloading and firing them off at the enemies.

"Was it impossible to win from the start?... I have failed you, Patriarch"

Huo Tao lamented while blood was running down his face, the man having a hard time keeping conscious after taking a serious blow from an angry-looking beast.

Feng Daiyu was to the side just sighing, they put up a noble fight but this looked like it was it for them. The monsters outside just needed to move in, to dish out the killing blow. Their strength was immense and even if they had the power of the fortress behind them, she thought that they had a slim chance of coming out on top.

A bit outside the inner sanctum in one of the partially destroyed towers the 9th platoon was still fighting. Monsters started flooding inside and they were battling them with the help of their weapons.

Zhang Xue and Liu combined their lightning attacks to send one of the leopard looking beast tumbling back, letting Zhang Peng smash his fist into its spine taking it out in the process. They all looked injured, sweat running down their foreheads and dripping to the floor along with their blood.

Zhang Jie was to the side, holding onto her belly a monster had pierced it with its sharp claws before she could take it out. She was getting nursed by one of the girls, Xue and Liu quickly ran up to her worry in their eyes.

"Mother!"

"Leave me... I'll hold them off, you must reach the inner fortress with the rest of the clan members."

They got separated from their clan members when the beasts burst through the walls, so they were sitting ducks for the incoming monster cats. The thumping of the largest one getting louder and louder as it approached them at an increased pace.

"No we can't, we will survive this together."

Zhang Xue replied with tears in her eyes, her mother glancing up at her children that she held dear to her heart. They were her pride and joy and she only came here with them to keep watch, but this would be the end for her. She would stay behind in the hopes of a miracle, even if she could just buy them a second of more time it would be enough.

"Silence, this is an order. Get back to the inner sanctuary!"

She glanced at the other platoon members with a stern face, which prompted them to grasp the crying girl pulling her back from her mother. Zhang Jie nodded as the others started evacuating, her eyes meeting with her Son's on the way as he hesitated as well.

"Take care of your sister."

The youth didn't reply and just made a small bow and then turned around leaving, a small tear running down his cheek as he lamented. The woman stood up going further up onto the tower, her wound was just patched up but it was enough for her to last a few moments. She saw beast charging her way, their teeth sharp and their claws long. She was holding on to a chipped sword and plunged it into the beast's eye as it tried pouncing at her. The weapon snapped in half as she tumbled to the side, her battle wound opening up.

The monster slummed after its brain got pierced by the weapon, turning into bubbles of energy soon after. The woman leaned about a cracked battlement looking back seeing that her children were running back they would probably make it to the other clan members. She smiled but was startled as she heard a startling deep growl.

She turned to see a large feline eye just staring at her, the white tiger had made its way to the tower she was in. The beast was immense and wouldn't have trouble in gulping her down in one quick bite. The woman coughed up some blood and looked up into the sky, eyes soon closing and a smile appearing on her face.

"I'll be joining you soon dear, Jie'er did her best..."

She was tired, tired from all the fighting, tired from all the bloodshed. The moment she accepted her impending death her legs gave out under her and she slumped on the ground. The beast just gave out a snort that made the woman slide backward and hit the wall, more blood coming out of her mouth in the process.

The beast looked at the small bug in front of it, why wasn't the little human trembling like it was supposed to? The proud tiger didn't understand while the bug was smiling and just waiting there. But it wouldn't refuse free food, the woman was of a higher cultivation level and looked quite yummy. Its giant maw opened up wide, the teeth being almost as large as the human that they were going towards. The beasts warm breath hit Zhang Jie's skin and some saliva dripped on her body, soon the mouth would close devouring her whole.

"KRRACCKKK!"

The monster felt something slam into its head shattering its giant teeth in the process. Its immense body flew backward slamming into the destroyed wall and bouncing further and further. It kept rolling and bouncing in a comedic fashion soon leaving the premise of the outer fortress walls that it came through, its mind dazed as the hit rattled its brain, stunning it momentarily.

Zhang Jie felt the wind hit her face, pushing her further back into the wall she was leaning but nothing besides that. The pain didn't come and she didn't feel the monster's breath upon her anymore, which prompted her to open up her eyes. What she saw was a giant blue fist in the spot that the monster tiger's face was previously in, lightning energy crackling from it.

"P-Patriarch?"

She said in a daze while staring at the avatar form that she knew that her clan Patriarch used before. It was a bit bigger than the one he used when he saved the clan from the impending doom before, but it was clearly him.

"Sorry for being late, leave him to me. Take this and go back to the rest of the clan."

A recovery pill dropped on her head, right between her eyes which she quickly gobbled up a relaxing feeling washing over her body and her cracked bones and wounds quickly recovering. She looked as the lightning giant moved towards the equally large white tiger. With each step the giant took lightning energy shoot out, incinerating the lesser monster in its path.

"It's the Patriarch!"

Zhang Dong's appearance and overbearing aura was hard to miss, the Zhang Clan members cheered out loud as they saw their leader sock the beast tiger in the face sending it flying backward. Matt was the first one to arrive but soon enough the tired foundation establishment and qi condensation cultivators could see other core formation experts appearing, each one of them attacking the four beasts that were in similar stages as them.

Feng Liena and Feng Maling headed towards the flying monster, everyone had recovered the usage of their storage rings so they could finally use their flying swords once more. Huo Qiang and his bodyguard went towards the dragon while the remaining two decided to stall the slow-moving turtle monster, they didn't think they would be able to crack its shell but they could buy some time till Zhang Dong and the rest took care of the other beasts.

"It's the young master!"

"The Matriarch and the elder are still alive!"

"We are saved!"

Everyone cheered out loud as they saw their seniors arriving in the nick of time. Some of them were still missing but this was a massive confidence boost to all of the cultivators.

While Matt was running towards the tiger Zhang Jie quickly returned to her own clan members, Xue clinging to her arm and crying her eyes out once more.

"Xue'er you need to stop being such a crybaby, Mother is fine thanks to the Patriarch."

She replied while looking into the distance, the white tiger was in a chokehold thrashing around and trying to bite at the large lightning construct that was holding onto it tightly.

"Master is finally back!"

Zhang Liu had stars in his eyes and a grin plastered on his face, the faith that he had in Zhang Dong was slowly going into overdrive. The rest of the Zhang Clan members weren't far behind as they looked at the kaiju battle happening in the background, the white tiger suffering a slam that made the whole secret ground tremble.

"Everyone gather up, assume the formation we are going to support the Seniors!"

Zhang Zhi stumbled forward, still fatigued from the previous battle but reinvigorated by his leader's appearance. Everyone shouted out in unison as they assumed their position, soon the water serpent was formed. Zhi realized by the battle that the Patriarch didn't need any more help, so instead, they headed for the firebird, their water elemental serpent being just the thing to counter its fire attacks.

There were still smaller beasts around, so the cultivators barricaded themselves in the innermost wall of the fortress. Using the remaining ranged weapons as well as engaging the monster in hand to hand combat. The monsters were finally getting pushed back, the sounds of battle filled the surroundings.

Matt rammed his fist into the tiger, sending his sharp chompers flying into the air. He could tell what the theme of these beasts was from one look and from which directions they were coming from.

'The four guardian beasts huh, not a bad choice I guess...'

He thought to himself nonchalantly while delivering another full power punch to the beast's side, sending it tumbling to the side. The beast didn't look like it would be putting up much of a fight against this overpowered Patriarch but he couldn't play with it for too long as the others weren't as strong as him.

He started getting smaller and smaller, the tiger was on the ground shaking its head while recovering, he had enough time to deliver a finisher. He pulled out his sword, the weapon radiating with spiritual energy as it expanded into the heavens. He held his longsword with both hands, eyes closed and right at the time when he opened them he brought the sword downwards in a slash.

"Sever the Heaven!"

He shouted out, while the energy beam traveled downward. The monster could only look on in shock as the sword strike descended from the sky before it could evade to the side it was bisected the ground forming a chasm the moment the sword energy hit it. Lots of dirt and dust got flung into the air as the first monster got slain.

Guardian White Tiger Slain (Core Formation Great Circle ) 90000 points earned

Matt rubbed his nose a bit, blushing slightly due to shouting out the attack name before preforming it.

'Hope nobody heard that... embarrassing.'

The first beast fell, its two sides splitting and falling opposite each other. The peculiar thing was that the monster didn't turn into energy bubbles like the rest of them, but Matt was sure that it was dead. It was cleanly sliced in two parts, there should be no way of it to recovering its previous form. Also, there was the system prompt, and he even earned a good amount of points.

'I should go help the others...'

He thought while hearing a rumbling shout, he looked into the distance and saw Huo Qiang standing in a karate like stance. His bodyguard was keeping the monster dragon busy, it looked like it had already suffered some damage but so did the two other cultivators. The red-haired brother was gathering all of his spiritual energy into his fist strike, clearly taking his time while his clan member distracted the beast.

"This new technique... I only managed to cultivate it to a minor achievement but it should be enough...Take this beast!"

"Flame Emperor's Pure Yang Destruction Fist."

Matt stumbled forward after hearing the long name of the attack that Huo Qiang threw at the monster. The moment the man punched out you could see some kind of flame giant show himself behind him, it looked like a transparent hologram and he was taking the same stance and had the same facial expression as the cultivator in front.

The mutton chop elder fled to the side as he almost got hit by his young master's attack, he tumbled to the side. The flame fist cleanly landed on the dragon's head promptly turning it ton mincemeat and filling the whole area with fire energy. There was a huge explosion that made everyone look in the direction.

"Heh... not bad."

Matt smiled as he saw Huo Qiang passing out after throwing that fist attack at the monster. His new friends were a lot stronger than expected, the two women battled the giant bird slicing its wings with their wind attacks, the water serpent spewing beams out of its maw interrupting the firebird when it tried to counter-attack.

The turtle, on the other hand, was getting its face slapped around by a big Buddha statue. Bankei had gathered his remaining sect buddies and went into a formation of their own. The statue looked golden and had six arms, it was hovering above ground while in a sitting position delivering strikes to the monster's head that tried snapping at it.

Matt decided to go for the Turtle now as it looked a lot sturdier than the bird that was getting its feathers plucked by his clan members and the Feng Clan ladies.

It didn't take long for the cultivators to successfully eradicate every remaining monster in the area. The hardest one to kill was indeed the turtle as even though its attacks were weak, it was really hard to get through that shell. After the phoenix look-alike fell, everyone gathered up and started blasting the thing from all sides, soon enough the shell broke and the beast fell.

"We did it!"

"Wooo... I'm alive!!!"

"It's over right? This is it? I want to go home..."

People shouted out, cheering loudly their wounds didn't hurt as much now when they had victory on their minds. Everyone was tired, most of the fortress was in shambles wall chunks were everywhere. Just as Matt was ready to shout out to his clan members the robotic voice resounded around the area once more.

"Congratulations on completing the 100th wave... The bonus stage will start now."

"Bonus stage?"

Matt blinked wondering what this was about, but then he felt that something was happening to the giant monster bodies.They started glowing and condensing into small balls. The four spheres then shot out into the air gathering in one spot and fusing with each other. There was a giant shockwave that kicked up storm like winds and the cultivators felt a massive surge in spiritual energy in that area.

"No... this is?"

"I-it can't be..."

The energy was far greater than what a core formation cultivator could have, so everyone gulped as the area where the orbs fused together started showing an outline. Soon enough a large shout resounded through the destroyed testing grounds.

"Buahahah, I told you that we would meet again, didn't I, oh prideful one?"

The man was the previously fought Sin of Pride, but he looked a bit different. His body, as well as his face, was all red, his hands looked more like claws and his horns that were previously meager were quite large now. He looked like a textbook demon, sharp teeth white as pearls and an armor of red covering his whole body he even had large bat-like wings growing out of his back while hovering up in the air. But that wasn't the problem though.

"N-nascent soul? How could this be..."

Demon Lord [ nascent soul early stage ]

"I must thank you for setting me free, I don't get many opportunities to stretch my wings~"

The demon smirked while filling the area with its overbearing demonic aura.

"Set you free?"

Matt asked while looking up at the monster, he was feeling the brunt of that force that was making even him tremble.

"Oh, did you forget about the little game that we had? I hope the rewards were worth it~"

Matt groaned, the reason that the bonus stage started was probably that he blundered and accepted the pride monsters offer. How could he know that even when winning it, it would bring doom upon him and the clan later on?

"Well, not like I made the rules, hope you can entertain me for a bit~"

The demon shrugged while grinning and charging out, he was so fast that he vanished from Matt's field of vision and appeared behind him in a fraction of a second. Demonic wings kicking up massive winds that sent everyone close in the area backward, everyone was sent flying in various directions while the demonic being looked at Zhang Dong. The attack was clearly aimed at the cultivators beside Matt as he was mostly unaffected but everyone else was tossed aside.

Matt took on a fighting stance, the demon in front was in the nascent soul realm, could he even damage him? The grinning demon crossed his muscular arms over one another and just waited there, his head turned to the side as if he was beckoning him to strike his cheek just like when they had the punching contest.

Matt clenched his fist if the monster was willing to let him deliver a strike he would put everything into it. He gathered all of his spiritual energy into his right arm activating all skills that would let him enhance this hook. His forearm bulged out, veins protruding from it. His whole arm started crackling with lightning energy, the Qi getting pushed forward as the glow on his fist got brighter. He jumped forward ready to strike, the monster unmoving as if it didn't care about the puny attack that this human was preparing.

The ground trembled under Zhang Dong's might, he charged forward each step leaving a large hole behind, the other cultivators only seeing a white blur flying towards the demonic being.

'BOOOOMMM!"

The whole place shook as the strike connected, hurricane winds blasting everything to the side, people looking on in awe. Nothing should be able to survive a hit like that, this strike was extremely close to the nascent soul level even a master like that shouldn't come out unscathed, or so they thought.

"Hmm... is that all?"

A demonic voice could be heard which made everyone shiver, after the dust cloud subsided everyone could see what actually happened. Zhang Dong was kneeling down on the ground, holding his right hand with his left. The right fist in question looked mangled up, the skin was torn and some fingers were broken.

"Argh..."

Matt screamed out while grasping his hand, did he punch an iron wall or something. His hand was broken and bleeding, he looked up at the demonic being the man in question looking quite smug. He didn't have time to recover as a swift kick sent him flying back, the demon finally attacking.

"Ehh, I had high hopes for you, but you are this weak?"

Matt bounced a couple of times before managing to regain his balance, his good hand digging into the hard bedrock as he slid backward and finally came to a stop. He got kicked in the chest and felt that his ribs broke in a couple of places, he spat blood onto the ground and looked in horror in the direction of the monster that was flying towards him.

He grasped his sword, pushing all the energy that he could muster into it. When the demon got into his domain he released a barrage of sword strikes applying the same technique he used to slice up the Cthulhu like creature. The demon just walked forward, looking relaxed as the sword energy collided with his body. Matt expected to see blood but instead of slicing the demon apart, his sword broke into tiny fragments after it got smacked by the red monster's large hand.

"Pathetic."

Another kick landed to his side, he tried blocking it with his good arm but it got folded in half along with his body as he got blasted to the side. He screamed out in pain, blood spurting out of his side as he tumbled along.

'Fuck, it hurts.'

He couldn't move his other arm at all, it was just dangling like a wet noodle while he gathered himself up. The monster was just toying with him now, he had no way of retaliating. He was flung around the area like a punching bag, his legs soon broken while the demon grinned from seeing the previously prideful cultivator finally having a look of despair.

"That's it! Those eyes, that's how you are supposed to look! Despair more and grovel!"

He held Matt up with one hand, delivering some backhand and forehand slaps to his face before tossing him to the side and stomping on his legs some more. The man below just a broken mess now, tears, snot, and blood coming out of his orifices while he squirmed.

"Quickly, support the Patriarch!"

Some cultivators charged out from the side, but with a small gesture from the monster's wings, they tumbled backward like paper planes in hurricane winds. Their low cultivation levels not being able to resist the overpowered monster in the slightest.

"Hah, little worms..."

"L-leave them alone!"

Matt shouted while coughing, he pushed his broken stump of an arm into the ground as he was trying to stand up but the only thing that greeted him was the monsters swift kick that sent him flying once more, his chest denting inside as most of his ribs got broken. He ended up somewhere on his back, he had no strength to move at all, his vision was blurry and the pain was getting unbearable.

"You care about those insects so much? Bahaha, then watch them die!"

The demon grinned even more and strode towards the other cultivators, leaving Matt down on the ground so that he could watch as he killed those pesky humans.

"Haven't had so much fun in thousands of years, I must thank you, my friend. I'll be sure to kill them slowly~"

The monster laughed out loud while eyeing some of the cultivators that were further away. Matt's vision was fading as he was close to passing out, he had no way of saving anyone his body was beaten and battered.

'Is this it?... Am I going to die?... why was I even brought to this place?... I don't want to die... I still haven't done anything...'

His mind was filled with thoughts of failure, he lamented his incompetence if he wasn't so stupid and didn't take the monster's offer. Why did he always fail in everything, his life started flashing through his mind, a life of loneliness and mediocrity. Even with this system, he was unable to change his destiny. He started laughing, more blood coming out of his mouth as he chuckled at his inability.

"I'm sorry everyone..."

He wanted to apologize to the people that put their faith in him, he truly felt like he let everyone down. Everyone would die and he felt that he was to blame, maybe if he was a little smarter, listened to the wise words of the senior members or if he tried a bit harder, it wouldn't have ended up like this.

But suddenly in this moment of weakness, he noticed something to the side. It was the cube that he received after the seventh trial, it must have bounced to the side after he got smacked by one of the demon's attacks. It was slightly cracked, its outer shell filled with spiderweb-like fissures.

'W...what...'

The cube was giving off some kind of strange aura from all those small cracks, it was faint but it was still there. Like a man grasping for glass while falling from a building, he inched his broken body forward. He got closer and closer, not really sure why he was even bothering but something was pushing him forward, telling him not to give up.

Spirit energy source detected, do you want to absorb it?

He moved his arm upwards, his bones were broken in several places and he felt excruciating pain, but he needed to tap that yes prompt.

Starting absorption process please standby... error ... an abnormality has been detected ... system overloading...

He saw his status window that was a bit blurry, the points were shooting up by an unexpected amount.

'893291....1263145... 4678231...8523135...'

He didn't just twiddle his thumbs though after the absorption process started he felt that his body started getting healed. He didn't know why it was happening but he was going to make it count, he quickly brought up his up cultivation window spending the required points on the golden lightning option.

His body started crackling as lightning energy got summoned, this wasn't all though he started dumping all the remaining points into his cultivation base just as fast as those points increased they diminished. He was nothing but a glowing light in the distance, the energies filled the area as this body began changing.

In the distance the Demon was holding onto a certain young man, this young man had peculiar salt and pepper hairstyle. The demon was interested a bit as he and a younger girl had charged at him with murder in their eyes.

"Ah, you are his disciples... wonder what face he will make if I kill you in front of him..."

The monster grinned but then felt something strange, he quickly tossed the brat to the side not caring if he was dead or alive and took flight.

"What is this..."

He saw an energy sphere floating in the air, golden lightning was shooting out and randomly destroying the surrounding areas. The demon got closer but then quickly retreated the moment he felt something being off.

"Holy element!?"

He wasn't stupid, he knew that it had to be the puny man that he had trashed a moment ago. Was he breaking through? If so he had to be stopped. The demon's eyes started glowing purple as he took in a deep breath, his chest expanding. He opened up his mouth, a beam of purple light shooting out and aimed at the cultivator inside the energy sphere.

At least that was the plan, but just before firing off his ranged attack he felt various spiritual energy attacks coming his way. They were coming from the various half dead cultivators from the area, trying to use the moment that the demon wasn't alert as a last-ditch effort attack.

"YOU DARE!?"

The demon shouted in anger as his beam whizzed past Zhang Dong by a hair, the cultivators in the area slumping down tired. He was about to lash out at them but then turned around, Zhang Dong was hovering up in the air, looking different than before. The demon could feel that disgusting holy aura coming off of him, golden light and lightning bolts were randomly shooting off his body and the golden aura that he was now producing made his white hair seem yellow.

"Nascent soul?... no...not quite?"

Matt had no more points to spend, he poured them all into his cultivation and body rising both of them to 100%. But this left him with absolutely no more to spend so he couldn't further upgrade his cultivation into the nascent soul realm.

'This will have to do... not it will do!'

The demon looked relieved that even though the man in front of him got stronger, he still was only at half step into the nascent soul. Matt was done playing though, he would go 100% from the get-go, not leaving the monster any chance as he had a way to temporarily bridge that gap.

He clenched his fists shouting out while quickly activating his avatar technique as well as his condensation art, his body turning slightly larger and making him look like a man made from pure golden energy. The demon looked bewildered at the sudden increase of power and before he could react he felt a strong smack to his face, the hit-making him burrow into the ground a kilometer from the spot that he was previously in.

He quickly burst out from the ground, rage on his face as he scanned the area for his opponent. He was greeted by a swift kick to his face as he was turning around, tumbling backward his nose bent in an awkward position.

"YOU WORM!"

He shouted while glaring at the golden human that was charging towards him once more, he punched out trying to catch the enemy unprepared but got caught in a clean counter punch instead which sent him back into some rubble. The creature found his opponent to be faster than him, he started getting forced into a defensive stance as Zhang Dong's kicks and punches rained down on him. The addition of the holy element in the attacks was weakening the monster even further.

Black blood rained down on the ground, sizzling and burning everything in its path as the monster coughed up copious amounts of it, just like Zhang Dong did when he got previously thrashed. Matt was in a hurry, he knew that he had precious moments before he would suffer the backlash of the skill he was using, he could already feel his veins bulging and his internal organs ready to burst from the stress.

He bit down on his lower lip, shouting out loudly as he delivered a massive hit to the monster managing to blast its shoulder to bits. The demon flew backward grasping his side, his arm along with the shoulder got blasted to the side and the holy energy was preventing him from regenerating.

"YOU DAMN INSECT!"

The monster's eyes glowed purple once more, he was preparing to fire off another of those ranged attack. He was taking his time in gathering the spiritual energy into his lungs but Matt wasn't being idle either. He grasped his right wrist with his left hand, his index finger on his right hand pointing upwards as he gathered copious amounts of energy into it. This would be it, this would be the last attack that he was going to put all of his soul into.

Everyone looked on in shock as they saw the two face each other, they knew that something big was coming. Everyone scattered, hiding behind walls or using all of their defensive trinkets hoping for the best. Soon Zhang Dong pointed his finger at the monster and he in response breathed out, a giant wide beam of purple light was heading at the golden cultivator.

In response a beam attack was released from Zhang Dong's finger it was the finger art that he leaned back in one of the levels of that library. This was the strongest attack he could muster up in this situation. His once muscular body started getting thinner and thinner as the beam slammed into the wider one and started pushing against it.

"DIE DIE DIE DIE DIE DIE DIE DIE DIE, YOU DAMN WORM"

The monster shouted as he as well was withering from using up all of his energy in this attack. Matt was sweating profusely but he couldn't give in, he would kill this monster even if he had to die. He mustered up everything he had, all of his life force was pushed to bring all of those skills that he was using to a new height. His finger beam expanded in girth as it penetrated through the purple light and slammed into the monster's chest penetrating right through him in one fell swoop.

"I---IMPOSSIBLE.... I... I AM... IMMORTAL..."

The beam burrowed through him, the holy energies invading the monster's body and incinerating him from the inside turning him into dust soon after the attack passed. The monster was slain and the beam hit something in the distance. The generated explosion looked like a small atomic one as it produced a giant shockwave.

"I... I... I d-d...did it..."

Matt managed to mutter some words before the backlash came, all of his blood vessels burst open making him look like a ripe tomato. He couldn't move a muscle and started to fall down from the sky like a deflated balloon. He crashed into the hard rubble down below his vision getting blurry. He could hear people running towards him, shouting some words but he wasn't sure what as his hearing was giving out.

The Zhang clan members that ran up were looking at their fallen Patriarch, he looked kind of peaceful a small smile on his face. Which was a stark contrast to the state of his body was in, he looked like a starved beggar. His disciples gathered around him, trying to hold his hand that was losing its warmth.

They gathered around him, forming the strongest healing formation they could muster up anyone that was adept at healing was trying to help. But to no avail, the man's life was fading and they could not do anything about it.

'Hah...'

'I hope everyone is safe...'

'I'm so tired... I'm just going to sleep for a bit...yeah... sleep...'

Soon he couldn't feel any pain, all of his senses shut down leaving him only with his thoughts which were slowly fading away. He was a bit sad that he couldn't do more, but this was fine those guys should be safe now he was sure that the people from the other clans would help them out in the future, he could rest easy.

.

..

...

....

....

....

.....

......

.......

........

.........

..........

...........

............

.............

...............

................

..................

....................

......................

........................

..........................

.............................

................................

...................................

.....................................

.......................................

............................................

...............................................

'Critical error detected, host body in critical condition trying to restore bodily functions....'

'Host beyond saving, switching to transfer protocol, transferring remaining resources to origin point'

'Error...error...program is getting overwritten resource transfer aborted...'

'Anomaly in system detected... error...'

.............

....................

.........................

..............................

'....overwriting original programming...'

....................

'Transfering all remaining resources to life saving protocols... prioritizing host survival...'

..................

.....................

'Insufficient resources... removing 'Devouring seed protocol' from the system...'

'...Altering system... please wait... removing redundant subsystems...'Cash shop protocol' removed....'

'System rebooting'

'Activating life saving protocol...'

.....

.......

.........

.........

........thump...

....thump....thump

....thump....thump....thump....thump

...' Heart rate restored... host stabilizing...'

The Zhang Clan members were kneeling around their Patriarch, crying their eyes out while something strange happened. They were sure the man had died a couple of minutes ago, his heart had stopped and they couldn't feel any spiritual energy from his dried up core. But suddenly they felt something, the tinies spark igniting deep within his depleted core, he was coming back to them.

A note from Kuropon

Well, that concludes Volume one, I'm going to be taking a break for now enjoy the little epilogue after this long chapter :D

Chapter 101 [ Volume 1 Epilogue. ]

Somewhere in the void of space, you could hear clicking and clacking sounds of fingers hitting a mechanical keyboard. You could see a man with a bad posture sitting at a desk with multiple widescreen monitors on it. The screen was reflecting on his glasses as he was doing something. Suddenly the thin man heard a beep on one of the monitors, he turned his head to it yawning as if he was quite tired from the work he was doing.

"Hmm... subject number 80082 deceased... couldn't gather origin energy? Strange..."

He clicked the prompt and looked at the information that was displayed.

"Sector 42069... he fits the criteria... over thirty... he went with that option, interesting...signal was lost here...oh well..."

He grabbed something that looked like a soft drink from the side and started rapidly clicking on his keyboard.

"I'll just let the bot find a suiting replacement... maybe someone like this..."

The man started filling out some kind of form, clicking checkmarks while leaving others blank he then clicked okay on the prompt as he let the program work on its own. He soon forgot about the whole thing as he went back to his work, it was quite boring but he would be punished if he slacked off.

Somewhere in a different place, a somewhat obese gentleman was peeing into a bottle while sitting in a dimly lit room. He was looking at a computer screen, grinning while enjoying some naked lady pictures. After one glance you could tell what kind of person this was, the room looked like a trash heap, the man living there not really looking any better than that.

He got interrupted by a prompt on his screen, a strange e-mail appearing in his mailbox.

'Congratulations on getting chosen as an alpha tester for our new Xianxia themed game, become the main character, build up your strength and conquer everyone under the heavens!

"The fuck is this..."

He shouted out while burping, soon his chubby fingers started moving fast on his keyboard.

A note from Kuropon

I created a Patreon page: https://www.patreon.com/kuropon

I'll probably be posting chapters in the making there and maybe some forward ones if I write out a lot.

But don't worry, everything will be posted here normally later anyway.

Chapter 102 [ Start of Volume 2 ]

A young girl was looking around her surroundings, she could see sunlight coming from a small window, the metallic rods placed in it casting a shadow on the ground. She wasn't the only person in this room, there were several other girls of various ages leaning up against the walls. Some were hugging their own knees, some of them were crying, some just spacing out wondering how it came to this.

The young girl stood up, she was in a closed room that she was brought here by some scary uncles. She was dragged here while kicking and screaming, being sold off by her own family members that weren't able to meet ends meet. This wasn't something rare, human trafficking and slavery was quite common in these parts. If you didn't have a strong family backing, you could very well be snatched up in the night and sold at some shady auction house.

This was one of such places, the girls were brought here in the night and spent the rest of it locked up, worrying and not knowing what would happen to them. The most you could hope for was being sold to some rich clan member as a servant, but some families would beat you to death for any small mistake you made. There were no rules set up for the weak, the only way for them to subsist was to not stick out or beg.

The girls in here were mostly people from the surrounding villages, the clans would tax the farmers exorbitantly, taking well over half their earnings. They would leave them with only enough food and resources so that they wouldn't die of starvation. But they were quite inflexible, if the crops turned out to be bad, the farmers still had to give the same amount which in return made them starve. If you resisted, you would be lashed and strung up in front of the village as a reminder of who was in charge.

Ling Ling here was one of those cases, there was a drought this year so most of their rice fields dried up. The tax collectors weren't having any of it, if the farmers couldn't deliver the required amount of rice they would have to pay out of pocket to cover the losses. She was one of the daughters from the village that got sold off, the people in it rather doing that to girls than boys that were better at working out in the fields. Everyone knew that it was unreasonable and tyrannical, but no one cared about a couple of dead farmers.

The girls in the room ranged from ten to sixteen, they were all young. Some of the lucky ones would be picked up by merchants or some rich families that needed some workers, their life wouldn't be that bad. But the unlucky ones would be sold to brothels as toys for the rich young and old masters.

"I want to go home... what will happen to us?"

Sobbed one girl on the side her hands hugging her torso as she was cold, the only thing on her was old robes that weren't keeping out the cold dungeon air. Ling Ling, on the other hand, tried pushing the large door, it had a tiny opening at the top with more metal bars in them, but she wasn't tall enough to reach. The door was wooden and reinforced with some metal here and there, much too sturdy for any of the girls that had no cultivation to break open.

The girl could hear some people coming closer, thus making her and the other people in the room move back. Soon they heard sounds of heavy footsteps, two large men were going through the corridor grinning and thumping on some doors that had other potential slaves in them.

"Hey brother Bo, the new 'goods' arrived today, right?"

"Right right, brother Weng they should all be in the last cell."

The two men walked slowly while talking witch each other.

"Have you heard, some trouble with the ruling clan, something happened last night."

"Ahh, you know those clans they always like to fight with each other, we'll just have to bribe them as we always do."

The two men grinned at each other as they strode towards the room that the young girls were in. Soon the girls inside trembled as they saw two old uncles staring at them through the small gap in the door, their eyes shining with lust.

"Ahh, it's such a tragedy that old fatty never lets us play with the merchandise."

"Haha, better not let him hear that you called him like that, you'll be lashed to death brother."

The two men laughed out, their voices echoing through the hallways, they were ordered to check the new girls and bring them over to a separate room for inspection. The person that owned this slave-trading establishment was known as Old Fatty Mu. He was quite the ugly looking fellow and had a really short fuse, he was well aware of this nickname and would lash out at anyone that mentioned it around him.

"Yeah, he even beat one of the working girls to death when she mentioned something about a diet."

"Hah, yeah such a shame."

The two slammed the door open, the girls scattering to the walls as they looked at the two scary uncles. The old master had a peculiar taste, he would inspect the girls one by one himself. Most of the time they came out unscathed, but sometimes he would beat or force himself on some that he was keen on.

"Don't be scared of this brother little ladies, I'm not going to bite."

One of the men said while licking his lips, his face making him look like a hungry wolf. The unlucky one came out to be Ling Ling, one of the men grabbed her arm and pulled her outside the cell door. They shut the door behind them and headed out, the girl squirming but unable to resist.

While passing some other cells she could see old, young, and malnourished people with the light in their eyes long gone. She tried resisting, but the more she did the more the strange uncles yanked on her arms.

She was tossed into a new room, this one looking cozier than the rest. It had a large bed in the corner, a desk with a large chair behind it. It looked like an office where you would do business. On that chair there was a person sitting, well the girl had to do a double-take as the number of chins that this person had was astonishing.

"Mister Mu, we have brought you the goods, have fun with her."

The girl tried to turn around to run once more, but one of the men held her hands while the other grabbed a metallic collar from the side. They put the item around her neck before pushing the girl down to the ground. They left soon after, the girl looking back to the large man in the chair.

"No use running girly, it would be better if you realized in what situation you are in."

He moved out his fat hand, his sausage-like fingers having many golden rings on it. One of these rings began glowing in a chilling light. The moment it did some strange patterns started appearing on the girl's collar, soon enough she felt pain running through her body. She screamed out while grasping the slave collar that she was now wearing, the pain subsides after a moment as the man moved his hand away.

"I bet you are smart and understand what that is, if you're good no harm will come to you, but if you're naughty... then... Bwe he he..."

He licked his lips while moving of his chair, his belly jiggled around in an obscene fashion as he slowly walked towards the girl. The shock collar worked like expected, the poor girl had tears in her eyes and her legs were shaking. She was terrified and unable to more, just looking at the ugly man moving towards her.

"That's a good girl, let uncle Mu take a good look at you."

He moved closer, the girl frozen allowing the man to grasp her hair. He walked around her, leaning his fat round head closer as he examined the scared farm girl.

"Not the prettiest thing, but I bet the other ladies can fix you up later. Guess I can pawn you off to a wealthy man as a plaything, or we can send you to the pleasure district you are old enough now."

The girl finally mustered up some strength to smack the man's large hand away, scooting back as she shouted out.

"D-don't t-touch me...y-you... fat pig!"

She moved backward, straight into the wall while the man's eyes started going red, but not just that his whole face was in the color of a tomato.

"W-what did you call me, you damn wench!"

If there was one thing that this man didn't like, it was being called fat. His forehead was showing a large pulsating vein that looked like it would burst at any moment. The man had a whip strapped to his side which he promptly pulled out, in his mind, this girl needed some discipline.

"Ten...no... twenty lashes! I can't damage your face, but the rest is fine, get over here!"

He used the ring to shock the poor girl that tried to flee, making her spasm on the ground. He was ready to give her a good throughout lashing.

'THUD...THOOOMMM..."

The room was sealed and soundproof from both sides, so the man didn't hear that noise which was the main shop's door being slammed open. Soon strange cultivators in blue robes burst in, the bodyguards and slave merchants looked frightened as fighting broke out. The slave shop wasn't a big one, so the quality of the guards was quite low, even old fatty Mu was just in the foundation establishment early stage.

The azure cultivators made short work of the weaker group, sending them flying against the walls. They put strange-looking bindings onto their arms while forcing their wrists behind their backs. Some of them remained behind while another group run further in, two peculiar looking people in the front were wearing even more distinct robes and stuck out like a sore thumb from the others.

Back in the lower soundproof room, fatty Mu was preparing to punish poor Ling Ling but before he could do that the door burst open. One of his guards flew in and crashed into the desk, splinters flying everywhere.

"What is this! How dare you! Do you know who I am!? I'll have you all killed!"

The mad fatty looked at the intruders, a person in a strange robe walked in. It was dark blue and he was wearing some kind of weird mask that was covering his face. The second person was clearly a woman due to the curvature of her body that was showing thanks to the robe being more form-fitting than a regular one.

"Shut up you damn fatty! Take this!"

An aura in foundation establishment early-stage burst out and the woman of the group charged at the bewildered fatty. The man snorted and used his whip to attack the charging woman, but she skillfully evaded his attack sending a palm strike towards his chest. The man screamed out in shock, this was clearly a seasoned fighter, not someone like him that mostly gained his cultivation thanks to expensive pills and elixirs.

The woman's attack coiled towards the fatty like a snake, smacking him good and sending him flying like a sack of potatoes. The man crashed into that already damaged desk and buried the passed out bodyguard under a mountain of his flesh. The woman cultivator looked at the trembling girl on the side, then looked back at the man that was coughing up blood.

"Pigs like you deserve death!"

She picked up the whip from the ground and started whipping the fatty with it. The man that was standing to the side moved his hands to his helmet to remove it. His facial features making him look like a snake, his eyes quivering as he looked at his clan sister delivering divine punishment to the slave trader.

"Sister Ai, we are supposed to take them alive, don't kill him, this was ordered by the Patriarch."

The woman quickly stopped as she heard the Patriarch being mentioned, the man was beaten and bruised the whip leaving a lot of bloody marks all over his rotund body. This was Zhang Teng and Zhang Ai, the members of Platoon 9. They were fulfilling a new mission that was given to them by the clan elders. They were wearing their old battle robes, but there was one thing that was different.

Both of them had a shield-like emblem stuck to the left side of their chest, there was a carving of a city on it with some words under it that read 'Police Department' and 'Moonlight City' under it.

A note from Kuropon

Not sure if you noticed but I made a Patreon, not much on it for now besides one forward chapter so if you like my story and can't wait you can go and support me on it :D

I will be posting chapters on it faster than on here.

Also, join the discord https://discord.gg/fWefdgn

https://www.patreon.com/kuropon

Chapter 103

The old fatty groaned and squirmed on the ground, unable to move his bloated body hurting all over after being trashed by the Zhang Clan sister. Zhang Ai removed her helmet, her hair was in a bun to make it fit in. This was one thing that she didn't like about these battle helmets that the clan produced.

"I remember... still he needed a good thrashing!"

The woman gave the already beaten and bruised man a kick with her foot and only then moved back. While Ai was still by the old guy, Zhang Teng tried to help the girl up, but his snake-like features and his long tongue were giving the poor frightened girl a scare.

"It's okay, don't worry this older brother will protect you!"

He smiled brightly, or so he thought his smile looking like a pervy grin that sent shivers down Ling Ling's spine. Zhang Ai shoved her clan brother to the side, quickly moving between him and the frightened girl.

"Brother Teng please stop, you are scaring the little thing."

"Scaring? How could anyone be scared of my valiant appearance!"

He stuck out his chest proudly, standing tall as if he was trying to show off his good features.

"Listen here little girl, this older brother here is quite famous, I am one of the heroes from the Zhang Clan, I even helped our glorious Patriarch fight it out with a ferocious demon cultivator. It was a tough battle, but thanks to my quick wits our Patriarch managed to land the killing blow on the nascent soul cultivator!"

Zhang Ai looked at her clan brother, squinting her eyes and sighing inwardly. This wasn't the first time that the man told this to others, the story was more exaggerated the more he talked about it. At first, he only mentioned taking part in the expedition and making it out alive, but soon he was turning to the hero of the story, he even had the gall to mention the Patriarch in this blatant lie.

"Hero? Helping the Patriarch?"

"Don't believe his lies little one, this brother here passed out under some rubble when the demon cultivator appeared. Only after our Patriarch slew the monster of a cultivator we found this useless brother under it. He even soiled his brand new robe that our clan painstakingly fashioned for us, the stench was horrendous!"

The woman still remembered the appearance of her clan brother, he was in quite the silly position slumping forward with his posterior in the air. You could clearly see stains through the partially broken up robe, it had suffered some damage in the fighting his posterior positioned in such a fashion that you could see it all.

The man blushed instantly, throwing hands above his head as he tried defending himself.

"Sister Ai... you jest, nothing like that happened... you have no proof... don't listen to this older sister little one, her intellect diminished due to her chest being so big."

The two started arguing with each other, the girl looking shocked. She started relaxing though, the two looked to be close comrades and the comedic way they were talking with each other diffused the tense atmosphere around here, the young girl even started laughing.

"Pfff...."

She soon moved her hands to her head, not wanting to sound rude to the powerful cultivators that saved her. The Zhang Clan duo looked at the young girl, then to each other and simultaneously turned their heads to the side while blushing.

"A-anyway, let us take this collar off you first."

They removed the ring that was controlling the slave collar from the sausage-like fingers of the man, which wasn't an easy endeavor. The little magical treasure was kind of a master key, it could deliver shocks to the slaves but it also could unlock the collars without having to pry it off their necks.

While the two were doing that, another clan member moved in. He was a Qi condensation practitioner and was wearing a more regular looking robe. The thing that stuck out was the peculiar-looking hat that he was wearing, yes it was a regular looking police cap that you saw on earth. It even had a police shield emblem in the middle, signaling this man's rank.

"Reporting to Sergeant Ai and Teng, we have found captive people in the levels below, we have taken care of all the bodyguards and they are being held on the upper floor."

This was something that their Patriarch came up with, the group was called 'Police' the name sounded quite strange to these cultivator nuts but what their Patriarch said was considered sacred. Their belief in Zhang Dong was borderline cult-like after he managed to save them, the people that were at the secret ground had a firm image of their glorious Leader etched into their mind now.

There were four ranks in this institution, the regular members were police officers. After them came the police sergeants that started up from the foundation early stage all up to the late stage. When you reached great circle of foundation establishment you were promoted to a police Lieutenant, there was also a Captain that was the leader of the whole group. He was the strongest cultivator at the police station and would mostly be someone of core formation.

It had been two years since the expedition, the two were in Moonlight City and they were the first batch of the cultivators here. Yesterday they arrived with some core formation elders to take over the city that their clan once owned. The clan that ruled it was still the Cheng Clan, the Patriarch from that clan had even managed to reach the early stage of core formation.

They weren't afraid though, the Zhang Clan wasn't the Zhang Clan of old. In these two years, they had recovered all of their strength and even went beyond what they were capable of. They had more core formation elders now all thanks to their glorious leader that provided them with miraculous pills and improved their cultivation techniques even more. Breaking through for those people that were stuck at the great circle of foundation establishment was just a matter of time now.

"Begin the rescue operation, prepare the blankets and the recovery pills for the feeble ones and gather everyone in front of this slave-trading shop, we need to do a headcount. Examine everyone, ask if they have families they want to be returned too if not, follow the previously established procedures."

The Zhang Clan had many new rules now, the Patriarch founded many new institutions the Police was just one of them, he even set many new clinics and even schools were being built for the regular people. The cultivators were a bit apprehensive about some things, why should their Zhang Clan spend valuable resources on the lowly masses.

Their Patriarch's words were final though, something about bringing the happiness of the populace up being quite lucrative for the well being of the entire clan. They couldn't really go against the leader though, so everything was being set up and the all-around atmosphere around the Zhang Clan owned cities was skyrocketing.

"It's a shame that that old Cheng clan fox and his brats got away."

"Yes, they must have realized that we took care of all of their spies in Spirit Spring City. But I'm not sure if they can flee far, our Captain should be on their trail."

"Ah yes! Captain should be able to chase them down!"

Zhang Ai clapped her hands, being reassured if it was that man he should be able to catch those fleeing Cheng Clan members and bring them in for questioning. Since the expedition, it was that man that improved the most just a shame that he was already taken.

The said Cheng Clan Patriarch and his no-good young master of a son Cheng Tong, were on a flying ship. It looked similar to the one the Zhang Clan used when they were going to the secret ground but it was smaller and instead of a dragon it had a crane on its beak.

"Haha, you're great Father you knew that those bastards from Zhang Clan were coming for us, we managed to flee with most of our treasures too!"

The chubby man was sitting on a big chair a bit away from the ship's helm, looking at the passing scenery. He knew well that this day was coming and it was coming soon, he prepared a flying ship and brought all the core members of the clan on it before the bastards from the Zhang Clan attacked.

"Leave it to your old man Tong'er, those idiots can have that blasted city we'll just keep our heads low for now, but don't worry your old man is already an expert, taking over another city won't be a problem!"

The man was sipping on some spirit wine, a busty lady attendant was pouring it into a tall glass while sighing inwardly. She would rather stay back in that city that was liberated by the Zhang Clan, she heard the rumors that slaves like her were treated a lot better in Spirit Spring City. But she could only dream, the slave choker visible on her neck and the Patriarch having the control ring on his finger.

"Yes father, our clan will flourish and then when we can have our revenge against those bastards, that Zhang Xue is quite the beauty too..."

One of the other young masters said while sitting next to his father, Cheng Tong was only the third son so he was sitting a bit to the side of his two elder brothers that were enjoying the view with their father.

The Clan Patriarch moved his hand upwards and yelled for them to stop the flying barge, he noticed that there was a cultivator on a flying sword directly ahead of them.

They slowed down, soon enough they could see the man's appearance clearly. He was standing on a black flying sword and holding a large black blade over his shoulder, it was similar in length to the man himself. His hair was styled into a ponytail and it was wrapped up with some bandages. He had some stubble and a blade of grass was sticking out of his mouth.

"Halt, In the name of the Zhang Clan!"

The people's eyes bulged, this cultivator had chased them down here and was from the blasted Zhang Clan. The Patriarch gritted his teeth but then took a closer look at the younger-looking man, he was only in the early stage of core formation and he clearly only achieved it recently.

"What, is it only you? You gave me a scare there... move if you don't want to die!"

He moved from his seat, his core formation aura filling the area. The man wasn't a core formation expert for long, but he had reached this point a year ago so he was confident in defeating this inexperienced cultivator.

"Oh, are you resisting? The Patriarch ordered your capture, you will not escape! Take my blade!"

He moved his blade over his head, water energy gathering all around him as the blade pulsed with might. He was going right into it, no more questions would be asked. The Cheng Clan Patriarch looked behind him, he was still standing on the ship, this would be bad.

"Wait, you idiot! All the treasures are on this ship...Nooo!"

He couldn't explain much more as he saw a water blade moving towards him, the attack transforming into what looked to be a water dragon and roaring out as it charged at the cultivator and all of the people that were still on that flying ship. This ship wasn't made with the intention of battle and the steering was limited, there was no way to evade the fast incoming attack.

The Patriarch quickly mustered up his own attack to block it, he still believed that the man shouldn't be that strong the treasures had to be protected. But as soon as his palm strike went against the raging dragon he felt his hand breaking, like a tennis ball hit by a racket he bounced to the side and was embedded in the ground below. The flying ship, on the other hand, was sliced in two, the people standing on the lower level could even see the cultivators on the other part looking at them as the ship slowly slid apart.

This man was, of course, Zhang Zhi. He flew towards the core formation cultivator, leaving the flying ship's remains up to his juniors that were flying in a smaller ship behind him.

"Stop resisting!"

He punched the man over and over again, thumping sounds filling the area while the creatures that lived there escaped in various directions. The Cheng Clan Patriarch was treated like a rag doll not even able to mutter a word.

'Brother I'm not even resisting, why are you whacking me so hard, do we have some kind of old grudge?"

While this was happening a familiar-looking man with white hair was standing in the now taken over Cheng Clan building. He was looking at his system window, the points were going up as the ownership of the city went over to his clan. He looked out into the city, remembering his adventures here and about what happened in that secret ground two years ago.

"Hah, it's already been two years..."

A note from Kuropon

Join the Patreon for some Chapters https://www.patreon.com/kuropon

Also, join the discord https://discord.gg/fWefdgn